<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-09-25T00:14:36.164Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Publish an npm Package - Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>68d44cc07b532bf921e47213</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-publish-an-npm-package/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T19:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve spent any time working with JavaScript, you’ve most likely come across npm—whether installing packages like Express, Lodash, or React, or running commands like npm init. While using npm is second nature for many JavaScript developers, some ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikegah Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Dependency Injection in Go - Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>68d44505e26e6f1a24c44ba9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-dependency-injection-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T19:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regardless of their initial size or scope, projects tend to grow in complexity over time. As new features are added and requirements evolve, the number of components and the connections between them multiply. Services, handlers, repositories, externa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabor Koos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fix Memory Leaks in React Applications]]></title>
        <id>68d443c623251efd1f372d02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fix-memory-leaks-in-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T19:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed your React application getting slower the longer you use it? This could be a result of memory leaks. Memory leaks are a common performance issue in React applications. They can slow down your application, crash your browser, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olaleye Blessing</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does a Creative Technologist Do?]]></title>
        <id>68d43e64c21b03de37bb4dce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-does-a-creative-technologist-do/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T18:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On paper, I studied computer science. However, most of my passions were artistic: writing, storytelling, and content creation. Over time, I found myself blending both worlds without recognizing it. Then I came across the term Creative Technologist an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ifeoma Udu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intent Prototyping: The Allure And Danger Of Pure Vibe Coding In Enterprise UX (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/intent-prototyping-pure-vibe-coding-enterprise-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/intent-prototyping-pure-vibe-coding-enterprise-ux/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yegor Gilyov examines the problem of over-reliance on static high-fidelity mockups, which often leave the conceptual model and user flows dangerously underdeveloped. He then explores whether AI-powered prototyping is the answer, questioning whether the path forward is the popular “vibe coding” approach or a more structured, intent-driven approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Yegor Gilyov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Typed Arithmetic]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389371</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-typed-arithmetic/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-24T12:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting in Chrome 140, we'll be able to calculate numeric values with mixed data types. Sounds small, but Amit demonstrates how big a deal this is, calling it Computational CSS.
CSS Typed Arithmetic originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amit Sheen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Search in JavaScript with Debouncing]]></title>
        <id>68d2d63ab7bb607e13c45cf4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-search-in-javascript-with-debouncing/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-23T17:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few months ago, my manager assigned me a task: implement a search functionality across an entire page. The tricky part was that the displayed text was shown in the form of prompts, and each prompt could be truncated after two lines. If the text exc...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajay Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code an LLM From Scratch – Theory to RLHF]]></title>
        <id>68d29469c234e0ab00c1b00a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-an-llm-from-scratch-theory-to-rlhf/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-23T12:36:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do LLMs actually work? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to build a large language model from scratch using pure PyTorch. This isn't your typical course that just scratches the surface. It’s a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Facial Recognition Authentication in a Social App with Face API]]></title>
        <id>68d20d7a6bd072175081e6b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integrate-facial-recognition-authentication-in-a-social-application/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-23T03:01:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social applications have evolved over the years, and there is a major need for secure methods to authenticate users' identities. Integrating multifactor authentication capabilities into applications is crucial for strengthening their integrity. In so...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clerk vs Kinde vs Better Auth: How to Choose the Right Next.js Authentication Library]]></title>
        <id>68d2074ea281a4364a16d324</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-the-right-nextjs-authentication-library/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-23T02:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Authentication is an important aspect when building applications, especially if they hold financial information or require users to sign into accounts. Building an auth library can be a lot of work, and there is no need to reinvent the wheel when so ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Baisden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Advanced AI Agents]]></title>
        <id>68d15f138a2020e83f638df2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-advanced-ai-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-22T14:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking to get hands-on with AI? We just posted a comprehensive course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel designed to help you build powerful AI agent applications. Led by Cerebras growth engineer Sarah Chieng alongside industry experts from Exa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambient Animations In Web Design: Principles And Implementation (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/ambient-animations-web-design-principles-implementation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/ambient-animations-web-design-principles-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating motion can be tricky. Too much and it’s distracting. Too little and a design feels flat. Ambient animations are the middle ground — subtle, slow-moving details that add atmosphere without stealing the show. In this article, web design pioneer Andy Clarke introduces the concept of ambient animations and explains how to implement them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Documentation that Helps Your Tech Community Grow]]></title>
        <id>68cde1bb85ffecd5a404fc5f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-documentation-that-helps-your-tech-community-grow/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T23:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good documentation is the backbone of a supported and empowered community. From the moment someone new joins and finds a clear guide to get started, to the experienced member who can quickly find a process, well-organized information saves everyone t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oladeji Oluwaseun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Tokenize Text in Python — Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>68cdb0341432174e4c7f6898</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-tokenize-text-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T19:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with Python, you may need to perform a tokenization operation on a given text dataset. Tokenization is the process of breaking down text into smaller pieces, typically words or sentences, which are called tokens. These tokens can then be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>AYUSH MISHRA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Chess and Become a Better Developer with Ihechikara Abba (ELO rating of 2285) [Podcast #189]]]></title>
        <id>68cd6ffad57a0c65e2ff97bf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-chess-and-become-a-better-developer-with-ihechikara-abba-elo-rating-of-2285-podcast-189/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's freeCodeCamp podcast we're talking with software engineer Ihechikara Abba, who has a chess ELO rating of 2285, putting him among top competitive chess players. We just published his freeCodeCamp course on chess end games, and an accomp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Brief Introduction to SQLite]]></title>
        <id>68cd625e82b856dadd4cceba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-brief-introduction-to-sqlite/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T14:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQLite is one of the most underappreciated tools in a developer's toolkit. It's a full-featured relational database that runs directly in your application. No server setup. No configuration files. No network protocols. Just a simple library that give...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On inclusive personas and inclusive user research]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389157</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/on-inclusive-personas-and-inclusive-user-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T13:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A set of notes taken from Eric Bailey's article about the use of inclusive personas and user research.
On inclusive personas and inclusive user research originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Nano Banana for Image Generation - Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>68cd5897ffbf18457f7bb85a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nano-banana-for-image-generation/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T13:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is changing the image generation and editing process into a smooth workflow. Now, with just a single prompt, you can tell your computer to generate or edit an existing image. Google just launched its new model for image generation or editing, "Nan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Store Data Locally with Isar in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>68cd561cebc0d959d789d679</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/store-data-locally-with-isar-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T13:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building Flutter applications, managing local data efficiently is critical. You want a database that is lightweight, fast, and easy to integrate, especially if your app will work offline. Isar is one such database. It is a high-performance, easy...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Psychology Of Trust In AI: A Guide To Measuring And Designing For User Confidence]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/psychology-trust-ai-guide-measuring-designing-user-confidence/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/psychology-trust-ai-guide-measuring-designing-user-confidence/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With digital products moving to incorporate generative and agentic AI at an increasingly frequent rate, trust has become the invisible user interface. When it works, interactions feel seamless. When it fails, the entire experience collapses. But trust isn’t mystical. It can be understood, measured, and designed for. Here are practical methods and strategies for designing more trustworthy and ethical AI systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for the Databricks Data Engineer Associate Certification Exam – And Pass!]]></title>
        <id>68cc9f07cb384618613c356d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-the-databricks-data-engineer-associate-certification-exam-and-pass/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-19T00:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for the Databricks Data Engineer Associate Certification exam and pass! We just posted a new course from Andrew Brown on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you earn the Databricks Data Engineer Associate Certification. This c...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing New freeCodeCamp Certifications in the Full Stack Developer Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>68cc7258080e9a4dee6b7952</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introducing-freecodecamp-checkpoint-certifications/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-18T20:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of CompTIA and the rigor of their certifications. I wanted freeCodeCamp's new Full Stack Developer cert to be similarly rigorous. But I made one major miscalculation. I underestimated people's desire to earn certifications within less t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Authentication and Authorization in ASP.NET]]></title>
        <id>68cc3e9e6c4695a8ff386d48</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-authentication-and-authorization-in-aspnet/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-18T17:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing modern web applications is an important skill for any developer, and a foundational part of this is understanding how to manage user access. We just posted new course on the freeCodeCamp.org that will teach you about authentication and autho...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Minimize The Environmental Impact Of Your Website]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/how-minimize-environmental-impact-website/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/how-minimize-environmental-impact-website/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As responsible digital professionals, we are becoming increasingly aware of the environmental impact of our work and need to find effective and pragmatic ways to reduce it. James Chudley shares a new decarbonising approach that will help you to minimise the environmental impact of your website, benefiting people, profit, purpose, performance, and the planet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (James Chudley)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Multimodal Makaton-to-English Translator for Accessible Education]]></title>
        <id>68cb5e6df1766dffdd20f610</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multimodal-translator-for-accessible-education/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-18T01:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A year nine student walks into class full of ideas, but when it is time to contribute, the tools around them do not listen. Their speech is difficult for standard voice systems to recognise, typing feels slow and exhausting, and the lesson moves on w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OMOTAYO OMOYEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does Cosine Similarity Work? The Math Behind LLMs Explained]]></title>
        <id>68cb5c87b90c34f2f16f5703</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-cosine-similarity-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-18T01:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you talk to a large language model (LLM), it feels like the model understands meaning. But under the hood, the system relies on numbers, vectors, and math to find the relationships between words and sentences. One of the most important tools tha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is it Time to Un-Sass?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389101</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/is-it-time-to-un-sass/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-17T14:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many of the Sass features we've grown to love have made their way into native CSS in some shape or form. So, should we still use Sass? This is how developer Jeff Bridgforth is thinking about it.
Is it Time to Un-Sass? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Bridgforth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Loops in C#]]></title>
        <id>68caa6382769a3737407de1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-loops-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-17T12:14:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing the same code repeatedly is poor practice in C# and doesn’t follow the Don’t Repeat Yourself (DRY) principle. But, there are many times in programming where you need to repeat commands, operations, or computations multiple times — perhaps cha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use ObjectBox in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>68c9995460a5f06c06227f63</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-objectbox-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-16T17:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ObjectBox is a high-performance, lightweight, NoSQL embedded database built specifically for Flutter and Dart applications. It provides reactive APIs, indexes, relationships, and migrations, all designed to make local data management smooth and effic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SerpApi: A Complete API For Fetching Search Engine Data]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/serpapi-complete-api-fetching-search-engine-data/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/serpapi-complete-api-fetching-search-engine-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-16T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From competitive SEO research and monitoring prices to training AI and parsing local geographic data, real-time search results power smarter apps. Tools like SerpApi make it easy to pull, customize, and integrate this data directly into your app or website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Preethi Sam)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functional Personas With AI: A Lean, Practical Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/functional-personas-ai-lean-practical-workflow/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/functional-personas-ai-lean-practical-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-16T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For too long, personas have been created with considerable effort, only to offer limited value. Paul Boag shows how to breathe new life into this stale UX asset and demonstrates that it’s possible to create truly useful functional personas in a lightweight way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Your Own Code Editor]]></title>
        <id>68c827a7023360e7e4bf5f8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-your-own-code-editor/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-15T14:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can you code a code editor in a code editor that you coded? We just published a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel where you’ll learn how to build your own browser-based code editor. In this tutorial, developer Mohammed Al Abrah walks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: cos() and sin()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389130</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-most-hated-css-feature-cos-and-sin/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-15T14:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to look at practical uses for CSS trigonometric functions. And we'll start with what may be the most popular functions of the "worst" feature: sin() and cos().
The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: cos() and sin() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Elastic And Bounce Effects With Expressive Animator]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/creating-elastic-bounce-effects-expressive-animator/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/creating-elastic-bounce-effects-expressive-animator/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elastic and bounce effects have long been among the most desirable but time-consuming techniques in motion design. Expressive Animator streamlines the process, making it possible to produce lively animations in seconds, bypassing the tedious work of manual keyframe editing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marius Sarca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with Collections in Go Using the Standard Library Helpers]]></title>
        <id>68c4a25692f6fb350ff863d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-collections-in-go-using-the-standard-library-helpers/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T22:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous article—Arrays, Slices, and Maps in Go: a Quick Guide to Collection Types—we explored Go's three built-in collection types and how they work under the hood. That gave us the foundation for storing and accessing data efficiently. But in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabor Koos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Python GUI Apps in GitHub Codespaces with Xvfb and noVNC]]></title>
        <id>68c4a196984613262158d040</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/run-python-gui-in-github-codespaces/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T22:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Codespaces gives you a full development environment in the cloud, directly in your browser. It’s great for writing and running code, but there’s one big limitation: it doesn’t support graphical applications out of the box, especially for Pytho...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayodele Aransiola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Transformer Models Work for Language Processing]]></title>
        <id>68c44ccedcb860533312bf30</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-transformer-models-work-for-language-processing/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T16:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever used Google Translate, skimmed through a quick summary, or asked a chatbot for help, then you’ve definitely seen Transformers at work. They’re considered the architects behind today’s biggest advances in natural language processing (NL...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Transformer Models for Language Processing]]></title>
        <id>68c44ccedcb860533312bf30</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-transformer-models-for-language-processing/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T16:39:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever used Google Translate, skimmed through a quick summary, or asked a chatbot for help, then you’ve definitely seen Transformers at work. They’re considered the architects behind today’s biggest advances in natural language processing (NL...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Data To Decisions: UX Strategies For Real-Time Dashboards]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/ux-strategies-real-time-dashboards/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/ux-strategies-real-time-dashboards/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Real-time dashboards are decision assistants, not passive displays. In environments like fleet management, healthcare, and operations, the cost of a delay or misstep is high. Karan Rawal explores strategic UX patterns that shorten time-to-decision, reduce cognitive overload, and make live systems trustworthy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Karan Rawal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Can We Actually Do With corner-shape?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389060</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-can-we-actually-do-with-corner-shape/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T14:20:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started messing around with code, rounded corners required five background images or an image sprite likely created in Photoshop, so when border-radius came onto the scene, I remember everybody thinking that it was the best thing ever. …
What Can We Actually Do With corner-shape? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playing the Developer Job Search Game to Win in 2025 with Danny Thompson & Leon Noel [Podcast #188]]]></title>
        <id>68c42771b2d1879f98d1094b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/playing-the-developer-job-search-game-to-win-in-2025-with-danny-thompson-and-leon-noel-podcast-188/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T14:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this week's interview, we've got a special treat. Quincy Larson talking with two legends in the self-taught developer community. Danny Thompson worked for 10 years at a Tennessee gas station, frying chicken for people to eat, sometimes working 80...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Front-End Developers Should Understand UI/UX Design]]></title>
        <id>68c4087abba5a7e638ae4cd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-front-end-developers-should-understand-uiux-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T11:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When users interact with a website or application, the first thing they notice isn’t the code. Instead, it’s the design and experience. Smooth navigation, intuitive layouts, and visually appealing interfaces are what keep users engaged. Behind these ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Asfak Ahmed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt Engineering Cheat Sheet for GPT-5: Learn These Patterns for Solid Code Generation]]></title>
        <id>68c3f6454edd0f63eaaf098e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prompt-engineering-cheat-sheet-for-gpt-5/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-12T10:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When large language models like ChatGPT first became widely available, a lot of us developers felt like we’d been handed a new superpower. We could use LLMs to help us develop new coding projects, build websites, and much more – just using a few prom...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling Multiple CSS Files into One]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389117</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/compiling-multiple-css-files-into-one/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-11T15:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stu Robson outlines two ways to compile multiple CSS files when you aren't relying on Sass for it.
Compiling Multiple CSS Files into One originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Secure Web Applications with PHP, Symfony, and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>68c2cf0fe8903924be3e8c8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-secure-web-applications-with-php-symfony-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-11T13:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data breaches are a constant threat, and traditional encryption practices often aren't enough to protect sensitive information throughout its entire lifecycle. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Every Student Should Join Hackathons]]></title>
        <id>68c2272573bc3e829c0afc65</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-every-student-should-join-hackathons/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-11T01:34:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After graduation, I noticed many fresh grads struggling to land jobs. It wasn’t because they lacked effort or qualifications. The real issue was that what we learn in university doesn’t fully match what employers are looking for. Now, with the rise o...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tech With RJ</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend CRUD Operations to Align with Business Workflows]]></title>
        <id>68c19bc01159a9ac851f6cb5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extend-crud-operations-to-align-with-business-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-10T15:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most developers are introduced to databases and APIs through a simple pattern: CRUD—Create, Read, Update, Delete. It seems like the perfect abstraction. With just four operations, you can model almost anything. Tutorials use it. Frameworks generate i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Kleier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Game Development by Building Your First Platformer with Godot]]></title>
        <id>68c1848b89889b1c80036d24</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-game-development-by-building-your-first-platformer-with-godot/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-10T14:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wanted to build your own video game but felt overwhelmed by where to start? We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you step-by-step from a blank screen to a complete, playable game using the powerful a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’re Your Top 4 CSS Properties?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388800</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whatre-your-top-4-css-properties/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-10T13:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone has a different opinion which is great because it demonstrates the messy, non-linear craft that is thinking like a front-end developer.
What’re Your Top 4 CSS Properties? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Design Accessible Browser Extensions]]></title>
        <id>68c169e7d950044818727fd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-design-accessible-browser-extensions/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-10T12:07:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a browser extension is easy, but ensuring that it’s accessible to everyone takes deliberate care and skill. Your extension might fetch data flawlessly and have a beautiful interface, but if screen reader users or keyboard navigators can’t us...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ophy Boamah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating CSS Cascade Layers To An Existing Project]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/integrating-css-cascade-layers-existing-project/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/integrating-css-cascade-layers-existing-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea behind this is to share a full, unfiltered look at integrating CSS Cascade Layers into an existing legacy codebase. In practice, it’s about refactoring existing CSS to use cascade layers without breaking anything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Ayomipo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Store Data Locally Using Hive in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>68c03b5738ba5d78dfb7c607</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-store-data-locally-using-hive-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-09T14:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we’ll build a Flutter application that demonstrates how to perform CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) operations using Hive for local data storage. Hive is a lightweight, fast key-value database written in pure Dart. Unlike SQLite,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate API Documentation Updates with GitHub Actions and OpenAPI Specifications]]></title>
        <id>68c0398aeff4d53c8494c5ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-automate-api-documentation-updates-with-github-actions-and-openapi-specifications/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-09T14:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining up-to-date API documentation is often one of the biggest pain points for developers and teams. Too often, the API spec changes but the docs lag behind, leaving developers with outdated or inconsistent information. This frustrates consumer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EZINNE ANNE EMILIA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Production-Ready Web Apps with the Hono Framework: A Deep Dive]]></title>
        <id>68bf3ea02c935a9d306bb65a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-production-ready-web-apps-with-hono/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T20:37:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a dev, you’d probably like to write your application once and not have to worry so much about where it's going to run. This is what the open source framework Hono lets you do, and it’s a game-changer. Hono is a small, incredibly fast web framework...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mayur Vekariya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Smart Expense Tracker with Python and LLMs]]></title>
        <id>68bef0e832085a1cd1a86107</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-smart-expense-tracker-with-python-and-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you’re sipping a hot latte from Starbucks on your way to work. You quickly swipe your card, and the receipt gets lost in your bag. Later in the day, you pay for an Uber ride, order lunch, and buy airtime. By evening, you know you’ve spen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Happiness Omale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Submit an App to the iOS App Store]]></title>
        <id>68beece9aaba834ff6c89ad9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-submit-an-app-to-the-ios-app-store/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T14:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iOS App Store submission process can feel like a daunting maze, but it doesn’t have to be. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel is designed to be your guide through this entire process, from start to finish. Shad Rayhan...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Postman Scripts to Simplify Your API Authentication Process]]></title>
        <id>68bee731d2147595571c5b44</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-postman-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T14:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Postman is a platform used by developers, API testers, technical writers and DevOps teams for testing, documenting and collaborating on API development. It provides a user-friendly interface for making different types of API requests (HTTP, GraphQL, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Orim Dominic Adah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With Navigation in Flutter Using AutoRoute]]></title>
        <id>68bee239d2147595571c5b1a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-navigation-in-flutter-using-autoroute/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T14:03:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigation is one of the most important parts of any mobile application. Users expect to move seamlessly between screens such as home, settings, profile, and more. While Flutter provides built-in navigation using Navigator, managing routes can quickl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composition in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388424</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/composition-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-08T13:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS is a composable language by nature. This composition nature is already built into the cascade. We simply don't talk about composition as a Big Thing because it's the nature of the language.
Composition in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zell Liew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is New in Go 1.25? Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>68bb7a5a881edef26f226cde</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-new-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-06T00:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go 1.25 isn’t a flashy release with big syntax changes. Instead, it’s a practical one: it fixes long-standing pitfalls, improves runtime safety, adds smarter tooling, and introduces a powerful new JSON engine. These are the kind of updates that make ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arrays, Slices, and Maps in Go: a Quick Guide to Collection Types]]></title>
        <id>68bb12907f6ca0ada2df447f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/arrays-slices-and-maps-in-go-a-quick-guide-to-collection-types/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T16:40:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Golang has a reputation for simplicity, and one reason is its small set of core data structures. Unlike some languages that offer lists, vectors, dictionaries, hashmaps, tuples, sets, and more, Go keeps things minimal. The three fundamental building ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabor Koos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Upload Service in Flutter Web with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>68bb0031e67497d3bf64ec82</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-upload-service-in-flutter-web-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T15:22:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Uploading files is one of the most common requirements in modern web applications. Whether it’s profile pictures, documents, or bulk uploads, users expect a smooth and reliable experience. With Flutter Web and Firebase Storage, you can implement this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI Study Planner Agent using Gemini in Python]]></title>
        <id>68baff7226d95038487cbb1f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-ai-study-planner-agent-using-gemini-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T15:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world is shifting from simple AI chatbots answering our queries to full-fledged systems that are capable of so much more. AI Agents can not only answer our queries but can also perform tasks we give them independently, making them much more power...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing freeCodeCamp Daily Python and JavaScript Challenges – Solve a New Programming Puzzle Every Day]]></title>
        <id>68bafb5703bcabb153325d47</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/introducing-freecodecamp-daily-python-and-javascript-challenges-solve-a-new-programming-puzzle-every-day/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T15:01:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community is excited to announce that our new Daily Coding Challenges are ready for you to tackle. 🎊 Consistent practice is one of the most effective ways to improve your coding skills. So in addition to the core coding curriculum, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Mondloch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to focus on building your skills when everything's so distracting with Ania Kubów [Podcast #187]]]></title>
        <id>68bafafeb9e1fc8577966b86</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-focus-on-building-your-skills-when-everythings-so-distracting-with-ania-kubow-podcast-187/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T15:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this week's interview, Quincy is talking with Ania Kubów. She's a software engineer and prolific programming teacher on YouTube. She shares tips for: Getting into game development and using JavaScript and browser games as an entry point How to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About CSS Color Interpolation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388479</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-you-need-to-know-about-css-color-interpolation/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-05T13:44:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Color what? Sunkanmi Fafowora explains how an everyday task for CSS can be used to create better colors experiences.  
What You Need to Know About CSS Color Interpolation originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Fine-Tune Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>68b99deeba241d08aec7ff6f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-fine-tune-large-language-models/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-04T14:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning helps you become a master and professional in AI engineering. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that offers a comprehensive guide to fine-tuning LLMs, taking you from the basics to advanced practical applicat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing For TV: Principles, Patterns And Practical Guidance (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/designing-tv-principles-patterns-practical-guidance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/09/designing-tv-principles-patterns-practical-guidance/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After covering in detail the underlying interaction paradigms of TV experiences in [Part 1](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/designing-tv-evergreen-pattern-shapes-tv-experiences/), it’s time to get practical. In the second part of the series, you’ll explore the building blocks of the “10-foot experience” and how to best utilise them in your designs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Milan Balać)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enhance Images with Neural Networks]]></title>
        <id>68b8e1073c8fb81fc2265eef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enhance-images-with-neural-networks/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-04T00:44:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is changing how we work with images. What once took hours in Photoshop can now happen in seconds with AI-powered tools. You can take a blurry picture, enlarge it without losing sharpness, fix the lighting, remove unwanted nois...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started With GoRouter in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>68b8dda2076b23349200d66a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-gorouter-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-04T00:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating between screens in Flutter is crucial for any app. And while the built-in Navigator API provides functionality, it can get complex for larger projects. This is where go_router shines, offering a more declarative, URL-based, and feature-ric...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Sentence Similarity Check Using Sentence Transformers]]></title>
        <id>68b86d04b7b16a9a0d9ce2d2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-sentence-similarity-check-using-sentence-transformers/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T16:29:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sentence similarity plays an important role in many natural language processing (NLP) applications.  Whether you build chatbots, recommendation systems, or search engines, understanding how close two sentences are in meaning can improve user experien...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Node.js Event Loop Works]]></title>
        <id>68b86cca911797ceb3fd37e0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-nodejs-event-loop-works/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T16:28:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Node.js event loop is a concept that may seem difficult to understand at first. But as with any seemingly complex subject, the best way to understand it is often through an analogy. In this article, you’ll learn how overworked managers, busy wait...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amanda Ene Adoyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graph Algorithms in Python: BFS, DFS, and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>68b86be0956e509211153b48</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/graph-algorithms-in-python-bfs-dfs-and-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T16:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how Google Maps finds the fastest route or how Netflix recommends what to watch? Graph algorithms are behind these decisions. Graphs, made up of nodes (points) and edges (connections), are one of the most powerful data structur...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oyedele Tioluwani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an AI Coding Agent in Python]]></title>
        <id>68b849526e3b7913adba6793</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-coding-agent-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T13:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This isn’t just your average AI agent tutorial. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is all about action! Lane Wagner of boot.dev will teach you to build your very own AI coding agent from scratch. Using Python and the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Mandarin Chinese for Beginners – Full HSK 1 Level]]></title>
        <id>68b847e923e7c29bdb07709b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mandarin-chinese-for-beginners-full-hsk-1-level/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T13:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just published a full beginner's course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you the fundamentals of Mandarin Chinese. This course is designed to guide you to the HSK 1 level. The Hanyu Shuiping Kaoshi (HSK) is China's official ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Bluetooth on Android More Reliable]]></title>
        <id>68b78f7fba46c4e7c6266797</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-bluetooth-on-android-more-reliable/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have had this happen before: your wireless earbuds connect perfectly one day, and the next they act like they’ve never met your phone. Or your smartwatch drops off in the middle of a run. Bluetooth is amazing when it works, but maddening when...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Save and Share Flutter Widgets as Images – A Complete Production-Ready Guide]]></title>
        <id>68b75671263a4383838a1d8a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-save-and-share-flutter-widgets-as-images-a-complete-production-ready-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-02T20:41:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many apps, you may want users to be able to save or share visual content generated in the UI. Flutter doesn’t ship with a “save widget to image” API, but with RepaintBoundary plus a few small packages, you can capture any widget, save it to the de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become an Expert in AI-Assisted Coding – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>68b754eb90a7b8458d3a959f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-an-expert-in-ai-assisted-coding-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-02T20:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine writing code 3-4x faster while maintaining quality. That's what AI-assisted development can offer. In simple terms, you can be more productive with AI tools like GitHub Copilot as your coding partner. They suggest code, help you debug, and sp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mrugesh Mohapatra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Common Open Source Contribution Myths – Debunked]]></title>
        <id>68b703ede63728a780d3fc1f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/common-open-source-contribution-myths-debunked/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-02T14:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many developers shy away from contributing to open source, as it can be intimidating and hard to get started. Even though your contributions might seem inconsequential at first, they can potentially have a huge impact on your career. In this article,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Orim Dominic Adah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should the CSS light-dark() Function Support More Than Light and Dark Values?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388888</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/should-the-css-light-dark-function-support-more-than-light-and-dark-values/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-02T14:44:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The light-dark() function is currently designed to support just two color schemes. Should it support others? Sunkanmi Fafowora says yes and no.
Should the CSS light-dark() Function Support More Than Light and Dark Values? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build AI Speech-to-Text and Text-to-Speech Accessibility Tools with Python]]></title>
        <id>68b5f910f596271023ce3698</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-accessibility-tools-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-09-01T19:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Classrooms today are more diverse than ever before. Among the students are neurodiverse learners with different learning needs. While these learners bring unique strengths, traditional teaching methods don’t always meet their needs. This is where AI-...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OMOTAYO OMOYEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Read and Write Deeply Partitioned Files Using Apache Spark]]></title>
        <id>68b4bd4bbcba09cb447c5a9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-read-and-write-deeply-partitioned-files-using-apache-spark/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T21:23:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use Apache Spark to write your data pipeline, you might need to export or copy data from a source to destination while preserving the partition folders between the source and destination. When I researched online on how to do this in Spark, I ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arun Shanmugam Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Breeze Of Inspiration In September (2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-september-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Could there be a better way to welcome the new month than with a new collection of desktop wallpapers? We’ve got some eye-catching designs to make your September just a bit more colorful. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Kubernetes Pods with Traceloop: A Complete Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>68b1d0b4c2405fa2535ed0c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-kubernetes-pods-with-traceloop-a-complete-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T16:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Kubernetes pods can feel like detective work. Your app crashes, and you're left wondering what happened in those critical moments leading up to failure. Traditional kubectl commands show you logs and statuses, but they can't tell you exactl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Snake Game using Phaser.js]]></title>
        <id>68b1c9406e763941de20cda2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-snake-game-using-phaserjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:37:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to make a small game that runs in the browser, Phaser.js is a great place to start. It’s a simple JavaScript library that helps you build interactive 2-D games that you can play in the browser. In this guide, you’ll learn what P...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use AI as an accelerator, not a crutch, with freelance engineer Ankur Tyagi  [Podcast #186]]]></title>
        <id>68b1c07f6b6bda31497df196</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-ai-as-an-accelerator-not-a-crutch-with-freelance-engineer-ankur-tyagi-podcast-186/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T15:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For this week's interview, I'm talking with Ankur Tyagi. He's a software engineer who's worked at multinational companies like Volvo, Barclays, and Accenture. He grew up in Pune, India and now lives in Gothenburg, Sweden.  Ankur is a prolific contrib...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Elevator: A Pure CSS State Machine With Floor Navigation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388637</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-elevator-a-pure-css-state-machine-with-floor-navigation/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T13:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, author Chris Sabourin walk through how modern CSS features can build a fully functional, interactive elevator that knows where it is, where it’s headed, and how long it’ll take to get there. No JavaScript required.
CSS Elevator: A Pure CSS State Machine With Floor Navigation originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Sabourin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompting Is A Design Act: How To Brief, Guide And Iterate With AI]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/prompting-design-act-brief-guide-iterate-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/prompting-design-act-brief-guide-iterate-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prompting is more than giving AI some instructions. You could think of it as a design act, part creative brief and part conversation design. This second article on AI augmenting design work introduces a designerly approach to prompting: one that blends creative briefing, interaction design, and structural clarity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Lyndon Cerejo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your AI Demos with Gradio]]></title>
        <id>68afa02d9547303a1dcc65cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-ai-demos-with-gradio/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-28T00:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of artificial intelligence moves fast. Every week, new models appear, older ones get better, and the tools to use them become easier. But if you are building a machine learning project, you may face one big problem: how to share your work q...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create 3D Web Experiences with JavaScript and Three.js]]></title>
        <id>68af51354dd5e596e553184e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-3d-web-experiences-with-javascript-and-threejs/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T18:40:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you want to improve you JavaScript skills and create 3D web experiences? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is designed to help anyone master JavaScript and Three.js by building five impressive and practical proje...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Break Free from Tutorial Hell: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>68af2c4fa028696d3cf7c091</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-break-free-from-tutorial-hell/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T16:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have ever spent weeks hopping from one coding tutorial to another, only to freeze the moment you are asked to build something from scratch, you're not alone. This loop, known as tutorial hell, is where many aspiring developers get stuck. It fe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Ezeani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Caching a Next.js API using Redis and Sevalla]]></title>
        <id>68af2baaa845284174a27982</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/caching-a-nextjs-api-using-redis-and-sevalla/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T16:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you hear about Next.js, your first thought may be static websites or React-driven frontends. But that’s just part of the story. Next.js can also power full-featured backend APIs that you can host and scale just like any other backend service. In...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Handle Permissions in Flutter: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>68af2b5d6d32776366258694</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-handle-permissions-in-flutter-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T15:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Permissions are crucial when building mobile applications that require access to device features such as location, camera, contacts, microphone, storage, and more. And handling permissions effectively ensures that your app provides a seamless user ex...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Radio Button Shopping Cart Trick]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=388588</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-radio-button-shopping-cart-trick/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T14:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's an approach for animating products added to a shopping cart that handles an infinite number of items using a variation of the ol' Checkbox Hack.
A Radio Button Shopping Cart Trick originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing For TV: The Evergreen Pattern That Shapes TV Experiences]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/designing-tv-evergreen-pattern-shapes-tv-experiences/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/08/designing-tv-evergreen-pattern-shapes-tv-experiences/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TV interface design is a unique, fascinating, and often overlooked field. It’s been guided by decades of evolution and innovation, yet still firmly constrained by its legacy. Follow Milan into the history, quirks, and unshakable rules that dictate how we control these devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Milan Balać)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for the Google Professional Cloud Architect Certification Exam – And Pass!]]></title>
        <id>68ae61c1eaacec5198b5743e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-the-google-professional-cloud-architect-certification-exam-and-pass/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T01:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just released a full course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel to help you prepare for the Google Cloud Professional Cloud Architect (GCP-PCA) certification exam. The Professional Cloud Architect certification is one of Google Cloud’s top cre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Arduinos for Computer Vision]]></title>
        <id>68ae60dd2ebe767204ec0f59</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-arduinos-for-computer-vision/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-27T01:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just published a new course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that mixes computer vision, deep learning, and Arduino into some really fun projects. In this course, you’ll build two hands-on applications using MediaPipe and OpenCV. The first ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Micro Frontends in React with Vite and Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>68ae1d943a7c9745e83e7797</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-micro-frontends-in-react-with-vite-and-module-federation/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T20:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micro Frontend Architecture has become increasingly popular in recent years, as teams look to re-use parts of their existing applications in new projects rather than rebuilding everything from scratch. Micro frontends also allow large teams to share ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Machine Learning System on Serverless Architecture]]></title>
        <id>68addf802314e8b22eae4655</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-machine-learning-system-on-serverless-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-08-26T16:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you’ve built a fantastic machine learning model that performs beautifully in notebooks. But a model isn’t truly valuable until it’s in production, serving real users and solving real problems. In this article, you’ll learn how to ship a pro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuriko Iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>