<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-02-11T00:12:59.899Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organizing Design System Component Patterns With CSS Cascade Layers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384306</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/organizing-design-system-component-patterns-with-css-cascade-layers/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T14:06:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy organizing code and find cascade layers a fantastic way to organize code explicitly as the cascade looks at it. The neat part is, that as much as it helps with "top-level" organization, cascade layers can be nested, which allows us to author more precise styles based on the cascade and inheritance.
Organizing Design System Component Patterns With CSS Cascade Layers originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Trimble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Any File a Template Using This Hidden macOS Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384563</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/make-any-file-a-template-using-this-hidden-macos-tool/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stationery Pad is a handy way to nix a step in your workflow if you regularly use document templates on your Mac. The long-standing Finder feature essentially tells a file’s parent application to open a copy of it by default, ensuring that the original file remains unedited.
Make Any File a Template Using This Hidden macOS Tool originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Created A Popular WordPress Theme And Coined The Term “Hero Section” (Without Realizing It)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/popular-wordpress-theme-term-hero-section/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/popular-wordpress-theme-term-hero-section/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2013, Marcel Moerkens was working on Brooklyn, his WordPress theme, and he needed a way to make it stand out from the pack of other WordPress themes. Little did he know that the intro section he called a “Hero” would become one of the most recognizable patterns in web design today. Here’s how the idea came to life and how it changed everything.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Marcel Moerkens)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From freeCodeCamp to CTO with Robotics Engineer Peggy Wang [Podcast #159]]]></title>
        <id>67a689db1b3d34453f8da64a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-freecodecamp-to-cto-with-robotics-engineer-peggy-wang-podcast-159/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T22:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Peggy Wang. She used freeCodeCamp to learn coding. She then worked in Big Tech as a robotics engineer. And now she's cofounder and CTO of Ego AI, a Y-Combinator-backed startup that builds human-like ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Penetration Testing in Cybersecurity? A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>67a62fc9c3ae66ee9e7a4b3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/beginners-guide-to-penetration-testing-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T16:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, almost every activity we engage in is intertwined with technology. From making payments via UPI and booking movie or travel tickets online to selling products through e-commerce platforms, technology has become an integral p...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>P S Mohammed Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create an npm Library]]></title>
        <id>67a627bfaf028c3f4ba71a05</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-npm-library/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:33:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the world of JavaScript development, npm (Node Package Manager) has become an essential tool for managing dependencies and sharing reusable code. Whether you're building a simple website or a complex web application, npm libraries help streamline ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>German Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn TypeScript – A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>67a62638dd67e262dbd96da1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-typescript-with-react-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T15:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This handbook will teach you the basics of TypeScript, including what it is, why it is useful, and the key features it offers. TypeScript was created by Anders Hejlsberg, a prominent software engineer at Microsoft who’s also known for his work on C# ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oghenekparobo Stephen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking RWD To The Extreme]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/taking-rwd-to-the-extreme/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/taking-rwd-to-the-extreme/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-07T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tomasz Jakut reflects on the evolution of web design, from the days of table-based layouts and Flash games to the rise of responsive web design (RWD), which often feels like the end of history in web layout. But as 2025 marks the 15th anniversary of Ethan Marcotte’s article, it’s worth asking whether something significant happened after RWD — something so seamless that it went almost unnoticed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tomasz Jakut)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate RTK Query with Redux Toolkit: A Step-by-Step Guide for React Developers]]></title>
        <id>67a4fbc311e2c2609ca60771</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-rtk-query-with-redux-toolkit/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T18:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redux is a state management library for JavaScript applications. It lets you create applications that behave in a predictable manner and run on different environments, including server and native environments. Redux Toolkit is the recommended way to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidera Humphrey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Engineering Roadmap]]></title>
        <id>67a4da7c28544da5426abc94</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-engineering-roadmap/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is rapidly transforming industries, and AI Engineers are at the forefront of this revolution. If you’re looking to break into AI Engineering or advance your skills, having a clear roadmap is essential. Mastering AI requires a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Container query units: cqi and cqb]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384468</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/container-query-units-cqi-and-cqb/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little gem from Kevin Powell's "HTML & CSS Tip of the Week" website, reminding us that using container queries opens up container query units for sizing things based on the size of the queried container.
Container query units: cqi and cqb originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Polymorphism in Python? Explained with an Example]]></title>
        <id>67a4d16ab891dd1403996d28</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-polymorphism-in-python-example/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-06T15:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Polymorphism is an object-oriented programming (OOP) principle that helps you write high quality, flexible, maintainable, reusable, testable, and readable software. If you plan to work with object-oriented software, it is crucial to understand polymo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Clustering in Python – A Machine Learning Engineering Handbook]]></title>
        <id>67a3eddcb87640f436f52ba3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clustering-in-python-a-machine-learning-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T23:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to learn how to discover and analyze the hidden patterns within your data? Clustering, an essential technique in Unsupervised Machine Learning, holds the key to discovering valuable insights that can revolutionize your understanding of complex d...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Analytical Dashboard with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>67a3aa3efc0a24bff2e83e65</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-analytical-dashboard-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you work with data or plan to in the future, at some point you'll likely need to build a comprehensive analytics dashboard. Sharing data through charts is a great way to provide others with a clearer understanding of this information. Pairing it w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefan Muzyka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Documentation as Code with Docusaurus and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>67a39f467e716749ae8c7b7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-docs-as-code-with-docusaurus-and-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T17:26:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For technical writers, keeping documentation up to date manually can be really frustrating. Issues like outdated guides, broken links, and missing updates are a pain, and they can make writers less productive. These issues can also make it harder for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EZINNE ANNE EMILIA</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Baseline Status in a WordPress Block]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382311</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/baseline-status-in-a-wordpress-block/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T14:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The steps for how I took the Baseline Status web component and made it into a WordPress block that can be used on any page of post.
Baseline Status in a WordPress Block originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Full Stack App with Next.js and Strapi]]></title>
        <id>67a4d4fb19ce74a3822b3eab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-app-with-nextjs-and-strapi/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-05T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern, dynamic websites requires a combination of powerful front-end frameworks and flexible content management systems. Whether you're a developer looking to enhance your skills or a beginner wanting to create your first web project, learn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scalable Access Control for Your Web App: The Handbook]]></title>
        <id>67a269edea59b2f402186a7d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-scalable-access-control-for-your-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T19:26:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access control is crucial for preventing unauthorized access and ensuring that only the right people can access sensitive data in your application. As your app grows in complexity, so does the challenge of enforcing permissions in a clean and efficie...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Samhitha Rama Prasad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pioneering Next-Gen Healthcare with AI, Epigenetics, and Bioengineering]]></title>
        <id>67a25a17305bf96e1daeccd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/next-gen-healthcare-with-ai-epigenetics-and-bioengineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T18:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bioengineering stands at the precipice of a transformative era, where the convergence of biology, engineering, and technology promises to redefine the very fabric of human existence. This is not hyperbole. It’s a reflection of the rapid strides being...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Vim Text Editor – An Introduction for Developers]]></title>
        <id>67a24bb37e501febb084c852</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-vim-text-editor-intro-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T17:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a carpenter without tools, a writer without a pen, or a chef without a knife—this is like trying to imagine a developer or sysadmin without a reliable text editor. For devs, text editors are the ultimate multitools, shaping how we create, man...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanishka Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple Tips to Help You Write Clean Code]]></title>
        <id>67a2380b9af7e36332fde944</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-for-writing-clean-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T15:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a developer isn’t as straightforward as many people think. It’s not just about learning a programming language and typing out code to build software. There’s a lot more to it. And one of the most confusing (and often frustrating) topics for dev...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Sharma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a Cloud Development Environment – Harness CDE, Gitpod, and Coder Compared]]></title>
        <id>67a22fc0b7eb4acc424cb220</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-choose-a-cloud-development-environment/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T15:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Development Environments (CDEs) have become essential tools in modern software development, offering enhanced productivity and streamlined workflows. This article compares three leading CDEs: Harness CDE, Gitpod, and Coder. My goal here is to o...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrations: From Simple Data Transfer To Modern Composable Architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/integrations-from-simple-data-transfer-to-composable-architectures/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/integrations-from-simple-data-transfer-to-composable-architectures/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s web development landscape, the concept of a monolithic application has become increasingly rare. Modern applications are composed of multiple specialized services, each of which handles specific aspects of functionality. This shift didn’t happen overnight - it’s the result of decades of evolution in how we think about and implement data transfer between systems. Let’s explore this journey and see how it shapes modern architectures, particularly in the context of headless CMS solutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Edoardo Dusi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compiling CSS With Vite and Lightning CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384050</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/compiling-css-with-vite-and-lightning-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-03T15:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are partials the only thing keeping you writing CSS in Sass? With a little configuration, it's possible to compile partial CSS files without a Sass dependency. Ryan Trimble has the details.
Compiling CSS With Vite and Lightning CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Trimble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Gas Station to Google with Self-Taught Cloud Engineer Rishab Kumar [Podcast #158]]]></title>
        <id>679cf6a3c58e5553aa30c9a3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-gas-station-to-google-self-taught-cloud-engineer-rishab-kumar-podcast-158/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T16:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Rishab Kumar, cloud engineer and developer advocate at Twillio. Rishab grew up in India and moved to Canada for school. But he couldn't afford to finish. He resorted...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Async Programming in TypeScript: Promises, Async/Await, and Callbacks]]></title>
        <id>679ced2e80ebdc55d3ee44c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-async-programming-in-typescript-promises-asyncawait-and-callbacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Async programming is a programming paradigm that allows you to write code that runs asynchronously. In contrast to synchronous programming, which executes code sequentially, async programming allows code to run in the background while the rest of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Isaiah Clifford Opoku</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome 133 Goodies]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383910</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/chrome-133-goodies/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T15:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you see the release notes for Chrome 133? It's currently in beta, but the Chrome team has been publishing a slew of new articles with pretty incredible demos that are tough to ignore. I figured I'd round those up in one place.
Chrome 133 Goodies originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping the page interactive while a View Transition is running]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384331</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/keeping-the-page-interactive-while-a-view-transition-is-running/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T14:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When using View Transitions you’ll notice the page becomes unresponsive to clicks while a View Transition is running. […] This happens because of the ::view-transition pseudo element – the one that contains all animated snapshots – gets overlayed on top 
…
Keeping the page interactive while a View Transition is running originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Look Closer, Inspiration Lies Everywhere (February 2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-31T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s make the most of the shortest of all months, with a new collection of desktop wallpapers celebrating new opportunities, sweet memories, happy little moments, and everything in between. All of them created with love by the community for the community. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Langchain Alternatives You Can Use to Build AI and Agentic Workflows]]></title>
        <id>679bcc0fa60eb167ae249fba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/langchain-alternatives-for-building-ai-and-agentic-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T18:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building AI and agentic workflows is at the core of modern AI development in 2025. And LangChain has been the go-to framework for creating AI applications for a while now. But some developers are seeking alternatives that offer more flexibility, simp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Process ID? How to Use PIDs for Process Management]]></title>
        <id>679bb8262a7ebc3c99ecb6ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-process-id-process-management-tutorial/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T17:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how a computer knows which program’s output to display, especially when multiple programs are running simultaneously? This is possible because of the Process ID (PID). A PID is a unique identifier that helps the operating syste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syeda Maham Fahim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Basics of API Security]]></title>
        <id>679b945fe7604181817d149e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-basics-of-api-security/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T15:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) are the backbone of modern software applications, enabling seamless communication between different systems and services. However, this interconnectedness also makes them a prime target for cyberattacks. API ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Dependent Dropdowns in React]]></title>
        <id>679b92469bbf0da70b05703a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-dependent-dropdowns-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T14:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many web applications, we often encounter forms where selecting an option in one dropdown unlocks a new set of options in another. These interconnected dropdowns, commonly known as dependent or cascading dropdowns, play a crucial role in creating ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Timothy Olanrewaju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Mistakes of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384089</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-mistakes-of-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T14:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All of the things that the CSS Working Group would change if they had a time-traveling Delorean to go back and do things over.
The Mistakes of CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Digital Playbook: A Crucial Counterpart To Your Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/digital-playbook-crucial-counterpart-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/digital-playbook-crucial-counterpart-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design systems play a crucial role in today’s digital landscape, providing a blueprint for consistent and user-friendly interfaces. But there’s another tool that deserves equal attention: the digital playbook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Clean Code Handbook: How to Write Better Code for Agile Software Development]]></title>
        <id>679a5fa86177eb24200d0f7f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-clean-code-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T17:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building scalable software applications requires writing clean code that’s so simple that any dev can understand it. In this article, I’ll explain and demonstrate what clean code is. Then I’ll share my favorite clean code patterns for building modern...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Programming with Shahan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Great Sprint Review – Actionable Tips for Developers and Teams]]></title>
        <id>679a5f09bd88c0851092079d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-a-great-sprint-review-actionable-insights/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T17:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my twenty years of being in the Software Engineer game, I’ve been through lots of Sprint Reviews. I’ve seen them done well, and I’ve seen them used as no more than a few hours every sprint for people to take a nice break in a meeting room. When do...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Object Oriented Programming in Python]]></title>
        <id>679a52c025db32662cde422f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-object-oriented-programming-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T16:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Object-oriented programming (OOP) is one of the most essential paradigms in modern software development. It provides a structured way to design and organize code, making it more reusable, maintainable, and scalable. Unlike procedural programming, whi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What on Earth is the `types` Descriptor in View Transitions?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383818</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-on-earth-is-the-types-descriptor-in-view-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T14:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The @view-transition at-rule has two descriptions. One is the commonly used navigation descriptor. The second is types, the lesser-known of the two, and one that probably envies how much attention navigation gets. But read on to learn why we need types and how it opens up new possibilities for custom view transitions when navigating between pages.
What on Earth is the `types` Descriptor in View Transitions? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transitioning Top-Layer Entries And The Display Property In CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/transitioning-top-layer-entries-display-property-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/transitioning-top-layer-entries-display-property-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-29T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not always the big features that make our everyday lives easier; sometimes, it’s those ease-of-life features that truly enhance our projects. In this article, Brecht De Ruyte highlights two such features: `@starting-style` and `transition-behavior` — two properties that are absolutely welcome additions to your everyday work with CSS animations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Basic CI/CD Pipeline with Webhooks on Linux]]></title>
        <id>67995e567a54c877fce42276</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-basic-cicd-pipeline-with-webhooks-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T22:46:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the fast-paced world of software development, delivering high-quality applications quickly and reliably is crucial. This is where CI/CD (Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery/Deployment) comes into play. CI/CD is a set of practices and to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan P. Romano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Essential CLI/TUI Tools for Developers]]></title>
        <id>6798fd7b4666e531b7dd7586</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/essential-cli-tui-tools-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we spend a lot of time in our terminals. And there are tons of great CLI/TUI tools that can boost our productivity (as well as some that are just fun to use). From managing Git repositories and navigating file systems to monitoring sys...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Pliutau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Java Collections Framework – A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>6798fd38ac05f27ed5691abd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-collections-framework-reference-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In your Java applications, you’ll typically work with various types of objects. And you might want to perform operations like sorting, searching, and iterating on these objects. Prior to the introduction of the Collections framework in JDK 1.2, you w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anjan Baradwaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Application with AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>6798f596558861e9737fa5af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-application-with-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda is a service from Amazon Web Services (AWS) that lets you run your code in response to events without managing servers. It’s a simple and scalable way to build applications. In this tutorial, I’ll show you how to use AWS Lambda with three ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Svelte 5 And The Future Of Frameworks: A Chat With Rich Harris]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/svelte-5-future-frameworks-chat-rich-harris/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/svelte-5-future-frameworks-chat-rich-harris/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After months of anticipation, debate, and even a bit of apprehension, Svelte 5 arrived earlier this year. Frederick O’Brien caught up with its creator, Rich Harris, to talk about the path that brought him and his team here and what lies ahead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1200 Free Computer Science Courses from the World’s Top Universities]]></title>
        <id>66c376aef278f15f931a3431</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/free-courses-top-cs-universities/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ve compiled 1200+ online courses offered by the 60 best universities in the world for studying computer science in 2024. We first built the list in 2020 using a data-driven approach that we have used each year, including 2024. You...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manoel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use DeepSeek-R1]]></title>
        <id>679a50c7e6ddf5991db7aef0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-deepseek-r1/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) is rapidly evolving, and one of the latest breakthroughs is DeepSeek-R1, a model that has gotten significant attention for its innovative approach to reasoning and problem-solving. Developed by the Chinese AI startup Deep...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Semantic Book Recommender Using an LLM and Python]]></title>
        <id>679a4f5bb1375fa89b16f391</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-semantic-book-recommender-using-an-llm-and-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-28T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Finding your next favorite book can be a challenge, but what if you could build a smart system that recommends books tailored to your interests? With the power of large language models (LLMs) and Python, you can create an intelligent book recommendat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting CSS Multi-Column Layout]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384002</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/revisiting-css-multi-column-layout/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T15:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After 20 years since Andy Clarke first published his book about Multi-Column Layout in CSS, he's back to encourage a fresh look at CSS columns for enhanced readability and design flexibility.
Revisiting CSS Multi-Column Layout originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Are Scripts and How Do They Work? Improve Your Productivity with Scripting]]></title>
        <id>679798b5c4e8c2bf2c88f7bc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-are-scripts-and-how-do-they-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-27T14:31:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers who have a lot of experience building rigid, quality software tend to automate most of their work by writing scripts. These scripts range from simple alias bash commands to repetitive cron triggers that run on a server. In this tutorial, y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting a developer job in 2025 with Lane Wagner [Podcast #157]]]></title>
        <id>67943609f67368a6fc69bdb4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/getting-a-developer-job-lane-wagner-podcast-157/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-25T00:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Lane Wagner. He's a software engineer, prolific contributor to freeCodeCamp, and founder of the Boot.dev online learning platform. We talk about: Lanes thoughts on college and computer science degre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Positioning Text Around Elements With CSS Offset]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383506</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/positioning-text-around-elements-with-css-offset/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to positioning elements on a page, including text, there are many ways to go about it in CSS — the literal position property with corresponding inset-* properties, translate, margin, anchor() (limited browser support at the moment), and so forth. The offset property is another one that belongs in that list.
Positioning Text Around Elements With CSS Offset originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Collections in C# – Lists, Arrays, Dictionaries, and More]]></title>
        <id>6793a90ea69c4db6e76c194a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-collections-in-csharp/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the first challenges beginners face when developing applications in C# is organising and managing data efficiently. Imagine keeping track of a list of items, mapping unique keys to values, or ensuring there are no duplicates in a collection – ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Develop with CodeIgniter on Ubuntu – Step-by-Step Environment Setup]]></title>
        <id>6793a7b71b1cdac77474f13a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-develop-with-codeigniter-on-ubuntu-environment-setup/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CodeIgniter is a popular open-source PHP framework you can use to build dynamic and robust web applications. It’s simple to use, fast, and flexible. This makes it a good option for any developer who wants to have a light yet powerful framework that w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>valentine Gatwiri</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Containerize a Node.js Application Using Docker – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>6793a775498f1e108e0ba05d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/containerize-a-nodejs-application-using-docker/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, applications and tools have become more complex to keep up with people’s changing requirements and expectations. But this can create issues of code compatibility and remote access. For example, a codebase that functions properly on Wi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Granular Segmentation with Feature Flags]]></title>
        <id>6793a744fc2bd29e0ece1253</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-granular-segmentation-with-feature-flags/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T14:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, SaaS has become an integral part of running many businesses. So rolling out new features that resonate with the user base is key to a business’s growth. Imagine a feature that promises to enhance user experience but that ends up resonatin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Adeniyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start Learning TypeScript – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>6792ea9437616d62ca07fe03</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/start-learning-typescript-beginners-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-24T01:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is the most widely-used programming language for web development. But it lacks type-checking support, which is an essential feature of modern programming languages. JavaScript was originally designed as a simple scripting language. Its loo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Akande Olalekan Toheeb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Things You Might Not Know About Custom Counter Styles]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383776</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/some-things-you-might-not-know-about-custom-counter-styles/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T17:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was reading through Juan’s recent Almanac entry for the @counter-style at-rule and I’ll be darned if he didn’t uncover and unpack some extremely interesting things that we can do to style lists, notably the list marker. You’re probably already …
Some Things You Might Not Know About Custom Counter Styles originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Keycloak for Identity and Access Management]]></title>
        <id>67924b2d0a4e059db2a7577f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/keycloak-identity-and-access-management/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-23T13:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether your deployment requires logins from hundreds of thousands of end users or just a few remote admins, there's no escaping the need to properly control access to your infrastructure. And integrating those logins with industry-standard tools lik...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Clinton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>6791307b3bc9c704716dadd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T17:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a website might seem daunting, but WordPress makes it accessible to everyone. With WordPress, you can create a professional website tailored to your needs, whether it’s for a personal blog, a small business, or an online store. The platform’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monitor Your Kubernetes Clusters with Prometheus and Grafana on AWS]]></title>
        <id>6790382dcb2eedbe449b6899</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-cluster-observability-with-prometheus-and-grafana-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T00:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a solid application monitoring and observability strategy is a critical foundational step when deploying infrastructure or software in any environment. Monitoring ensures that your systems are running smoothly, while observability provides i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eti Ijeoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metasploit for Beginners — A Guide to the Powerful Exploitation Framework]]></title>
        <id>679037f81f50429b12d52738</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-metasploit-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re starting your journey into penetration testing, you’ve likely heard of Metasploit. Metasploit is one of the most versatile tools in cybersecurity. It helps simplify vulnerability testing and exploitation. Metasploit helps us find and fix we...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-Time Intrusion Detection System with Python and Open-Source Libraries]]></title>
        <id>678faf10f366e60cf6e7b6d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-real-time-intrusion-detection-system-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Intrusion Detection System (IDS) is like a security camera for your network. Just as security cameras help identify suspicious activities in the physical world, an IDS will monitor your network to help detect any potential cyber attacks and securi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a “Starred” Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382660</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-starred-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris wrote about “Likes” pages a long while back. The idea is rather simple: “Like” an item in your RSS reader and display it in a feed of other liked items. The little example Chris made is still really good.…
Creating a “Starred” Feed originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Discord Webhooks with Next.js 15 – Example Project]]></title>
        <id>678fa927b9b8fe257214e1be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integrate-discord-webhooks-with-nextjs-15-example-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve likely seen (or used) contact forms on websites that ask for customer feedback, potential work opportunities, customer contact info, and so on. But do you know what’s required to get all that feedback, contact info, and data sent to a private ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating The Challenges Of Modern Open-Source Authoring: Lessons Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/navigating-challenges-modern-open-source-authoring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/navigating-challenges-modern-open-source-authoring/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alvaro Saburido delves into the current state and challenges of Open-Source authoring, sharing lessons learned from both community- and company-driven initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Saburido)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for Technical Interviews Using Neetcode 150]]></title>
        <id>67912f406a65d8a9c9ef9f7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-technical-interviews-using-neetcode-150/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical interviews can be intimidating, especially when you're preparing for roles at top tech companies. To succeed, you need a solid grasp of algorithms, data structures, and problem-solving strategies. The NeetCode 150 is an invaluable resource—...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Reality VS Speculation with Google Machine Learning Engineer Jiquan Ngiam [Podcast #156]]]></title>
        <id>678ad60f07a0a18254c0d6a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-reality-vs-speculation-jiquan-ngiam-podcast-156/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T22:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jiquan Ngiam. He's a former Google Brain engineer who's building tools to make AI useful for everyone – not just developers. We talk about the power of AI and it's practical capabilities, and separat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Langbase Memory Agents to Make Any LLM a Conversational AI for Your Docs]]></title>
        <id>678ac8f3892c4e60d8af0e95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-langbase-memory-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T21:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s 2025, and Large Language Models (LLMs) still can’t access your private data. Ask them something personal, and they’ll either guess or give you the wrong answer. That’s the limitation—they’re trained on public information and don’t have access to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run an Effective Daily Scrum – Tips for Team Members and Managers]]></title>
        <id>678a7845720a1885d5f75ecd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-an-effective-daily-scrum/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T15:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start with a simple question: Why do we get together for a short meeting each day?  If you work on a Scrum team, you’ve probably heard of a daily scrum, sometimes called a daily stand-up. It’s one of the key events in scrum. The “daily” usually...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Menu Navigation Using Anchor Positioning]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383518</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-menu-navigation-using-anchor-positioning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T14:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anchor positioning can be great for little interactive effects — as Temani Afif shows off with this clever idea for a menu hover.
Fancy Menu Navigation Using Anchor Positioning originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Ode To Side Project Time]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/ode-to-side-project-time/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/ode-to-side-project-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A once-revered perk of some tech workplaces, the status of ‘side project time’ seems to have slipped in recent years. Frederick O’Brien believes it deserves a comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Deep Learning Research Tutorial - Theory, Code, and Math]]></title>
        <id>678921f0a510ee899ead3f7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-deep-learning-research-tutorial-theory-code-and-math/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T15:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding deep learning research can often feel like unraveling a dense and intricate puzzle. From decoding mathematical notation to navigating complex code bases, the process can be daunting, especially for newcomers. But with the right guidance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Use GitHub Actions: a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>6789193ad7f606e4fbf4d0a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-use-github-actions-step-by-step-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T14:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions are one of the most helpful features of GitHub. Actions help you automate, build, test, and deploy your app from your GitHub. They also help you perform code reviews and tests, manage branches, triage issues, and more. In simple terms,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Device AI: Building Smarter, Faster, And Private Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/on-device-ai-building-smarter-faster-private-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/on-device-ai-building-smarter-faster-private-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shouldn’t there be a way to keep your apps or project data private and improve performance by reducing server latency? This is what on-device AI is designed to solve. It handles AI processing locally, right on your device, without connecting to the internet and sending data to the cloud. In this article, Joas Pambou explains what on-device AI is, why it’s important, the tools to build this type of technology, and how it can change the way we use technology every day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Engineering Handbook – How to Start a Career and Excel as an AI Engineer]]></title>
        <id>67881bffe4f437ad54564e34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ai-engineering-handbook-how-to-start-a-career-and-excel-as-an-ai-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T20:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered who’s behind the groundbreaking technologies like ChatGPT from OpenAI, Tesla’s autonomous vehicles, or the humanoid robots redefining our perception of artificial intelligence? What does it take to be one of those innovators dr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev T</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Simplify Python Library RPM Packaging with Mock and Podman]]></title>
        <id>67880c8c282408c6e731883a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-python-library-rpm-packaging-with-mock-and-podman/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T19:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Packaging libraries and applications written in Python comes with its challenges. And while virtual environments are great for controlling and standardizing installations, there are some scenarios where using them may not be the best. For example, sa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Programmatically Highlight Text with the CSS Custom Highlight API]]></title>
        <id>6787d62041c11049156708c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-programmatically-highlight-text-with-the-css-custom-highlight-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T15:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can highlight text in the browser by clicking and dragging through the desired text. And sometimes this works fine. But there are times when you’ll want to programmatically highlight some text in an HTML document. In this article, I’ll discuss a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web-Slinger.css: Across the Swiper-Verse]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383533</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-slinger-css-across-the-swiper-verse/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T15:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Meyer with a super clever idea using scroll-driven animations as an interaction to "like" or "dislike" something.
Web-Slinger.css: Across the Swiper-Verse originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Web Scraper App with Playwright and React: A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>6787cb727ee491a35577e9d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-web-scraper-app-with-playwright-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T14:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are going to build a small web scraper app. This application will scrape data from the Airbnb website and display it in a nice grid view. We will also add a Refresh button that will be able to trigger a new scraping round and update the resu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Lisp Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>6789208ba535fc45fab6acd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-lisp-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to explore a programming language that combines elegance, flexibility, and a rich history of innovation, Lisp is a perfect choice. With over six decades of influence on computer science, Lisp has played a foundational role in sh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Social Authentication with Strapi and Nuxt.js]]></title>
        <id>6786814ce75a85acb18f1d2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-social-authentication-with-strapi-and-nuxtjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T15:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing security is a critical aspect of every development process. But it’s crucial to make your apps accessible for users signing up for the application. So, creating a seamless experience for users while they sign up and maintaining security thr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashimi0x</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Agriculture: How AI-Enhanced Farming Can Increase Crop Yields [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>67867ea8a91f104f3f20e6a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-agriculture-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is revolutionizing the agriculture industry, paving the way for a future of smarter, more efficient farming practices. Imagine a world where crops are grown with precision and care, maximizing yields like never before. With AI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways That Cloudways Makes Running This Site a Little Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382719</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-ways-that-cloudways-makes-running-this-site-a-little-easier/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T14:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
It’s probably no surprise to you that CSS-Tricks is (proudly) hosted on Cloudways, DigitalOcean’s managed hosting arm. Given both CSS-Tricks and Cloudways are part of DigitalOcean, it was just a matter of time …
A Few Ways That Cloudways Makes Running This Site a Little Easier originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role Of Illustration Style In Visual Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/role-illustration-style-visual-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/role-illustration-style-visual-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we determine the most suitable illustration style? How should illustrations complement and reflect your corporate identity? What will resonate most with your target audience? And regarding the content, what type of illustration would best enhance it, and how would it work for the age range it is primarily for? Thomas Bohm shares insightful examples and discusses the key qualities of effective illustrations, emphasizing the importance of understanding your audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are 850+ Ivy League Courses You Can Take Right Now for Free]]></title>
        <id>66d45eb473634435aafcef96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ivy-league-free-online-courses-a0d7ae675869/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Dhawal Shah The 8 Ivy League schools - Harvard, Yale, Princeton, Columbia, Cornell, Dartmouth, Brown, and the University of Pennsylvania - are among the most prestigious universities in the world. In 2025, all 8 Ivy League schools are ranked in th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Portfolio Website With HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>67859c6915988a75c229dee2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-simple-portfolio-website-with-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T23:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While browsing through some of my old projects, I stumbled upon a portfolio I worked on a while back. The funny thing? I never used it. So, I decided to give it a fresh look and thought, why not share it with you? As a developer, having a portfolio i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Relational Database Basics – Key Concepts for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>67853e7ede435f43fdeb589d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-relational-database-basics-key-concepts-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, data is everywhere, and it’s at the heart of most modern applications. Databases are the unsung heroes that keep it all organised and accessible. Many sites use databases, from social media platforms to online shopping retai...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Wait for the sibling-count() and sibling-index() Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-wait-for-the-sibling-count-and-sibling-index-functions/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I want to look into one of those cases of impatient and how the community has waited for that feature, to be specific, two upcoming functions: sibling-count() and sibling-index().
How to Wait for the sibling-count() and sibling-index() Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Mermaid JavaScript Library to Create Flowcharts]]></title>
        <id>678520dfd55476f9efb1de92</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-mermaid-javascript-library-to-create-flowcharts/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve recently searched for an online diagramming tool, you might have noticed that most of them rely on drag-and-drop functionality. While this is helpful for people who can’t code, it can be hard to maintain. It can also be a bit difficult to m...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Flowcharts and Bring Joy to your Coding]]></title>
        <id>67852099c122b063bd5743eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-flowcharts-with-mermaid/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding can be intense. Especially when you are knee-deep in debugging or trying to map complex projects. For many developers — novice and pros alike — it is not uncommon to spend hours staring at code, looking for answers that won’t come. You may hav...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>