<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-12-26T00:16:11.113Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Docker Container in AWS Lambda]]></title>
        <id>694c7990b7478745bce04604</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-a-docker-container-in-aws-lambda/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T23:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While containers are quite lightweight and provide various benefits, it can be challenging to decide how best to deploy them. There are a number of ways to deploy and run Docker containers. But some are best for orchestrating and managing containers,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Agnes Olorundare</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prepare for Technical Job Interviews –  Based on My Experience Landing a Job]]></title>
        <id>694c23da6c9dee59dd506fea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-prepare-for-technical-job-interviews-based-on-my-experience-landing-a-job/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-24T17:33:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi, I’m Ilyas. I’m a web developer, and this is my story about how I struggled with interviews for a long time and what finally helped me break through. I’ll talk about what failing basic interview questions taught me about recall, preparation, and s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilyas Seisov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas gifts for you from the freeCodeCamp community: Learn Python, SQL, Spanish, and more]]></title>
        <id>694b1ba8c5784bd06a2425d7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/christmas-gifts-freecodecamp-community-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T22:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2025 has been an amazing year for the global freeCodeCamp community. And we’re thrilled to cap it off with the launch of several Christmas Gifts for you: freeCodeCamp's Python certification freeCodeCamp's JavaScript certification (Version 10) free...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GenUI in Flutter to Build Dynamic, AI-Driven Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>694aca4b18de35b28c2daacb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-genui-in-flutter-to-build-dynamic-ai-driven-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T16:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In standard app development, the User Interface (UI) is static. You write code for a button, compile it, and it remains a button forever. GenUI flips this model on its head. With GenUI, Google’s Generative UI SDK, your application's interface becomes...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Support Agent with Vercel AI SDK]]></title>
        <id>694ac4a879c823aae0f86bc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-support-agent-with-vercel-ai-sdk/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T16:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel AI SDK is a TypeScript-first toolkit for building AI features. It streamlines text generation, embeddings, and structured outputs. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you to use the Vercel AI SDK to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2025 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=391203</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2025-edition/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T15:52:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the best job I've had in my life and it's only possible because you keep showing up each day to read, learn, share, and discuss all-things-front-end (and a little CSS, of course) with us.
Thank You (2025 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giving Users A Voice Through Virtual Personas]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/giving-users-voice-virtual-personas/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/giving-users-voice-virtual-personas/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Turn scattered user research into AI-powered personas that give anyone consolidated multi-perspective feedback from a single question.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's A1 Professional Chinese Curriculum (Beta) is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>694968e875dd1910710dddef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-a1-professional-chinese-curriculum-beta-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T15:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published the introductory chapters of our new A1 Professional Chinese Curriculum. You can now get started learning Chinese with what’s already available. Each chapter includes hundreds of interactive tasks designed to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[text-decoration-inset is Like Padding for Text Decorations]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390681</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/text-decoration-inset-is-like-padding-for-text-decorations/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T14:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The text-decoration-inset property solves a problem that we’ve had since the beginning of the web, which is that text decorations such as underlines extend beyond the first and last characters, resulting in vertical misalignment.
text-decoration-inset is Like Padding for Text Decorations originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Test and Improve AI Applications with an Evaluation Flywheel]]></title>
        <id>69491adc842069e2b48bbae7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-test-and-improve-ai-applications-with-an-evaluation-flywheel/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-22T10:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In traditional programming, developers rely on unit tests to catch mistakes in applications. But when building AI products, that safety net doesn't exist. Responses can shift with model updates, data changes, and subtle fluctuations in prompts or ret...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yemi Ojedapo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's New Relational Databases Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>694595068a4df0c53d579475</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-new-relational-databases-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T18:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new Relational Databases certification. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résumé, CV, or LinkedIn profile. Each certification is filled with h...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Firewalls Really Do and Why Every Network (Still) Needs Them]]></title>
        <id>69458cd3b6f1f6f9219e5bf5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-firewalls-really-do-and-why-every-network-still-needs-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T17:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firewalls are one of the oldest tools in network security.  Many people think they are outdated or replaced by newer tools like endpoint security or cloud security platforms, but that’s not the case. Firewalls still play a critical role in protecting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-time AI Gym Coach with Vision Agents]]></title>
        <id>69458b6967b30377c55c8aa3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-real-time-ai-gym-coach-with-vision-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T17:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computer vision is transforming how people train, from at-home workouts to smart gym mirrors. Imagine walking into your home gym, turning on your camera, and having an AI coach that sees your movements, counts your reps, and corrects your form in rea...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ekemini Samuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's B1 English for Developers Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>69458ad0ac78bce0b11301d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-b1-english-for-developers-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T17:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new B1 English for Developers certification for intermediate learners of English as a second language. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résum...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masonry Layout is Now grid-lanes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390640</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/masonry-layout-is-now-grid-lanes/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T16:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's settled! A new CSS display property keyword called grid-lanes will trigger a masonry layout mode.
Masonry Layout is Now grid-lanes originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get promoted as a dev without becoming a manager – Staff Engineer Santosh Yadav interview [Podcast #202]]]></title>
        <id>6945687d98d5297cf37169d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-promoted-as-a-dev-without-becoming-a-manager-staff-engineer-santosh-yadav-interview-podcast-202/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T15:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Quincy Larson interviews Santosh Yadav. The son of a textile worker, he grew up inner-city Mumbai and studied hard to get into university. From there he's worked as a software engineer for 16 years. Along the way, he's picked up every distincti...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Measure The Impact Of Features]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/how-measure-impact-features-tars/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/how-measure-impact-features-tars/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet TARS — a simple, repeatable, and meaningful UX metric designed specifically to track the performance of product features. Upcoming part of the Measure UX & Design Impact (use the code 🎟 IMPACT to save 20% off today).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Smart HomeKit Virtual Light in Go]]></title>
        <id>69449f453cbff85be8965f37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-smart-homekit-virtual-light-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T00:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I wanted to understand how smart home devices actually work. When you scan a QR code and a light appears in your Home app, what's really happening? When you tap "on", what bytes travel across your network? The best way I know to understand...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rez Moss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI Agent with LangChain and LangGraph: Build an Autonomous Starbucks Agent]]></title>
        <id>69449a6dcd2a4eec1f27eb1b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-starbucks-ai-agent-with-langchain/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-19T00:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in 2023, when I started using ChatGPT, it was just another chatbot that I could ask complex questions to and it would identify errors in my code snippets. Everything was fine. The application had no memory of previous states or what was said the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Djibril-M🍀</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an LSM Tree Storage Engine from Scratch – Full Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6944631e80f40a442d1799df</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-lsm-tree-storage-engine-from-scratch-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-18T20:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Databases are one of the most important parts of a software system. They allow us to store huge amounts of data in an organized way and retrieve it efficiently when we need it. In the early days, when the volume of data was relatively small, engineer...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramesh Sinha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search CSS-Tricks Raycast Extension]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=391171</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/search-css-tricks-raycast-extension/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-18T15:34:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jelte Lagendijk built a Raycast extension for searching CSS-Tricks articles where you simply type and a get a solid set of real-time results.
Search CSS-Tricks Raycast Extension originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a 2D Pixel Art Game in Unity]]></title>
        <id>694417d0824ee9f1eae819f5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-2d-pixel-art-game-in-unity/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-18T15:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build a complete 2D Pixel Art Tower Defense game in Unity from scratch! We just posted a step-by-step tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will guide you from a blank project to a fully playable game with a main menu, mu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's A1 Professional Spanish Curriculum (Beta) is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>6942e1421e5725744121909c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-a1-professional-spanish-curriculum-beta-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-17T16:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published the first three chapters of our new A1 Professional Spanish Curriculum. Each chapter includes hundreds of interactive tasks designed to help you take your first steps in learning Spanish with confidence. How...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive List of Avatars Using Modern CSS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390660</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-list-of-avatars-using-modern-css-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-17T15:21:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we follow up the work we did to create responsive rows of circular images in a previous article by arranging the images around a circle with a clean hover effect.
Responsive List of Avatars Using Modern CSS (Part 2) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Animations Part 7: Recreating Toon Text With CSS And SVG]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/smashing-animations-part-7-recreating-toon-text-css-svg/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/smashing-animations-part-7-recreating-toon-text-css-svg/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, pioneering author and web designer [Andy Clarke](https://stuffandnonsense.co.uk) shows his techniques for creating [Toon Text titles](https://stuffandnonsense.co.uk/toon-text/index.html) using modern CSS and SVG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Does an MCP Work Under the Hood? MCP Workflow Explained]]></title>
        <id>6941a65f3076ac3edd6fdaf0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-does-an-mcp-work-under-the-hood/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-16T18:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve all faced that awkward limitation with AI: it can write code or explain complex topics in seconds, but the moment you ask it to check a local file or run a quick database query, it hits a wall. It’s like having a genius assistant who is locked ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajay Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s !important #1: Advent Calendars, CSS Wrapped, Web Platform Updates, and More]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=391134</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-important-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-16T17:03:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best CSS news from around the web from the last two weeks. In this edition: advent calendars, CSS Wrapped 2025, and the latest Web Platform Updates.
What’s !important #1: Advent Calendars, CSS Wrapped, Web Platform Updates, and More originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug Kubernetes Apps When Logs Fail You – An eBPF Tracing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>694190c566a5d5cb99995f9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-kubernetes-apps-when-logs-fail-you-an-ebpf-tracing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-16T17:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say your Kubernetes pod crashes at 3am and the logs show nothing useful. By the time you SSH into the node, the container is gone, and you're left guessing what happened in those final moments. This is the reality of debugging modern applicatio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>694189cc7d760e7dd4cabc0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/supabase-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-16T16:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supabase is an open-source Backend-as-a-Service (BaaS) platform that provides developers with a powerful set of tools to build applications quickly. This comprehensive video tutorial introduces you to Supabase by building a real-world React.js Sales ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Perform Secure Hashing Using Python's hashlib Module]]></title>
        <id>69409201ee1f8b8545e218b8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-perform-secure-hashing-using-pythons-hashlib-module/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-15T22:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hashing is a fundamental technique in programming that converts data into a fixed-size string of characters. Unlike encryption, hashing is a one-way process: you can't reverse it to get the original data back. This makes hashing perfect for storing p...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toon Title Text Generator]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=391095</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/toon-title-text-generator/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-15T17:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andy Clarke with a brand-new resource. It generates the sort of fun typography that Andy commonly uses in his own work that's geared towards cartoon headings.
Toon Title Text Generator originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Responsive List of Avatars Using Modern CSS (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390560</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/responsive-list-of-avatars-using-modern-css-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-15T16:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A list of rounded images that slightly overlap each other is a classic web design pattern. The main idea is not complex, but the new thing is the responsive part. that dynamically adjusts the overlap between the images so they fit inside the container.
Responsive List of Avatars Using Modern CSS (Part 1) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's New Python Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>6940200b3e9f58ff90228d6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-new-python-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-15T14:49:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new Python certification. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résumé, CV, or LinkedIn profile. Each certification is filled with hundreds of hou...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Use Git and GitHub – A Beginner-Friendly Handbook]]></title>
        <id>693c859b176ed5964e28b921</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-how-to-use-git-and-github-a-beginner-friendly-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-12T21:14:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, you’re going to dive into something really exciting: Git and GitHub. To start, let’s clear one thing up: Git and GitHub are not the same thing. In short, Git is the tool that runs on your own computer and keeps track of changes in y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumit Saha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Optimistic UI Pattern with the useOptimistic() Hook in React]]></title>
        <id>693c5d28a2bfa1537f407a65</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-optimistic-ui-pattern-with-the-useoptimistic-hook-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-12T18:21:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever clicked a Like icon on a social media app and noticed the count jumps instantly? The colour of the icon changes at the same time, even before the server finishes the action. Now imagine you hit the same Like button, but it takes its swe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The "AI is going to replace devs" hype is over – 22-year developer veteran Jason Lengstorf [Podcast #201]]]></title>
        <id>693c2e0a16d9b095b8e7825d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ai-is-going-to-replace-devs-hype-is-over-22-year-developer-veteran-jason-lengstorf-podcast-201/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-12T15:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Quincy Larson interviews Jason Lengstorf. He's a college dropout who taught himself programming while building websites for his emo band. 22 years later he's worked as a developer at IBM, Netlify, run his own dev consultancy, and he now runs Co...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Else Could Container Queries… Query?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390654</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-else-could-container-queries-query/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-12T14:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How far can we really go with container queries? There are dozens of media queries now, so what if there were dozens of container queries as well? What could we use them for?
What Else Could Container Queries… Query? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn n8n to Design, Develop, and Deploy Production-Grade AI Agents]]></title>
        <id>693b0c06b189322615083d9f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-n8n-to-design-develop-and-deploy-production-grade-ai-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-11T18:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[n8n is an open-source, visual workflow automation tool that lets you connect applications, APIs, and AI models to build complex, intelligent automations. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will be your guide to maste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with YAML in Python – A Guide with Examples]]></title>
        <id>6939fb2773d2f31ad28cfef5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-yaml-in-python-a-guide-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T22:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've ever worked with configuration files, Docker Compose, Kubernetes, or CI/CD pipelines, you've probably used YAML. It's everywhere in modern development, and for good reason: it’s human-readable, simple, and powerful. In this guide, you'll le...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Polars Library in Python for Data Analysis]]></title>
        <id>6939b88a5a4b3354fde8c07b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-polars-library-in-python-for-data-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T18:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I’ll give you a beginner-friendly introduction to the Polars library in Python. Polars is an open-source library, originally written in Rust, which makes data wrangling easier in Python. The syntax of Polars is very similar to Pandas...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sara Jadhav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[React’s Critical "React2Shell" Vulnerability — What You Should Know, and How to Upgrade Your App]]></title>
        <id>6939b6ee10076c81dd6c3f49</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/reacts-critical-react2shell-vulnerability-what-you-should-know-and-how-to-upgrade-your-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T18:07:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web development is always evolving, and sometimes those changes happen a bit under the hood. One such change involved the shift to React Server Components (RSC). If you’re a NextJS or React developer, especially using the App Router, understanding th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arunachalam B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's A2 English for Developers Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>6939973f5518db00ad552055</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-a2-english-for-developers-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T15:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new A2 English for Developers certification. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résumé, CV, or LinkedIn profile. How Does the A2 English for D...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nielda Karla</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building NMT from Scratch – PyTorch Replications of 7 Landmark Papers]]></title>
        <id>6939907d149667a2e0b357dd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/building-nmt-from-scratch-pytorch-replications-of-7-landmark-papers/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T15:23:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the complete neural machine translation journey. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is a comprehensive journey through the evolution of sequence models and neural machine translation (NMT). It blends hist...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build AI Agents with Langbase]]></title>
        <id>69398d140eb4fb84a7ed1561</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-ai-agents-with-langbase/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T15:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to build AI agents with Langbase. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to create context-engineered agents that use memory and AI primitives to take action and deliver accurate, production-read...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Scroll-Based Animations in Full view()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390516</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-scroll-based-animations-in-full-view/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T15:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not that hard to do! Preethi shows you how it's really the same old animation you’re used to writing in CSS, only applied on a view timeline instead of a normal timeline.
Creating Scroll-Based Animations in Full view() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Latency in Your Generative AI Apps with Gemini and Cloud Run]]></title>
        <id>69398520ef68a953062588d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-latency-in-your-generative-ai-apps-with-gemini-and-cloud-run/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-10T14:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've built your first Generative AI feature. Now what? When deploying AI, the challenge is no longer if the model can answer, but how fast it can answer for a user halfway across the globe. Low latency is not a luxury, it's a requirement for good u...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amina Lawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible UX Research, eBook Now Available For Download]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/accessible-ux-research-ebook-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/accessible-ux-research-ebook-release/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eBook versions of “Accessible UX Research,” a new Smashing Book by Michele A. Williams, are now available for download! Which means soon the book will go to the printer. Order the eBook for instant download now or reserve your print copy at the presale price.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ari Stiles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Wrapped 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390785</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-wrapped-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T15:52:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chrome Dev Team recaps the new CSS features that shipped in Google Chrome this past year in one amazingly designed webpage. They cover new functionality for creating more customizable components, next-gen interactions, and optimizing ergonomics.
We’ve …
CSS Wrapped 2025 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Trimble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fit width text in 1 line of CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390777</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fit-width-text-in-1-line-of-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T15:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chrome team recently prototyped a working solution for fitting text to the width of a container in CSS using a text-grow property.
Fit width text in 1 line of CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State, Logic, And Native Power: CSS Wrapped 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/state-logic-native-power-css-wrapped-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/state-logic-native-power-css-wrapped-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Wrapped 2025 is out! We’re entering a world where CSS can increasingly handle logic, state, and complex interactions once reserved for JavaScript. Here is an unpacking of the standout highlights and how they connect to the bigger evolution of modern CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Brecht De Ruyte)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Production-Grade Generative AI Applications]]></title>
        <id>693775071df2bd7125d8e5f3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-production-grade-generative-ai-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T01:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI applications are everywhere today, from chatbots to code assistants to knowledge tools. With so many frameworks and models available, getting started seems pretty easy. But taking an LLM prototype and turning it into a reliable, scalabl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wisamul Haque</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Cloud Security Fundamentals in AWS – A Guide for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>69377429f6e4912378332463</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-cloud-security-fundamentals-in-aws-a-guide-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-09T00:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security is a vital part of every system and infrastructure. The word "security" comes from the Latin securitas, which is composed of se- (meaning “without”) and cura (meaning “care” or “worry”). Originally, it meant "without worry." Over time, it ha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Embedded Analytics Makes Your App More Valuable]]></title>
        <id>693704c4f37606a62f1727d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-embedded-analytics-makes-your-app-more-valuable/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-08T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most business apps capture data. They track orders, tickets, leads, expenses, tasks, or deliveries. But when someone needs insights, they often leave the app, export a file or open a BI tool to get answers. This extra step slows down decisions and cr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Figma MCP vs Kombai: Cloning the Front End from Figma with AI Tools]]></title>
        <id>693703cb19e18638588e6285</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/figma-mcp-vs-kombai-frontend-clone-comparison/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-08T16:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Frontend automation is moving fast. Tools like Figma MCP and Kombai can read design context and generate working UI code. I wanted to see what you actually get in practice, so I decided to compare them. Figma MCP exposes design metadata to AI clients...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shrijal Acharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's New JavaScript Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>6936e6e9ba6866f4046b4f36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-new-javascript-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-08T14:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new JavaScript certification. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résumé, CV, or LinkedIn profile. Each certification is filled with hundreds of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[That Time I Tried Explaining HTML and CSS to My 5-Year Old Niece]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390475</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/that-time-i-tried-explaining-html-and-css-to-my-5-year-old-niece/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-08T14:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would like to tell you what I learned from a five-year old child about HTML and CSS. It’s funny how explaining something you do almost naturally teaches you about yourself and what you take for granted.
That Time I Tried Explaining HTML and CSS to My 5-Year Old Niece originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevine Nzapdi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How UX Professionals Can Lead AI Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/how-ux-professionals-can-lead-ai-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/how-ux-professionals-can-lead-ai-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-08T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lead your organization’s AI strategy before someone else defines it for you. A practical framework for UX professionals to shape AI implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Web Components Proposal From 1998]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390691</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/html-web-components-proposal-from-1998/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-05T18:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's easy to think of HTML Web Components as a recent feature, but it has roots that go all the way back to 1998.
HTML Web Components Proposal From 1998 originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build No-Code AI Workflows Using Activepieces]]></title>
        <id>6932fc1b589bda49dd014db7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-no-code-ai-workflows-using-activepieces/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-05T15:36:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is now part of daily work for many teams. People use it to write content, analyse data, answer support requests, and guide business decisions. But building AI workflows is still hard for many users. Most tools need code, a com...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build your own learning path using Open Source with Kunal Kushwaha [Podcast #200]]]></title>
        <id>6932f37cc34687e487990bf9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-learning-path-using-open-source-with-kunal-kushwaha-podcast-200/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-05T15:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Quincy Larson interviews Kunal Kushwaha. He's a software engineer and prolific computer science teacher on YouTube. He failed the JEE, the Indian Engineering Entrance Exam, TWICE. But he persevered. He did 4 years of university but attended ZER...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond The Black Box: Practical XAI For UX Practitioners]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/beyond-black-box-practical-xai-ux-practitioners/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/beyond-black-box-practical-xai-ux-practitioners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explainable AI isn’t just a challenge for data scientists. It’s also a design challenge and a core pillar of trustworthy, effective AI products. Victor Yocco offers practical guidance and design patterns for building explainability into real products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git & GitHub Crash Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6931ef1a5feb2860f3beafd6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-and-github-crash-course-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-04T20:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is important for any developer. We just posted a course that will help you learn Git and GitHub from scratch with clear examples, real workflows, branching, merging, stashing, rebase, pull requests, and more. This course is great for beginners wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Become an AI Researcher]]></title>
        <id>6931ed67859ffe0c32f1133b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/become-an-ai-researcher/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-04T20:21:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to become an AI Researcher. This course will guide you step-by-step, starting with the foundational mathematics essential for understanding modern AI, before divi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an Admin Dashboard with shadcn/ui and TanStack Start]]></title>
        <id>6931bd617fcd342128f08ed6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-admin-dashboard-with-shadcnui-and-tanstack-start/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-04T16:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, we’ll build a feature-rich admin dashboard using shadcn/ui for beautiful, reusable components and TanStack Start for a powerful, type-safe full-stack framework. By the end, you’ll have: A fully functional /dashboard layout A statisti...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajay Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Creative With “The Measure”]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390477</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-creative-with-the-measure/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-04T14:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A good measure makes reading text comfortable, while a bad one makes it more difficult. So, rather than allowing layout to dictate the measure, doesn’t it make more sense for the measure to inform layout decisions?
Getting Creative With “The Measure” originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-Powered RAG Chatbot with Amazon Lex, Bedrock, and S3]]></title>
        <id>6930baf2becf9d70ca80fcd0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-ai-powered-rag-chatbot/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-03T22:34:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chatbots are widely adopted among software companies, especially those that interact heavily with customers. It is typically used for tasks such as customer support, answering questions, and providing information on websites, apps, and messaging plat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chisom Uma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up CUDA and WSL2 for Windows 11 (including PyTorch and TensorFlow GPU)]]></title>
        <id>69309b9e8c594b8177306456</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-cuda-and-wsl2-for-windows-11-including-pytorch-and-tensorflow-gpu/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-03T20:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re working on complex Machine Learning projects, you’ll need a good Graphics Processing Unit (or GPU) to power everything. And Nvidia is a popular option these days, as it has great compatibility and widespread support. If you’re new to Machin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bluetooth Low Energy Devices Work: GATT Services and Characteristics Explained]]></title>
        <id>69307a1e2b79515d02383320</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-bluetooth-low-energy-devices-work-gatt-services-and-characteristics-explained/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-03T17:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every time you check your smartwatch for heart rate, read the battery level of wireless earbuds, unlock a Bluetooth smart lock, or watch sensor data stream into an app, you are experiencing the result of GATT working quietly in the background. GATT i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First MCP Server using FastMCP]]></title>
        <id>693070aab61ab28f12ea4687</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-first-mcp-server-using-fastmcp/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-03T17:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Model Context Protocol, or MCP, is changing how large language models connect with data and tools.  Instead of treating an AI model as a black box, MCP gives it structured access to information and actions.  It is like the USB-C port for AI, creating...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn NestJS for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>692f67007fa18557e4b8ce73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-nestjs-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-02T22:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NestJS is a progressive Node.js framework for building efficient and reliable server-side applications. It uses TypeScript by default and encourages clean, modular code with concepts including controllers, services, and dependency injection. We just ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn R Programming from Harvard University]]></title>
        <id>692f65b7eaee334f9337fc73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-r-programming-from-harvard-university/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-02T22:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard University creates amazing beginner computer science courses. We just released Harvard CS50’s introduction to programming using a language called R, a popular language for statistical computing and graphics in data science and other domains. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scrollytelling on Steroids With Scroll-State Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390205</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/scrollytelling-on-steroids-with-scroll-state-queries/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-02T16:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unconvinced of the value of scrollytelling? Alright, skeptic, let’s first warm up with some common use cases for scroll-based styling.
Scrollytelling on Steroids With Scroll-State Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp's New Responsive Web Design Certification is Now Live]]></title>
        <id>692f044a17ed56d5a1781fb1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamps-new-responsive-web-design-certification-is-now-live/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-02T15:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The freeCodeCamp community just published our new Responsive Web Design certification. You can now sit for the exam to earn the free verified certification, which you can add to your résumé, CV, or LinkedIn profile. Each certification is filled with ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Masonry: Things You Won’t Need A Library For Anymore]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/masonry-things-you-wont-need-library-anymore/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/12/masonry-things-you-wont-need-library-anymore/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Masonry is almost here! Patrick Brosset takes a deep dive into what this long-awaited feature means for web developers and how you could make use of it in your own work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevent a page from scrolling while a dialog is open]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390613</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/prevent-a-page-from-scrolling-while-a-dialog-is-open/"/>
        <updated>2025-12-01T17:25:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bramus:
Chrome 144 features a small change to overscroll-behavior: it now also works on non-scrollable scroll containers. While this change might seem trivial, it fixes an issue developers have been dealing with for ages: prevent a page from 
…
Prevent a page from scrolling while a dialog is open originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sparkle Of December Magic (2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-december-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-30T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With December just around the corner, how about some new desktop wallpapers to welcome the last month of the year — and the holiday season, if you’re celebrating? Our latest edition of monthly wallpapers has got you covered. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tips from a Serial Career Changer with GitHub's Andrea Griffiths [Podcast #199]]]></title>
        <id>6929b680d93baaf4c44b19fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/tips-from-serial-career-changer-github-andrea-griffiths-podcast-199/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-28T14:49:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Quincy Larson interviews Andrea Griffiths, who taught herself programming using freeCodeCamp while working in construction. She moved to the US from Colombia when she was 17, and within 6 months she joined the US Army. She ran a chain of gyms b...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Accessibility Problem With Authentication Methods Like CAPTCHA]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/accessibility-problem-authentication-methods-captcha/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/accessibility-problem-authentication-methods-captcha/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CAPTCHAs were meant to keep bots out, but too often, they lock people with disabilities out, too. From image classification to click-based tests, many “human checks” are anything but inclusive. There’s no universal solution, but understanding real user needs is where accessibility truly starts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eleanor Hecks)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-Driven Search Experience using Meilisearch]]></title>
        <id>692782273df4e33b78a46d72</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-ai-driven-search-experience-using-meilisearch/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-26T22:41:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Search is one of the most important features in modern applications. Users expect instant answers, useful suggestions, and results that match their intent even when they make spelling mistakes.  Most traditional search systems struggle to deliver thi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Theming and Customization in Flutter: A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>6927302dc91eac2c85873f95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/theming-and-customization-in-flutter-a-handbook-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-26T16:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design is not just about how something looks. In product engineering, design shapes how an experience feels, how users interact with it, and how consistently the brand comes alive across every screen. Flutter provides powerful tools for this, but tru...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>