<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-03-19T00:14:07.154Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Web Acessibility]]></title>
        <id>67d9aa58a50edbbdc70e2941</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-web-accessibility-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is a great place to access information and connect with people. It has opened up countless opportunities, making life more convenient in many ways. But not everyone experiences the web in the same way. Websites are difficult to use for people...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Alert Provisioning with the SigNoz Terraform Provider]]></title>
        <id>67d87353b13a6fd9fb559ada</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-alert-provisioning-with-the-signoz-terraform-provider/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T19:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern infrastructure requires continuous monitoring and rapid incident response. However, manually configuring and managing alerts is not only labor-intensive but also susceptible to human error. Automating alert provisioning allows you to enforce c...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug and Prevent Buffer Overflows in Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>67d84f228d156200bc7d3d8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-and-prevent-buffer-overflows-in-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T16:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buffer overflows are one of the most serious software bugs, especially in embedded systems, where hardware limitations and real-time execution make them hard to detect and fix. A buffer overflow happens when a program writes more data into a buffer t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham Banerjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling Counters in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384529</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/styling-counters-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T16:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going from the most basic ways to style lists directly in HTML to advanced customization techniques that are even capable of making things that aren't lists look like lists.
Styling Counters in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping With RSelenium (Chrome Driver) and Rvest]]></title>
        <id>67d8272af45871e3e821d5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-rselenium-chrome-driver-and-rvest/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T13:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you automatically extract data from websites, so you can store it in a structured format for later use. In this article, you'll explore how to use popular R libraries for web scraping to extract data from a website. The target websi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elabonga Atuo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Components Vs. Framework Components: What’s The Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/web-components-vs-framework-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/web-components-vs-framework-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some critics question the agnostic nature of Web Components, with some even arguing that they are not real components. Gabriel Shoyomboa explores this topic in-depth, comparing Web Components and framework components, highlighting their strengths and trade-offs, and evaluating their performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a self-taught developer while supporting a family [Podcast #164]]]></title>
        <id>67d4a92df560badb8e1f0360</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-self-taught-developer-while-supporting-a-family-podcast-164/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T22:09:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jesse Hall. He's software engineer and a developer advocate at MongoDB. He taught himself to code while raising kids and working on the Best Buy Geek Squad fixing computers. Jesse has created tons of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect, Read, and Process Sensor Data on Microcontrollers – A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>67d45997c9e7f2d42bb1c540</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/connect-read-process-sensor-data-on-microcontrollers-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T16:30:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world, computers are ubiquitous and generally serve two primary purposes. The first is general-purpose computing, where they handle a wide range of tasks, including running diverse applications and programs. Examples include laptops, deskt...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham Banerjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Components Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383422</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-components-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T12:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Jehl released a course called Web Components Demystified. This is my full set of notes from Scott's course. You'll still want to take the course on your own, and I encourage you to because Scott is an excellent teacher who makes all of this stuff extremely accessible, even to noobs like me.
Web Components Demystified originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn AWS Incognito for Authentication]]></title>
        <id>67d38995d1f16f987c9eb503</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-aws-incognito-for-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-14T01:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you're building a web app, mobile app, or API, understanding how to implement robust authentication and authorization is a critical skill. AWS Cognito is a powerful ability that simplifies user management, authentication, and access control, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Exploit the EternalBlue Vulnerability on Windows – A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>67d35b3cba576fa68285a197</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-exploit-the-eternalblue-vulnerability-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T22:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve followed cybersecurity news over the past few years, you’ve likely come across EternalBlue. This critical Windows exploit played a key role in the widespread WannaCry ransomware attack that affected systems in over 150 countries. In this ar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Synchronization for Edge Computing with SymmetricDS]]></title>
        <id>67d2cc837d28795ed4ea4d3e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-synchronization-for-edge-computing/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T12:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Edge computing is a distributed system design that moves computation and data storage to where it’s most required – at the ‘edge’ of the network. Moving these tasks to the edge of the network enables computing in real time, which reduces the cost of ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Divya Valsala Saratchandran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Prevent WordPress SQL Injection Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-prevent-wordpress-sql-injection-attacks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-prevent-wordpress-sql-injection-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you thought about the security risks WordPress websites face? Anders Johansson explores why they are frequent hacker targets and shares how WordPress SQL injection attacks work and how to remove and prevent them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anders Johansson)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Essentials]]></title>
        <id>67d23a5a68fbee7d6b2ec767</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-essentials/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-13T01:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is the backbone of modern web development, powering everything from interactive websites to complex web applications. Object-oriented programming (OOP), prototypical inheritance, ES6 classes, Node.js, and asynchronous programming are all k...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Full-Stack Developer in 2025 (and Get a Job) – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>67d1f8cced96446e8fad7db9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/become-a-full-stack-developer-and-get-a-job/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T21:12:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whenever I publish a new article, I receive countless emails and DMs across social media asking, "How can I become a Full Stack Developer like you? How much DSA do I need to know? How long does it take?" Well, I always say, "Wait for my next tutorial...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prankur Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run a Sprint Retrospective Using the Start, Stop, Continue Method]]></title>
        <id>67d1f7a9ed7b17e04fb90aa7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-a-sprint-retrospective-start-stop-continue-method/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-12T21:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been writing a lot of articles lately on Agile methodologies. And for this one, I wanted to cover how to get the most out of a Sprint Retrospective. I’ve been participating and running Sprint Retrospectives now for 15 years and I truly believe t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering Search With Astro Actions and Fuse.js]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384941</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/powering-search-with-astro-actions-and-fuse-js/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T15:26:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Astro, we can generate most of our site during our build, but have a small bit of server-side code that can handle search functionality using something like Fuse.js. In this demo, we’ll use Fuse to search through a set of personal “bookmarks” that are generated at build time, but return back proper results from a server call.
Powering Search With Astro Actions and Fuse.js originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build Confidence In Your UX Work]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-build-confidence-in-your-ux-work/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-build-confidence-in-your-ux-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-11T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UX initiatives are often seen as a disruption rather than a means to solving existing problems in an organization. In this post, we’ll explore how you can build trust for your UX work, gain support, and make a noticeable impact. Part of [Measure UX and Design Impact](https://measure-ux.com/) by yours truly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Meets Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385112</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/smashing-meets-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T15:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The videos from Smashing Magazine's recent event on accessibility were just posted the other day. I was invited to host the panel discussion with the speakers, including a couple of personal heroes of mine, Stéphanie Walter and Sarah Fossheim. But I was just as stoked to meet Kardo Ayoub who shared his deeply personal story as a designer with a major visual impairment.
Smashing Meets Accessibility originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Enforce Type Safety in FormData with TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>67cef1f13c2aba931eee9785</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enforce-type-safety-in-formdata-with-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-10T14:06:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with the FormData interface in JavaScript, where data is appended as key/value pairs, there's no built-in way to enforce type safety on the keys you append. This can lead to typos, missing keys, and unexpected runtime errors. But in Type...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olabisi Olaoye</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Software Design Basics: Key Phases and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>67cb6446f54b40e1e9144db0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-software-design-basics/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T21:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding has become one of the most common tasks in modern society. With computers now central to almost every field, more people are designing algorithms and writing code to solve various problems. From healthcare to finance, robust software systems p...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham Banerjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn fewer skills but go deeper - the Caleb Curry interview [Podcast #163]]]></title>
        <id>67cb4f49e5cd83d2948ab4fe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-fewer-skills-but-go-deeper-the-caleb-curry-interview-podcast-163/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T19:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Caleb Curry. He's a software engineer and prolific computer science educator. He recently started mentoring dozens of developers directly and helping them with their skills and careers. We talk about...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Python SIEM System Using AI and LLMs for Log Analysis and Anomaly Detection]]></title>
        <id>67cb2cab98825a8b61ca9121</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-python-siem-system-using-ai-and-llms/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T17:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we’ll build a simplified, AI-flavored SIEM log analysis system using Python. Our focus will be on log analysis and anomaly detection. We’ll walk through ingesting logs, detecting anomalies with a lightweight machine learning model, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CSS-Only Star Rating Component and More! (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384919</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-css-only-star-rating-component-and-more-part-2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-07T13:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of a two-part series, Temani Afif demonstrates an alternative approach to creating the star rating component from the first article using experimental scroll-driven animations rather than using the border-image property.
A CSS-Only Star Rating Component and More! (Part 2) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn PyTorch in Five Projects]]></title>
        <id>67c9e1b1b9163aa35c6dc2ee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-pytorch-in-five-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deep learning has revolutionized the way we approach complex problems like image recognition, natural language processing, and even audio analysis. At the core of many deep learning applications is PyTorch, a powerful and flexible framework that allo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe don’t use custom properties in shorthand properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385117</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/maybe-dont-use-custom-properties-in-shorthand-properties/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T16:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This easily qualifies as a "gotcha" in CSS and is a good reminder that the cascade doesn't know everything all at the same time. If a custom property is invalid, the cascade won't ignore it, and it gets evaluated, which invalidates the declaration.
Maybe don’t use custom properties in shorthand properties originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Largest Contentful Paint Issues With Subpart Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-fix-largest-contentful-issues-with-subpart-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-fix-largest-contentful-issues-with-subpart-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling with slow Largest Contentful Paint (LCP)? Newly introduced by Google, LCP subparts help you pinpoint where page load delays come from. Now, in the Chrome UX Report, this data provides real visitor insights to speed up your site and boost rankings. Matt Zeunert unpacks what LCP subparts are, what they mean for your website speed, and how you can measure them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Zeunert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Fix Largest Contentful Issues With Subpart Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-fix-largest-contentful-issues-subpart-analysis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-fix-largest-contentful-issues-subpart-analysis/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Struggling with slow Largest Contentful Paint (LCP)? Newly introduced by Google, LCP subparts help you pinpoint where page load delays come from. Now, in the Chrome UX Report, this data provides real visitor insights to speed up your site and boost rankings. Matt Zeunert unpacks what LCP subparts are, what they mean for your website speed, and how you can measure them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Zeunert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Machine Learning Concepts plus Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>67c90b95f53d5f98abdef4ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-machine-learning-concepts-plus-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T02:42:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Machine learning is revolutionizing industries by enabling computers to learn from data, recognize patterns, and make decisions without explicit programming. If you've ever been curious about how AI systems work, this course provides a structured int...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a simple MMO Game in Unity]]></title>
        <id>67c90a7950860cc5f8cd4d06</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-simple-mmo-game-in-unity/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-06T02:37:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an MMO (Massively Multiplayer Online) game may seem like a daunting task, but with the right tools and guidance, you can bring your game idea to life. Whether you're an aspiring game developer or just curious about how online multiplayer gam...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grouping Selection List Items Together With CSS Grid]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384971</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/grouping-selection-list-items-together-with-css-grid/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-05T13:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Preethi demonstrates how to make a user interface to group selected items using CSS Grid using two different methods: the auto-fill keyword for stable layouts and the span keyword for flexible arrangements.
Grouping Selection List Items Together With CSS Grid originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a MERN Stack To-Do App]]></title>
        <id>67c74d6473daa61c95803cfc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-mern-stack-to-do-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-04T18:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will walk you through building a full-stack MERN To-Do application. It covers setting up the environment, writing code to demonstrate core CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) operations, and connecting the application to MongoDB Atlas, a f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Social Learning Platform using Next.js, Stream, and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>67c5c657e04393229206983b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-social-learning-platform-using-nextjs-stream-and-supabase/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T15:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media and real-time communication have transformed how people interact, making it easier to share ideas, collaborate, and learn from others, regardless of location. From professional networks to online study groups, these platforms allow vario...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Asaolu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functions in CSS?!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384685</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/functions-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T13:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arguments?! Return values?! What's crazier, you can use functions right now in Chrome Canary! So, after reading and playing around, here are my key insights on what you need to know about CSS Functions.
Functions in CSS?! originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case For Minimal WordPress Setups: A Contrarian View On Theme Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/case-minimal-wordpress-setups-contrarian-view-theme-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/case-minimal-wordpress-setups-contrarian-view-theme-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-03T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern frameworks are supposed to help speed up development while providing modern tools and a developer-friendly workflow. In reality, Kevin Leary has found that they cause far more problems than they solve. This ultimately leads to the big question: why are modern theme frameworks so popular, and do they really benefit developers in the long run?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kevin Leary)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Git through Gamification – A Visual Guide to Key Version Control Concepts]]></title>
        <id>67c1cfa78df3594301bc3fef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-git-through-gamification/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-02T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git has many concepts and commands that you’ll need to understand before you feel confident using it. Some of these concepts may sound trivial, especially to someone who has worked with Git before. But like most Git and coding concepts, even the “sim...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Stopak</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Zod for React API Validation]]></title>
        <id>67c1f994107ebba152ad9e79</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-zod-for-react-api-validation/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T17:59:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In React applications, handling API (Application Programming Interface) responses can be challenging. You might encounter data that’s missing crucial fields, that’s formatted unexpectedly, or that simply doesn’t match what you anticipated. This incon...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emore Ogheneyoma Lawrence</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to become a developer in your 30s with Anjana Vakil [Podcast #162]]]></title>
        <id>67c1e77814978ff66bb8a865</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-developer-in-your-30s-anjana-vakil-podcast-162/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T16:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Anjana Vakil. She left academia to learn to code and got her first developer job in her 30s. Anjana was an English teacher who studied computational linguistics, and found building software to be mor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CSS-Only Star Rating Component and More! (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384906</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-css-only-star-rating-component-and-more-part-1/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T14:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you'll learn how to make a full-on star rating component out of nothing but a single input element and vanilla CSS.
A CSS-Only Star Rating Component and More! (Part 1) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sunshine And March Vibes (2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-28T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by the community for the community, the wallpapers in this collection are the perfect opportunity to get your desktop ready for spring — and, who knows, maybe they’ll spark some new ideas, too. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Linear Algebra for Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>67c07627b9cb8c91fbfe2e7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-linear-algebra-for-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-27T14:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linear algebra is a fundamental building block of machine learning. Whether you are working with deep learning models, optimization algorithms, or computer vision applications, understanding linear algebra concepts can give you a solid mathematical f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build an AI Chat Application with the MERN Stack]]></title>
        <id>67bf99792e5bf2f98ee2466d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-chat-application-with-the-mern-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T22:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered chat applications are becoming an essential part of modern web development, enabling users to interact with intelligent conversational agents. Whether for customer support, virtual assistants, or educational tools, building your own AI cha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Vision Transformer from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>67bf961287f2aad5763d1f78</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-vision-transformer-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T22:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transformers have revolutionized natural language processing, and now they are transforming computer vision as well. Vision Transformers (ViTs) apply the power of self-attention to image processing, offering state-of-the-art performance in tasks like...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Crossy Road Game Clone with React Three Fiber]]></title>
        <id>67bf859b948d001fe6c9ab99</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-crossy-road-game-clone-with-react-three-fiber/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T21:20:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you’ll learn how to create a clone of the mobile game Crossy Road with React Three Fiber. In a previous tutorial, I taught you how to build this game using Three.js and vanilla JavaScript. And here, you’ll learn how to make the same...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using & Styling the Details Element]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383813</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-styling-the-details-element/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T16:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we're 5+ years into 
, we know more about it than ever before. I thought I'd round that information up so it's in one place I can reference in the future without having to search the site — and other sites — to find it.
Using & Styling the Details Element originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If-Else vs Switch Case in JavaScript – Which One is Better?]]></title>
        <id>67bf38654fdd15eb4db76755</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/if-else-vs-switch-case-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T15:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript has been a popular programming language for almost 30 years now. Whether you’re using it for web applications, mobile applications, backend services, or even desktop applications, you’ll find that JavaScript has deep roots. Many of the lib...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Human Element: Using Research And Psychology To Elevate Data Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/human-element-using-research-psychology-elevate-data-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/human-element-using-research-psychology-elevate-data-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-26T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Effective data storytelling isn’t a black box. By integrating UX research & psychology, you can craft more impactful and persuasive narratives. Victor Yocco and Angelica Lo Duca outline a five-step framework that provides a roadmap for creating data stories that resonate with audiences on both a cognitive and emotional level.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Yocco &amp; Angelica Lo Duca)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Reusable useSearch Hook in React]]></title>
        <id>67be32ff803613c5edf10387</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-reusable-usesearch-hook-in-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-25T21:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I needed to add a search feature to a React app. Naturally, I did what many developers would do—I turned to Google for help. The first article I found was about building a search and filter component in React. As I read through it, I couldn...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the Cold Start Problem in Recommender Systems?]]></title>
        <id>67be316dd9d7f9374abc151b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cold-start-problem-in-recommender-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-25T21:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recommender systems are used to provide personalized experiences for customers in many industries today, including e-commerce, social media, entertainment, and education. These recommender systems make recommendations based on user preferences and co...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Praise James</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run LaTeX Projects Locally (for Free) On Windows]]></title>
        <id>67bde54468de46f577ed25f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-latex-projects-locally-for-free-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-25T15:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LaTeX is a high-quality typesetting system that is widely used in technical, academic, and scientific writing. It’s very popular in academia, especially in fields like mathematics, physics, computer science, and engineering. LaTeX is not a word proce...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Speed Up Website Loading by Removing Extra Bits and Bytes]]></title>
        <id>67bca6f616cf4617f656a33f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/speed-up-website-loading/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T17:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start with an interesting fact: according to research done by Akamai, a 1-second delay in loading a website’s page can decrease the conversion rate by 7%. We are currently living in a fast-paced world, where time is money for everyone. People e...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying the Web Dev Mindset to Dealing With Life Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384565</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/applying-the-web-dev-mindset-to-dealing-with-life-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-24T13:42:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The grain of truth was that even if you love your job, it can’t love you back. Yet what I’m hooked on isn’t one job, but the power of code and language.
Applying the Web Dev Mindset to Dealing With Life Challenges originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to go full-on Renaissance Man mode in 2025 with Vaughn Gene [Podcast #161]]]></title>
        <id>67b8d14181f9a2aaa77a646f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-go-full-on-renaissance-man-mode-in-2025-with-vaughn-gene-podcast-161/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T19:17:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Vaughn Gene. He's a self-taught software engineer who works with lots of freelance clients. Vaughn lived in Japan for 10 years, and speaks Japanese, speaks Spanish, plays guitar, plays piano, and is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toe Dipping Into View Transitions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384665</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/toe-dipping-into-view-transitions/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-21T14:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The View Transitions API is more a set of features than it is about any one particular thing. And it gets complex fast. But in this post, we’ll cover a couple ways to dip your toes into the waters without having to dive in head-first.
Toe Dipping Into View Transitions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code a Crossy Road Game Clone with Three.js]]></title>
        <id>67b7bad6bcd9ef47aba6001d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-a-crossy-road-game-clone-with-threejs/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T23:29:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, you’ll learn how to create a clone of the mobile game Crossy Road with Three.js. The goal of this game is to move a character through an endless path of static and moving obstacles. You have to go around trees and avoid getting hit ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hunor Márton Borbély</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a DeepSeek R1 API in R with Plumber]]></title>
        <id>67b7b91a534c03e678009324</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-a-deepseek-r1-api-in-r-with-plumber/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T23:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To create an AI chatbot and integrate it with another platform, you have to communicate with large language model using an API. This API receives prompts from the client and sends them to the model to generate answers. In this tutorial, you will lear...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Replit Clone with Socket.io, Monaco Editor, and Copilotkit]]></title>
        <id>67b7b7b46d2a73d146b3a978</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-replit-clone-with-socketio-monaco-editor-and-copilotkit/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T23:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been coding for about a decade now. And over the years, I’ve tried my fair share of development tools—especially IDEs like Sublime Text, Atom, and even NetBeans back in my college days. But when VS Code came along, it completely changed the game...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prankur Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Ways to Access DeepSeek Using Third-Party Apps]]></title>
        <id>67b746282e12c8160896e071</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-ways-to-access-deepseek-using-third-party-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered coding assistants have changed the way developers write software. They help automate repetitive tasks, catch errors early, and speed up development. But not all AI coding tools are built with security in mind. One of the most promising fre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Ways to Access DeepSeek( Third-Party Apps)]]></title>
        <id>67b746282e12c8160896e071</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/secure-ways-to-access-deepseek-third-party-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI-powered coding assistants have changed the way developers write software. They help automate repetitive tasks, catch errors early, and speed up development. But not all AI coding tools are built with security in mind. One of the most promising fre...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwadamisi Samuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Kubernetes and EKS for Deployment]]></title>
        <id>67b743e1674d20deafd5b082</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-kubernetes-and-eks-for-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-20T15:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the de facto standard for container orchestration, allowing developers to efficiently deploy, manage, and scale applications. But deploying Kubernetes clusters in the cloud can be complex. That’s where Amazon Elastic Kubernetes ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an ASP.NET Core MVC Web App]]></title>
        <id>67b626105b8a70c6cf85c5be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-an-aspnet-core-mvc-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T18:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building modern web applications requires a solid understanding of both frontend and backend development. ASP.NET Core MVC is a powerful framework for creating full-stack web applications with clean architecture and maintainable code. Whether you're ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Working With Multiple CSS Anchors and Popovers Inside the WordPress Loop]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382234</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/working-with-multiple-css-anchors-and-popovers-inside-the-wordpress-loop/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T13:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know, super niche, but it could be any loop, really. The challenge is having multiple tooltips on the same page that make use of the Popover API for toggling goodness and CSS Anchor Positioning for attaching a tooltip to its respective anchor element.
Working With Multiple CSS Anchors and Popovers Inside the WordPress Loop originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a serverless AI agent to generate cold emails for your dream job]]></title>
        <id>67b5df98970327b4e047537c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-serverless-ai-agent-for-generating-cold-emails/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T13:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cold emails can make a huge difference in your job search, but writing the perfect one takes time. You need to match your skills with the job description, find the right tone, and do it over and over again—it’s exhausting. This guide will walk you th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with OpenAPI in Go]]></title>
        <id>67b5da4da9d7e29052110938</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-openapi-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T13:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well-structured and well-documented APIs are a pleasure to work with. And nowadays the standard is OpenAPI, which comes with a good methodology for defining an API interface first, and only then constructing everything around it. This makes it easier...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Pliutau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn User Management in RHEL: A Comprehensive Guide]]></title>
        <id>67b5da0a6db178277c2bebc9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-user-management-in-rhel-a-comprehensive-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T13:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you're throwing a house party. You wouldn’t hand out keys to every guest, right? Some friends can roam freely, some should probably stick to the living room, and a few—well, let’s just say they need supervision. Managing users in RHEL is kind...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanishka Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human-Centered Design Through AI-Assisted Usability Testing: Reality Or Fiction?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/human-centered-design-ai-assisted-usability-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/human-centered-design-ai-assisted-usability-testing/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eduard Kuric discusses the significance and role of context in the creation of relevant follow-up questions for unmoderated usability testing, how an AI tasked with interactive follow-up should be validated for its capability to incorporate such context, and what the potential — along with the risks — of AI interaction in usability testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eduard Kuric)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Kubernetes Network Policy and Secure Your Cluster]]></title>
        <id>67b49d275027eb87a4a1ba21</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-kubernetes-network-policy-and-secure-your-cluster/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T14:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a Kubernetes environment, proper networking allows for seamless communication between various components within the cluster and the external environment. As your applications grow, networking becomes more and more important and helps ensure that t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eti Ijeoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Classes in JavaScript – A Handbook for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>67b47d2761b19f350f00901b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-classes-in-javascript-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T12:29:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you curious about classes in JavaScript but feel a little puzzled about how they work or why you'd even use them? If that's you, then you're definitely in the right place. Lots of developers find classes a bit tricky at first, and honestly, I was...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Shadow AI? The Hidden Risks and Challenges in Modern Organizations]]></title>
        <id>67b450b56572419f24094c04</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shadow-ai-hidden-risks-and-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T09:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine this: a marketing manager uses ChatGPT to draft a personalized email campaign. Meanwhile, a developer experiments with a machine learning model trained on customer data, and an HR team integrates an artificial intelligence (AI) tool to screen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonya Moisset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How OWASP Helps You Secure Your Full-Stack Web Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/how-owasp-helps-secure-full-stack-web-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/02/how-owasp-helps-secure-full-stack-web-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-18T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OWASP vulnerabilities list is the perfect starting point for web developers looking to strengthen their security expertise. Let’s discover how these vulnerabilities materialize in full-stack web applications and how to prevent them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Burel)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use FakeLogger to Make Testing Easier In .Net]]></title>
        <id>67b3b736d8f6ac012e312ac5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-fakelogger-to-make-testing-easier-in-net/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T22:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When writing unit tests in .NET, you may need to verify that methods are logging exceptions, errors, or other key information. You might think, No problem, I'll just mock ILogger using my favourite mocking library – for example Moq, NSubstitute, or F...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What If Machine: Bringing the “Iffy” Future of CSS into the Present]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384446</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-what-if-machine-bringing-the-iffy-future-of-css-into-the-present/"/>
        <updated>2025-02-17T14:24:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My thesis for today's article offers further reassurance that inline conditionals are probably not the harbinger of the end of civilization: I reckon we can achieve the same functionality right now with style queries, which are gaining pretty good browser support.
The What If Machine: Bringing the “Iffy” Future of CSS into the Present originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>