<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-01-23T00:12:43.727Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a WordPress Website]]></title>
        <id>6791307b3bc9c704716dadd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-wordpress-website/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T17:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a website might seem daunting, but WordPress makes it accessible to everyone. With WordPress, you can create a professional website tailored to your needs, whether it’s for a personal blog, a small business, or an online store. The platform’...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Monitor Your Kubernetes Clusters with Prometheus and Grafana on AWS]]></title>
        <id>6790382dcb2eedbe449b6899</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-cluster-observability-with-prometheus-and-grafana-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T00:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a solid application monitoring and observability strategy is a critical foundational step when deploying infrastructure or software in any environment. Monitoring ensures that your systems are running smoothly, while observability provides i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eti Ijeoma</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metasploit for Beginners — A Guide to the Powerful Exploitation Framework]]></title>
        <id>679037f81f50429b12d52738</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-metasploit-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-22T00:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re starting your journey into penetration testing, you’ve likely heard of Metasploit. Metasploit is one of the most versatile tools in cybersecurity. It helps simplify vulnerability testing and exploitation. Metasploit helps us find and fix we...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-Time Intrusion Detection System with Python and Open-Source Libraries]]></title>
        <id>678faf10f366e60cf6e7b6d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-real-time-intrusion-detection-system-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Intrusion Detection System (IDS) is like a security camera for your network. Just as security cameras help identify suspicious activities in the physical world, an IDS will monitor your network to help detect any potential cyber attacks and securi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a “Starred” Feed]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382660</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-a-starred-feed/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:21:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chris wrote about “Likes” pages a long while back. The idea is rather simple: “Like” an item in your RSS reader and display it in a feed of other liked items. The little example Chris made is still really good.…
Creating a “Starred” Feed originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Discord Webhooks with Next.js 15 – Example Project]]></title>
        <id>678fa927b9b8fe257214e1be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/integrate-discord-webhooks-with-nextjs-15-example-project/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T14:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’ve likely seen (or used) contact forms on websites that ask for customer feedback, potential work opportunities, customer contact info, and so on. But do you know what’s required to get all that feedback, contact info, and data sent to a private ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating The Challenges Of Modern Open-Source Authoring: Lessons Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/navigating-challenges-modern-open-source-authoring/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/navigating-challenges-modern-open-source-authoring/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alvaro Saburido delves into the current state and challenges of Open-Source authoring, sharing lessons learned from both community- and company-driven initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Alvaro Saburido)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for Technical Interviews Using Neetcode 150]]></title>
        <id>67912f406a65d8a9c9ef9f7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-technical-interviews-using-neetcode-150/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-21T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical interviews can be intimidating, especially when you're preparing for roles at top tech companies. To succeed, you need a solid grasp of algorithms, data structures, and problem-solving strategies. The NeetCode 150 is an invaluable resource—...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Reality VS Speculation with Google Machine Learning Engineer Jiquan Ngiam [Podcast #156]]]></title>
        <id>678ad60f07a0a18254c0d6a9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-reality-vs-speculation-jiquan-ngiam-podcast-156/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T22:13:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jiquan Ngiam. He's a former Google Brain engineer who's building tools to make AI useful for everyone – not just developers. We talk about the power of AI and it's practical capabilities, and separat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Langbase Memory Agents to Make Any LLM a Conversational AI for Your Docs]]></title>
        <id>678ac8f3892c4e60d8af0e95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-langbase-memory-agents/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T21:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s 2025, and Large Language Models (LLMs) still can’t access your private data. Ask them something personal, and they’ll either guess or give you the wrong answer. That’s the limitation—they’re trained on public information and don’t have access to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run an Effective Daily Scrum – Tips for Team Members and Managers]]></title>
        <id>678a7845720a1885d5f75ecd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-an-effective-daily-scrum/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T15:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s start with a simple question: Why do we get together for a short meeting each day?  If you work on a Scrum team, you’ve probably heard of a daily scrum, sometimes called a daily stand-up. It’s one of the key events in scrum. The “daily” usually...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fancy Menu Navigation Using Anchor Positioning]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383518</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/fancy-menu-navigation-using-anchor-positioning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T14:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Anchor positioning can be great for little interactive effects — as Temani Afif shows off with this clever idea for a menu hover.
Fancy Menu Navigation Using Anchor Positioning originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Ode To Side Project Time]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/ode-to-side-project-time/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/ode-to-side-project-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-17T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A once-revered perk of some tech workplaces, the status of ‘side project time’ seems to have slipped in recent years. Frederick O’Brien believes it deserves a comeback.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Deep Learning Research Tutorial - Theory, Code, and Math]]></title>
        <id>678921f0a510ee899ead3f7c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understanding-deep-learning-research-tutorial-theory-code-and-math/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T15:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding deep learning research can often feel like unraveling a dense and intricate puzzle. From decoding mathematical notation to navigating complex code bases, the process can be daunting, especially for newcomers. But with the right guidance...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Use GitHub Actions: a Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>6789193ad7f606e4fbf4d0a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-use-github-actions-step-by-step-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T14:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions are one of the most helpful features of GitHub. Actions help you automate, build, test, and deploy your app from your GitHub. They also help you perform code reviews and tests, manage branches, triage issues, and more. In simple terms,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On-Device AI: Building Smarter, Faster, And Private Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/on-device-ai-building-smarter-faster-private-applications/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/on-device-ai-building-smarter-faster-private-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shouldn’t there be a way to keep your apps or project data private and improve performance by reducing server latency? This is what on-device AI is designed to solve. It handles AI processing locally, right on your device, without connecting to the internet and sending data to the cloud. In this article, Joas Pambou explains what on-device AI is, why it’s important, the tools to build this type of technology, and how it can change the way we use technology every day.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Engineering Handbook – How to Start a Career and Excel as an AI Engineer]]></title>
        <id>67881bffe4f437ad54564e34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-ai-engineering-handbook-how-to-start-a-career-and-excel-as-an-ai-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T20:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered who’s behind the groundbreaking technologies like ChatGPT from OpenAI, Tesla’s autonomous vehicles, or the humanoid robots redefining our perception of artificial intelligence? What does it take to be one of those innovators dr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tatev T</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Simplify Python Library RPM Packaging with Mock and Podman]]></title>
        <id>67880c8c282408c6e731883a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/simplify-python-library-rpm-packaging-with-mock-and-podman/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T19:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Packaging libraries and applications written in Python comes with its challenges. And while virtual environments are great for controlling and standardizing installations, there are some scenarios where using them may not be the best. For example, sa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Vicente Nunez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Programmatically Highlight Text with the CSS Custom Highlight API]]></title>
        <id>6787d62041c11049156708c3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-programmatically-highlight-text-with-the-css-custom-highlight-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T15:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can highlight text in the browser by clicking and dragging through the desired text. And sometimes this works fine. But there are times when you’ll want to programmatically highlight some text in an HTML document. In this article, I’ll discuss a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joe Attardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web-Slinger.css: Across the Swiper-Verse]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383533</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-slinger-css-across-the-swiper-verse/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T15:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lee Meyer with a super clever idea using scroll-driven animations as an interaction to "like" or "dislike" something.
Web-Slinger.css: Across the Swiper-Verse originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Dynamic Web Scraper App with Playwright and React: A Step-by-Step Guide]]></title>
        <id>6787cb727ee491a35577e9d5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-dynamic-web-scraper-app-with-playwright-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T14:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are going to build a small web scraper app. This application will scrape data from the Airbnb website and display it in a nice grid view. We will also add a Refresh button that will be able to trigger a new scraping round and update the resu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mihail Gaberov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the Lisp Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>6789208ba535fc45fab6acd4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-lisp-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-15T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to explore a programming language that combines elegance, flexibility, and a rich history of innovation, Lisp is a perfect choice. With over six decades of influence on computer science, Lisp has played a foundational role in sh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up Social Authentication with Strapi and Nuxt.js]]></title>
        <id>6786814ce75a85acb18f1d2d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-social-authentication-with-strapi-and-nuxtjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T15:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing security is a critical aspect of every development process. But it’s crucial to make your apps accessible for users signing up for the application. So, creating a seamless experience for users while they sign up and maintaining security thr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashimi0x</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI in Agriculture: How AI-Enhanced Farming Can Increase Crop Yields [Full Book]]]></title>
        <id>67867ea8a91f104f3f20e6a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ai-in-agriculture-book/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T15:11:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is revolutionizing the agriculture industry, paving the way for a future of smarter, more efficient farming practices. Imagine a world where crops are grown with precision and care, maximizing yields like never before. With AI...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vahe Aslanyan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Few Ways That Cloudways Makes Running This Site a Little Easier]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=382719</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-few-ways-that-cloudways-makes-running-this-site-a-little-easier/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T14:49:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
It’s probably no surprise to you that CSS-Tricks is (proudly) hosted on Cloudways, DigitalOcean’s managed hosting arm. Given both CSS-Tricks and Cloudways are part of DigitalOcean, it was just a matter of time …
A Few Ways That Cloudways Makes Running This Site a Little Easier originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Role Of Illustration Style In Visual Storytelling]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/role-illustration-style-visual-storytelling/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/role-illustration-style-visual-storytelling/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do we determine the most suitable illustration style? How should illustrations complement and reflect your corporate identity? What will resonate most with your target audience? And regarding the content, what type of illustration would best enhance it, and how would it work for the age range it is primarily for? Thomas Bohm shares insightful examples and discusses the key qualities of effective illustrations, emphasizing the importance of understanding your audience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Thomas Bohm)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here are 850+ Ivy League Courses You Can Take Right Now for Free]]></title>
        <id>66d45eb473634435aafcef96</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/ivy-league-free-online-courses-a0d7ae675869/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-14T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Dhawal Shah The 8 Ivy League schools - Harvard, Yale, Princeton, Columbia, Cornell, Dartmouth, Brown, and the University of Pennsylvania - are among the most prestigious universities in the world. In 2025, all 8 Ivy League schools are ranked in th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Simple Portfolio Website With HTML and CSS]]></title>
        <id>67859c6915988a75c229dee2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-simple-portfolio-website-with-html-and-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T23:06:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While browsing through some of my old projects, I stumbled upon a portfolio I worked on a while back. The funny thing? I never used it. So, I decided to give it a fresh look and thought, why not share it with you? As a developer, having a portfolio i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Relational Database Basics – Key Concepts for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>67853e7ede435f43fdeb589d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-relational-database-basics-key-concepts-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital world, data is everywhere, and it’s at the heart of most modern applications. Databases are the unsung heroes that keep it all organised and accessible. Many sites use databases, from social media platforms to online shopping retai...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zubair Idris Aweda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Wait for the sibling-count() and sibling-index() Functions]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383435</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-wait-for-the-sibling-count-and-sibling-index-functions/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T15:08:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I want to look into one of those cases of impatient and how the community has waited for that feature, to be specific, two upcoming functions: sibling-count() and sibling-index().
How to Wait for the sibling-count() and sibling-index() Functions originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Mermaid JavaScript Library to Create Flowcharts]]></title>
        <id>678520dfd55476f9efb1de92</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-mermaid-javascript-library-to-create-flowcharts/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve recently searched for an online diagramming tool, you might have noticed that most of them rely on drag-and-drop functionality. While this is helpful for people who can’t code, it can be hard to maintain. It can also be a bit difficult to m...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Flowcharts and Bring Joy to your Coding]]></title>
        <id>67852099c122b063bd5743eb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-flowcharts-with-mermaid/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-13T14:18:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding can be intense. Especially when you are knee-deep in debugging or trying to map complex projects. For many developers — novice and pros alike — it is not uncommon to spend hours staring at code, looking for answers that won’t come. You may hav...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>evaristo.c</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CUDA and GPU Programming with Elliot Arledge [Podcast #155]]]></title>
        <id>678179c8a470cbfb227dbd02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cuda-gpu-programming-elliot-arledge-podcast-155/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T19:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Elliot Arledge. He's a 20-year old computer science student who's created several popular freeCodeCamp courses on LLMs, the Mojo programming language, and GPU programming with CUDA. He joins us from ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with RHEL: A Beginner’s Guide to Linux Basics]]></title>
        <id>67813ff98eada5cd9c2f7dc7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guide-to-rhel-linux-basics/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T15:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine an operating system so reliable that it powers the world’s biggest servers, the fastest supercomputers, and even the cloud infrastructure of leading tech companies. Welcome to Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) — the backbone of modern IT system...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tanishka Makode</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solo Development: Learning To Let Go Of Perfection]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/solo-development-learning-to-let-go-of-perfection/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/solo-development-learning-to-let-go-of-perfection/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-10T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The best and worst thing about solo development is the “solo” part. There’s a lot of freedom in working alone, and that freedom can be inspiring, but it can also become a debilitating hindrance to productivity and progress. Victor Ayomipo shares his personal lessons on what it takes to navigate solo development and build the “right” app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Ayomipo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Semantic Matching? How to Find Words in a Document Using NLP]]></title>
        <id>67802329a9edea9df0053dd7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-semantic-matching-find-words-in-a-document-using-nlp/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T19:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever found yourself searching a document for a specific word or phrase just to discover that the term you're looking for isn't there? It can be frustrating, right? Sometimes, even though you might not see the exact term you’re looking for, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ibrahim ogunbiyi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tight Mode: Why Browsers Produce Different Performance Results]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383563</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/tight-mode-why-browsers-produce-different-performance-results/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T16:16:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote a post for Smashing Magazine that was published today about this thing that Chrome and Safari have called “Tight Mode” and how it impacts page performance. I’d never heard the term until DebugBear’s Matt Zeunert mentioned it in …
Tight Mode: Why Browsers Produce Different Performance Results originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tight Mode: Why Browsers Produce Different Performance Results]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/tight-mode-why-browsers-produce-different-performance-results/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/tight-mode-why-browsers-produce-different-performance-results/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We know that browsers do all sorts of different things under the hood. One of those things is the way they not only *fetch* resources like images and scripts from the server but how they [prioritize those resources](https://www.debugbear.com/blog/request-priorities?utm_campaign=sm-7). Chrome and Safari have implemented a “Tight Mode” that constrains which resources are loaded and in what order, but they each take drastically different approaches to it. With so little information about Tight Mode available, this article attempts a high-level explanation of what it is, what triggers it, and how it is treated differently in major browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Geoff Graham)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Language Server Protocol – Easier Code Editing Across Languages and Tools]]></title>
        <id>677ef3f83b47b21899e957c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-the-language-server-protocol-easier-code-editing-across-languages/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T21:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past, many code editors were built just for one specific language. To provide rich and smart code editing, tight integration between the editor and the language tooling was a must. On the other hand, there were (and still are) more general-pur...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Pliutau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Talk to Any Database Using AI – Build Your Own SQL Query Data Extractor]]></title>
        <id>677ef38c05d7f213e7d2a766</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/talk-to-databases-using-ai-build-a-sql-query-data-extractor/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T21:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I took a break from writing to focus on my exams. During this time, I had an interesting experience: I had the chance to explain SQL (Structured Query Language) to my peers. While exploring SQL in-depth, I encountered a common frustration: ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prankur Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Generative AI in 23 Hours]]></title>
        <id>677ee5d707323c1a72821397</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-generative-ai-in-23-hours/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T20:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is revolutionizing industries and workflows, and learning to work with AI in the cloud is an important skill for modern developers. Whether you're a beginner or looking to deepen your understanding of generative AI, this cours...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Christmas Icons with JavaScript and HTML]]></title>
        <id>677ede843a92814ab28fbf50</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-christmas-icons-with-javascript-and-html/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T20:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating unique projects is one of the best ways to grow as a programmer, and what better way to learn than by building something creative for the holiday season? Imagine crafting a festive Christmas calendar from scratch, generating eye-catching, cu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lesser Known Uses Of Better Known Attributes]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/lesser-known-uses-better-known-attributes/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/lesser-known-uses-better-known-attributes/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML attributes are like little instructions that we add to the markup of elements to make them do certain things or behave in certain ways. For example, most of us know that the `target` attribute with a value of `_blank` opens the link in a new tab or window. But did you know that you can use it on the `form` element, too? John Rhea presents several lesser-known uses for common HTML attributes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (John Rhea)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Discover Hidden Subdomains as an Ethical Hacker]]></title>
        <id>677d84ad446398ca6f670bef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-discover-hidden-subdomains-as-an-ethical-hacker/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Subdomains are an essential part of a website’s infrastructure. They provide additional functions in a web application, such as APIs, admin portals, and staging environments. As an ethical hacker, discovering subdomains is a critical step in learning...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Help Someone with Their Code Using the Socratic Method]]></title>
        <id>677d816db702998ae550cebf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-help-someone-with-their-code-using-the-socratic-method/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a programming community, freeCodeCamp helps many people who have questions about their code. It can be quite tempting to simply provide the learner with the answer and move on, but that’s actually detrimental to the learning process. Here’s why: W...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Naomi Carrigan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Run Integration Tests with GitHub Service Containers]]></title>
        <id>677d8125f9b13835118c7958</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-integration-tests-with-github-service-containers/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T19:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I published an article about using Testcontainers to emulate external dependencies like a database and cache for backend integration tests. That article also explained the different ways of running the integration tests, environment scaffol...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Pliutau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Design For High-Traffic Events And Prevent Your Website From Crashing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/designing-high-traffic-events-cloudways/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/designing-high-traffic-events-cloudways/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product drops and sales are a great way to increase revenue, but these events can result in traffic spikes that affect a site’s availability and performance. To prevent website crashes, you’ll have to make sure that the sites you design can handle large numbers of server requests at once. Let’s discuss how!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Saad Khan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Spreadsheets by Building 33 Projects]]></title>
        <id>677ee4b10bc6d529ee0098b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-spreadsheets-by-building-33-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-07T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spreadsheets are an essential tool for managing data, solving problems, and automating workflows, whether you're a student, professional, or hobbyist. Mastering them can unlock countless possibilities in productivity and creativity. Imagine automatin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVM Kernels Explained: How to Tackle Nonlinear Data in Machine Learning]]></title>
        <id>677c5a037d6144e9c5ef49f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/svm-kernels-how-to-tackle-nonlinear-data-in-machine-learning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T22:32:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever considered how your phone can recognize handwritten text and convert it into regular computer text? Or how your email can separate messages automatically into spam and non-spam categories? Both of these examples work based on classifica...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josiah Adesola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Importance of Investing in Soft Skills in the Age of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-importance-of-investing-in-soft-skills-in-the-age-of-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T14:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am still an AI skeptic. The biggest risk I foresee is that if your sole responsibility is to write code, your job is at risk. It’s not time to panic, but I do see a lot of value in evolving your soft skills.
The Importance of Investing in Soft Skills in the Age of AI originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Bell</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Does AI Really Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/understanding-ai-meaning/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/01/understanding-ai-meaning/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-06T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We, as human beings, don’t worry too much about making sure the connections land at the right point. Our brain just works that way, declaratively. However, for building AI, we need to be more explicit. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Atila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Real-time Network Traffic Dashboard with Python and Streamlit]]></title>
        <id>67786dec9c66c24e89239f0a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-real-time-network-traffic-dashboard-with-python-and-streamlit/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T23:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to visualize your network traffic in real-time? In this tutorial, you will be learning how to build an interactive network traffic analysis dashboard with Python and Streamlit. Streamlit is an open-source Python framework you can...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chaitanya Rahalkar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Server-Sent Events vs WebSockets – How to Choose a Real-Time Data Exchange Protocol]]></title>
        <id>677835cd5280589b2bc82110</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/server-sent-events-vs-websockets/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T19:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our fast-paced digital era, real-time data exchange has become critical in creating responsive and dynamic user experiences. It’s especially important in applications like live news updates, chat systems, AI generative platforms, and so on. In thi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Svitlana Lorman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Terraform – Infrastructure-as-Code in Practice]]></title>
        <id>67782a8fd3a89d514105e418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-terraform-infrastructure-as-code-in-practice/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-03T18:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, cloud development has seen a major paradigm shift. Newer and more complex applications are deployed rapidly to the cloud to minimize downtime. And through all of this, the concept of Infrastructure-as-Code and various tools have emerg...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Learning to Code Easier by Focusing on the Fundamentals]]></title>
        <id>6776aff4291cde01e8a6dff0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-learning-to-code-easier-by-focusing-on-the-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T15:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the beginning of the year again, and perhaps you’re still struggling to learn that programming language. We’ve all been there. Let me share a story from my own journey. In 2016, I thought I wasn’t cut out for programming. After months of trying ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Optimize Next.js Web Apps for Better Performance]]></title>
        <id>6776a323218b455d646035b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/optimize-nextjs-web-apps-for-better-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-01-02T14:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As engineers, we often get so carried away with other aspects of development that we overlook how users perceive and interact with our applications. This oversight can result in users leaving the app almost as soon as they arrive, leading to higher b...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ayantunji Timilehin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Front-End Features For Designers In 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/12/new-front-end-features-for-designers-in-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/12/new-front-end-features-for-designers-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searching for the most flexible front-end workflows and toolkits, it’s easy to forget how powerful some of the fundamentals on the web have become these days. This post is a journey through new front-end features and what they are capable of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year, New Hopes, New Dreams (January 2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2024/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-31T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe 2025 has already started as you’re reading this, maybe you’re still waiting for the big countdown to begin — either way, it’s never too late or too early for some New Year’s inspiration! Our new collection of desktop wallpapers has got you covered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thank You (2024 Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=383295</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/thank-you-2024-edition/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T16:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm more thankful this time around because, last year, I didn't even get to write this post. But now that I'm back, writing this feels so, so, so good. There's a lot more gusto going into my writing when I say: thank you so very much! Let's tie a bow on this year and round up what happened around here in 2024.
Thank You (2024 Edition) originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile App Development with React Native]]></title>
        <id>6772ae6d57dd031ab1ad4671</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mobile-app-development-with-react-native/"/>
        <updated>2024-12-30T14:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile app development has become an essential skill in today’s digital landscape, and React Native is one of the leading tools for creating powerful, cross-platform mobile apps. React Native combines the best parts of React and native app developmen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>