<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-04-15T00:14:33.844Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Local RAG App with Ollama and ChromaDB in the R Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>67fd5ac89a2c2895da61d799</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-local-rag-app-with-ollama-and-chromadb-in-r/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T18:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Large Language Model (LLM) is a type of machine learning model that is trained to understand and generate human-like text. These models are trained on vast datasets to capture the nuances of human language, enabling them to generate coherent and co...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elabonga Atuo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate CI/CD with GitHub Actions and Streamline Your Workflow]]></title>
        <id>67fd2db6c741f3f1aec5ecd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-cicd-with-github-actions-streamline-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T15:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CI/CD stands for Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery. It is a system or set of processes and methodologies that help developers quickly update codebases and deploy applications. The Continuous Integration (CI) part of CI/CD means that deve...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the CSS text-wrap Property to Create Balanced Text Layouts on Your Websites]]></title>
        <id>67fd1442fd23722b0a451053</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-css-text-wrap-property/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T13:57:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An inconsistent text layout can really ruin the look of your website’s design. Maybe a heading has an extra word that wraps to another line, or in a paragraph some lines are longer than others. This can leave the whole thing looking messy and hard to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Azubuike Duru</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Proxmox Cluster for Free – Virtualization Basics]]></title>
        <id>67fd1282e4687cd6aa7dcd1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-a-proxmox-cluster-virtualization-basics/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T13:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtualization is a game-changer for developers, hobbyists, and IT enthusiasts. It lets you run multiple operating systems on one machine, which is perfect for testing apps, hosting servers, or learning new tech. If you want to take it further, clust...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shamsuddoha Ranju</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Django Signals in Your Projects]]></title>
        <id>67fd101ad7ec2850d2df790d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-django-signals-in-your-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T13:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Django signals can be a lifesaver if you're building anything with Django and want your code to stay clean and organized. They help you connect different parts of your app without everything getting tangled together. Think of them like walkie-talkies...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next Level CSS Styling for Cursors]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385604</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/next-level-css-styling-for-cursors/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-14T12:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom cursors with CSS are great, but we can take things to the next level with JavaScript. Using JavaScript, we can transition between cursor states, place dynamic text within the cursor, apply complex animations, and apply filters.
Next Level CSS Styling for Cursors originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Declan Chidlow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Accountant to Data Engineer with Alyson La [Podcast #168]]]></title>
        <id>67f9c04b3e25f02ff9a26b80</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-accountant-to-data-engineer-with-alyson-la-podcast-168/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-12T01:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Alyson La. She taught herself how to code while working as an accountant at GitHub and was able to transition to a data scientist there, then ultimately a software e...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TypeSpec for Documenting and Modeling APIs]]></title>
        <id>67f96c998b09f2bdfa144c8b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-typespec-for-documenting-and-modeling-apis/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T19:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're curious and passionate about technology like I am, and you’re looking for clarity in your code, you've likely already experienced the limitations of conventional tools for documenting and modeling APIs. Tools such as Swagger, JSON Schema, o...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adalbert Pungu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks Chronicles XLIII]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385404</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-chronicles-xliii/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-11T12:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This CSS-Tricks update highlights significant progress in the Almanac, recent podcast appearances, a new CSS counters guide, and the addition of several new authors contributing valuable content.
CSS-Tricks Chronicles XLIII originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Train Your Own LLM]]></title>
        <id>67f8338f0d301512a59fb77f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/train-your-own-llm/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T21:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how large language models like ChatGPT are actually built? Behind these impressive AI tools lies a complex but fascinating process of data preparation, model training, and fine-tuning. While it might seem like something only experts wit...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gild Just One Lily]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/gild-just-one-lily/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/gild-just-one-lily/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Gilding the lily” isn’t always bad. In design, a touch of metaphorical gold — a subtle animated transition, a hint of color, or added depth in a drop shadow — can help communicate a level of care and attention that builds trust. But first? You need a lily. Nail the fundamentals. Then, gild it carefully.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Garrity)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extend the Django User Model]]></title>
        <id>67f7ccb69fc8333e720a4185</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-extend-the-django-user-model/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T13:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're working with Django and building anything that involves user accounts – like a blog, a store, or a membership site – you’ll likely hit a point where the default user model just isn’t enough. Maybe you want to add a profile picture, a phone ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Udemezue John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Lazygit to Improve Your Git Workflow]]></title>
        <id>67f7cc7aaf72aa46d378eaa0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-lazygit-to-improve-your-git-workflow/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T13:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lazygit is an open-source command line terminal UI for Git commands that I’ve used for the last couple of years, and it’s become my new best friend. Basically, the Lazygit tool is a wrapper for the Git command line that replaces it with a UI. Instead...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rajdeep Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tailwind’s @apply Feature is Better Than it Sounds]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385232</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/tailwinds-apply-feature-is-better-than-it-sounds/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T12:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the time, people showcase Tailwind's @apply feature with one of Tailwind's single-property utilities (which changes a single CSS declaration). When showcased this way, @apply doesn't sound promising at all. So obviously, nobody wants to use it. Personally, I think Tailwind's @apply feature is better than described.
Tailwind’s @apply Feature is Better Than it Sounds originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zell Liew</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cascading Layouts: A Workshop on Resilient CSS Layouts]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385758</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cascading-layouts-a-workshop-on-resilient-css-layouts/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-10T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If I were starting with CSS today for the very first time, I would first want to spend time understanding writing modes because that’s a great place to wrap your head around direction and document flow. But right after that, …
Cascading Layouts: A Workshop on Resilient CSS Layouts originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Clojure – Learn Clojure Programming Basics]]></title>
        <id>67f7044b8d28cad83fb095a2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-clojure-programming-basics/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T23:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial introduces the programming language, Clojure. Clojure is an awesome functional programming language that runs on Java's Virtual Machine (JVM). It is sometimes called a LISP, which is short for 'LISt Processing'. You'll need to have some...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Lynx to Create JavaScript Mobile Apps]]></title>
        <id>67f6a2b6a00282687c8e224d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-lynx-to-create-javascript-mobile-apps/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T16:39:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving landscape of cross-platform development, a new player has emerged that promises to revolutionize the way developers create applications: Lynx. Developed by ByteDance, the company behind TikTok, Lynx is an open-source framework...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Carousels]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385672</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-carousels/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-09T13:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome has prototyped these features and released them in Chrome 135. Adam Argyle has a wonderful explainer over at the Chrome Developer blog. Kevin Powell has an equally wonderful video where he follows the explainer. This post is me taking notes from them.
CSS Carousels originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Multilingual Social Recipe Application with Flutter and Strapi]]></title>
        <id>67f59a4c27d15057ec14c438</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multilingual-social-recipe-app-with-flutter-and-strapi/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T21:51:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there! In this project, you will build a multilingual social recipe application using Flutter and Strapi. Flutter is an open-source UI software development kit created by Google. It allows you to build beautiful and highly interactive user interf...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevine Nzapdi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Setup and Installation Tools – CMake, vcpkg, Docker & Copilot]]></title>
        <id>67f5418259aa448cc705cefd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-setup-and-installation-tools-cmake-vcpkg-docker-and-copilot/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T15:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up a C++ development environment can be one of the most challenging aspects for newcomers, especially when juggling different operating systems and toolchains. Whether you’re aiming to build robust applications or contribute to professional-g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Manim For Making UI Animations]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/using-manim-making-ui-animations/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/using-manim-making-ui-animations/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-08T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animation makes things clearer, especially for designers and front-end developers working on UI, prototypes, or interactive visuals. Manim is a tool that lets you create smooth and dynamic animations, not just for the design field but also in math, coding, and beyond, to explain complex ideas or simply make everything a little bit more interactive.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joas Pambou)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling Like I Have No Release: A Journey Towards Sane Deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385271</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/feeling-like-i-have-no-release-a-journey-towards-sane-deployments/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying like an idiot comes down to a mismatch between the tools you use to deploy and the reward in complexity reduced versus complexity added.
Feeling Like I Have No Release: A Journey Towards Sane Deployments originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Live Chat to Your Applications with Rocket.chat]]></title>
        <id>67f3d275332a812ead444418</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-live-chat-to-your-applications-with-rocketchat/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-07T13:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fastest way to gather valuable information about your site’s users is still by talking to them. And what better way to do this than by adding a chat system to your app? For my case, I just wanted to add a chat system to my portfolio website so I]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Spruce Emmanuel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From drop-out to software architect with Jason Lengstorf [Podcast #167]]]></title>
        <id>67f041c2f87b5fbfcc550e46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-drop-out-to-software-architect-with-jason-lengstorf-podcast-167/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T20:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Jason Lengstorf. He learned to code out of necessity building websites for local emo bands. He dropped out of college but eventually worked as an engineer at IBM and has gone on to roles at many othe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Vulnerabilities and Exploits for Ethical Hackers]]></title>
        <id>67eff5fe4b8a95f016459cda</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vulnerabilities-vs-exploits-for-ethical-hackers/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T15:08:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding vulnerabilities and exploits is crucial for anyone interested in cybersecurity. Let's learn what they are. What Are Vulnerabilities? A vulnerability is a flaw in software or hardware that attackers can exploit. These flaws can range fro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New “Web” Readiness Report]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385268</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-new-web-readiness-report/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T13:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML 5 Readiness was a site that showed through a rainbow of colors the browser support for several web features. What about a new version?
A New “Web” Readiness Report originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Business Case To Promote Accessibility In Your B2B Products]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/how-build-business-case-promote-accessibility-b2b-products/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/how-build-business-case-promote-accessibility-b2b-products/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-04T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When passion for accessibility meets business indifference, what bridges the gap? Gloria Diaz Alonso shares how she turned frustration into strategy — by learning to speak the language of business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gloria Diaz Alonso)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Wireshark Filters to Analyze Your Network Traffic]]></title>
        <id>67ee83d004f007db33e0f920</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/use-wireshark-filters-to-analyze-network-traffic/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-03T12:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireshark is an open-source tool widely regarded as the gold standard for network packet analysis. It allows you to capture live network traffic or inspect pre-recorded capture files, breaking down the data into individual packets for detailed examin...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hang Hu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cryptography Handbook: Exploring RSA PKCSv1.5, OAEP, and PSS]]></title>
        <id>67edb47680c0ce2ff2faebb9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-cryptography-handbook-rsa-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T22:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RSA algorithm was introduced in 1978 in the seminal paper, "A Method for Obtaining Digital Signatures and Public-Key Cryptosystems". Over the decades, as RSA became integral to secure communications, various vulnerabilities and attacks have emerg...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hamdaan Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Node.js Application on AWS]]></title>
        <id>67ed67823b8c37d192779b99</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-deploy-a-nodejs-application-on-aws/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T16:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud platforms and infrastructure allow you to easily deploy and host backend services and applications. In this article, you’ll learn how to run a Node.js/Express application away from the confines of your local personal computer to make it accessi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oluwatobi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code a full stack Instagram Clone with Laravel and MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>67ed4efef1d155fc22688c46</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/code-a-full-stack-instagram-clone-with-laravel-and-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T14:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to transform your web development skills by building a complex, real-world application? We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Laravel and MongoDB to create a full stack Instagram ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fetch API vs. Axios vs. Alova: Which HTTP Client Should You Use in 2025?]]></title>
        <id>67ed4e54f03ad9ca955f36d0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/fetch-api-vs-axios-vs-alova/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T14:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the days of the Fetch API and Axios, developers used callback-based HTTP requests. They manually managed requests with asynchronous operations and, in the process, wrote deeply nested code. This was known as callback hell. Then, in 2015, a pro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdullah Salaudeen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Failure to International Success: How Online Learning Platforms Saved My Life]]></title>
        <id>67ed3edd597c0ff6bdcf4c45</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-online-learning-platforms-saved-my-life/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T13:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is better to be a samurai in a garden than an agricultural worker in a war - Miyamoto Musashi In this article, I’ll share my story. When I was younger, I thought I was destined to be a failure in life. To be isolated from everyone. But years late...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMIL on?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385540</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/smil-on/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T12:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, it turns out that SVG's built-in animation features were never deprecated as planned. Sure, CSS and JavaScript are more than capable of carrying the load, but it's good to know that SMIL is not dead in the water as previously thought, and is actually well-supported.
SMIL on? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Drupal To Storyblok Migration Tool: An Engineering Perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/building-drupal-storyblok-migration-tool-engineering-perspective/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/04/building-drupal-storyblok-migration-tool-engineering-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-02T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Edoardo Dusi shares the engineering and architectural choices made by the team at Storyblok and how real-world migration challenges were addressed using modern PHP practices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Edoardo Dusi)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand and Code DeepSeek V3]]></title>
        <id>67ec22879f76b0cdc2046ddb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/understand-and-code-deepseek-v3/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T17:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DeepSeek V3 is a cutting-edge large language model. It leverages sophisticated techniques like a unique Multi-Head Latent Attention mechanism and a Mixture of Experts architecture for enhanced efficiency and capability. Understanding this model provi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting Strong DX With Astro Components and TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385086</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/crafting-strong-dx-with-astro-components-and-typescript/"/>
        <updated>2025-04-01T13:50:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing we can do to help teams code consistently is provide type-checking so that all of the configurable options for a specific component are available while coding. Bryan demonstrates how he does this with TypeScript when working with Astro components.
Crafting Strong DX With Astro Components and TypeScript originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bryan Robinson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Team of AI Agents for Your Website for Free Using Agno and Groq]]></title>
        <id>67eb1b3398e2cf5154940366</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-team-of-ai-agents-for-your-website-for-free/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T22:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is quickly changing the way we work, and more and more companies are using it to help them get and retain clients. Teams are also using AI to create innovative and responsive websites capable of engaging visitors while also providing helpful infor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Baisden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Worlds Collide: Keyframe Collision Detection Using Style Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385188</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/worlds-collide-keyframe-collision-detection-using-style-queries/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T14:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interactive CSS animations with elements ricocheting off each other seem more plausible in 2025. While it’s unnecessary to implement Pong in CSS, the increasing flexibility and power of CSS reinforce Lee's suspicion that one day it will be a lifestyle choice whether to achieve any given effect with scripting or CSS.
Worlds Collide: Keyframe Collision Detection Using Style Queries originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lee Meyer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blossoms, Flowers, And The Magic Of Spring (April 2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-31T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The beginning of the new month is the perfect opportunity to give your desktop a makeover. If you’re looking for some beautiful and unique wallpapers to cater for a bit of inspiration this April, well, this post has got you covered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From broke musician to working dev. How college drop-out Ryan Furrer taught himself to code [Podcast #166]]]></title>
        <id>67e6f817cd414b8fc3de97c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-broke-musician-to-working-dev-ryan-furrer-podcast-166/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T19:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Ryan Furrer. He's a Front End Engineer working on tools that help companies monitor their buildings for energy usage, water leaks, and other environmental factors. Ryan dropped out of college and wor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Your Code is Slow: Common  Performance Mistakes Beginners Make]]></title>
        <id>67e6c26a4c687a76c3f3934d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-your-code-is-slow-common-performance-mistakes-beginners-make/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T15:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe you’ve experienced something like this before: you’ve written code that works, but when you hit “run,” it takes forever. You stare at the spinner, wondering if it’s faster to just solve the problem by hand. But you end up looking something like...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy a Restful Web Service on Microsoft Azure App Service]]></title>
        <id>67e6c180423cd4f90a6350b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-a-restful-web-service-on-microsoft-azure-app-service/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T15:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there! 👋, How’s it going? I hope you're doing well. Whether you're a seasoned coder, a curious learner, or just someone browsing through, welcome to my little corner of the internet. In this tutorial, we’ll dive into how you can deploy a web ser...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alaran Ayobami</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Home VPN Using Tailscale on a Raspberry Pi]]></title>
        <id>67e6c11d423cd4f90a6350ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/set-up-a-home-vpn-using-tailscale-on-a-raspberry-pi/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T15:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, you’ll learn how to set up a VPN which you can host on a Raspberry Pi. I am a fan of Raspberry Pis because these small form factor computers are a favourite tool for tinkerers, like me. This VPN will allow you to access your home net...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Anomfueme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Visual Regression Testing With Playwright]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385297</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/automated-visual-regression-testing-with-playwright/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T15:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With visual regression testing, we can update a page, take screenshots before and after the fact, and compare the results for unintended changes. In this article, learn how to set up visual regression testing using Playwright.
Automated Visual Regression Testing With Playwright originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frederik Dohr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Send Emails in Python using Mailtrap SMTP and the Email API]]></title>
        <id>67e6ab43aa64aee164e7985e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/send-emails-in-python-using-mailtrap-smtp-and-the-email-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T13:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I’ll walk you through the process of sending emails in Python using two different methods:  The traditional SMTP setup with the built-in ‘smtplib’ module.  Mailtrap email API via Mailtrap’s official SDK.  If you’re unfamiliar wi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Argue Against AI-First Research]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-argue-against-ai-first-research/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/how-to-argue-against-ai-first-research/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies have been turning their attention to “synthetic,” AI-driven user testing. However, as convenient as it might seem, it’s dangerous, expensive, and usually diminishes user value. Let’s take a closer look at why exactly it is problematic and how we can argue against it to make a case for UX research with real users. Part of [Smart Interface Design Patterns](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com) by yours truly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the top Excel formulas and functions]]></title>
        <id>67e5643f0a2aebb29e2c2264</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-top-excel-formulas-and-functions/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-27T14:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Excel is one of the most powerful tools for data analysis, organization, and automation. Whether you're a student, business professional, or data analyst, mastering Excel formulas and functions can significantly boost your productivity. However, with...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive Video Streaming With Dash.js In React]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/adaptive-video-streaming-dashjs-react/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/adaptive-video-streaming-dashjs-react/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML `` is the de facto element we turn to for embedding video content, but it comes with constraints. For example, it downloads the video file linearly over HTTP, which leads to performance hiccups, especially for large videos consumed on slower connections. But with adaptive bitrate streaming, we can split the video into multiple segments at different bitrates and resolutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Teng Wei Herr)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Programming in C++]]></title>
        <id>67e48bff04e3150220f40379</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-programming-in-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T23:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, I’ll give you a comprehensive introduction to programming in C++. You don't need to have any previous programming experience in order to begin. Along the way, you will learn about the flow of control, variables, conditional statemen...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Move Figma Components to Penpot]]></title>
        <id>67e48bc10d600bc3806ccf54</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-recreate-figma-components-in-penpot/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T23:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Penpot is an open-source design tool for creating complete design systems. It is free, self-hostable, and allows multiple projects. Penpot supports reusable components and assets and allows files and libraries to be shared across projects. Penpot fil...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fatuma Abdullahi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create Microservices with NestJS]]></title>
        <id>67e434766d7e1561ea4bf0e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-microservices-with-nestjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T17:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microservices architecture has become a popular approach for building scalable and maintainable applications. By breaking down large applications into smaller, independent services, developers can improve performance, maintainability, and scalability...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host Local LLMs in a Docker Container on Azure]]></title>
        <id>67e42705cb510eea06095d36</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/host-llms-locally-in-docker-on-azure/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T16:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever run into a situation where you want to test some local AI models, but your computer doesn't have enough specs to run them? Or maybe you just don't like bloating your computer with a ton of AI models? You're not alone in this. I’ve faced...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shrijal Acharya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is SRE? A Beginner's Guide to Site Reliability Engineering]]></title>
        <id>67e4265f7281ac30028843e1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-site-reliability-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T16:07:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s digital age, we expect our online experiences to be fast, reliable, and always available. But what happens behind the scenes to make our expectations a reality? The answer is Site Reliability Engineering (SRE). SRE is a discipline that ens...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Omolade Ekpeni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Extract  YouTube Analytics Data and Analyze in Python]]></title>
        <id>67e425c92a171465d4fb4cce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/extract-youtube-analytics-data-and-analyze-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-26T16:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a YouTube content creator, you’ll make data-driven decisions when posting content. This helps you target the right audience when creating your videos. YouTube Studio provides YouTube Analytics, where you can get comprehensive data about you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adejumo Ridwan Suleiman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Connect Your AWS EC2 Instance to VS Code]]></title>
        <id>67e2ec52cd467794ee79d63e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-connect-your-aws-ec2-instance-to-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T17:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a DevOps engineer, it is crucial to master at least one cloud provider. Cloud services simplify storage, data migration, and CI/CD workflows and help make these tasks easier and more efficient. If you need a basic introduction to cloud computing, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner's Guide to Observability in Cloud Native Applications]]></title>
        <id>67e2d66c64d44185d5a6d406</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/observability-in-cloud-native-applications/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T16:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're new to cloud native technologies, you may have heard the term 'observability' before. But what exactly does it mean? Is it simply the ability to observe? And if so, what are we observing and why? I had the same questions when I started lear...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Victoria Nduka</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orchestrating AWS Lambda with GraphQL and Apollo Connectors]]></title>
        <id>67e2d5e080e11112e050be00</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-orchestrate-aws-lambda-with-graphql-and-apollo-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T16:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Lambda is a computing service that enables you to run arbitrary code functions without needing to provision, manage, or scale servers. It’s often used in the logic tier of a multi-tier architecture to handle tasks such as processing files in S3 o...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rob Walters</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python's Built-in Profiling Tools: Examples and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>67e2d5a9436e3bed610a8a95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-pythons-built-in-profiling-tools-examples-and-best-practices/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T16:11:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python is known for its simplicity and readability, making it a favorite among developers. But this simplicity sometimes comes at the cost of performance. When your Python application grows or needs to handle larger workloads, understanding what's ha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sahu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Host a Static Website on AWS S3 and CloudFront]]></title>
        <id>67e2cd0841be93b03e257b93</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/host-a-static-website-on-aws-s3-and-cloudfront/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T15:34:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps might seem like a complex field with various specializations and tools. In this article, I’ll simplify one key aspect by demonstrating how to host a static website using Amazon S3 (Simple Storage Service) and CloudFront, AWS’s Content Delivery...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oghenekparobo Stephen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use TestContainers in .Net]]></title>
        <id>67e2cbfdaa97659cd53cf39f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-testcontainers-in-net/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At some point in your development lifecycle, you will need to test that your system can integrate with another system, whether it be another API, a database, or caching service, for example. This can be a laborious task of spinning up other servers h...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Grant Riordan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Case Study: Combining Cutting-Edge CSS Features Into a “Course Navigation” Component]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/case-study-combining-cutting-edge-css-features-into-a-course-navigation-component/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-25T12:47:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having been tasked with creating a UI component for navigating the content of an online course, Daniel found himself neck-deep in a pool of new CSS features that he wound up using on the project.
Case Study: Combining Cutting-Edge CSS Features Into a “Course Navigation” Component originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Send Email Function using Nodemailer and OAuth2]]></title>
        <id>67e1ec8917e7e6a0f12cddf5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-send-email-function-using-nodemailer-and-oauth2/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-24T23:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to communicate by sending emails through web applications is important these days. It helps businesses stay connected with their potential customers. In this article, you’ll learn how to implement the Send Email function in your web app us...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Okoro Emmanuel Nzube</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Support Logical Shorthands in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385389</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/support-logical-shorthands-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-24T14:06:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a bit of a blind spot when working with CSS logical properties concerning shorthands.
Support Logical Shorthands in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From hating coding to programming satellites at age 37 with Francesco Ciulla [Podcast #165]]]></title>
        <id>67ddbf930d353b1d4dfa0ebd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/programming-satellites-at-age-37-with-francesco-ciulla-podcast-165/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T19:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, I interview Francesco Ciulla. He's a software engineer who has worked with the European Space Agency on code that powers the Copernicus satellite program. More Francesco has published courses on learning Docker ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn API Fundamentals and Architecture – A Beginner-Friendly Guide]]></title>
        <id>67dd93c136028f6326576025</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-api-fundamentals-and-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T16:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some questions for you: How do you log in to apps with your Google, Apple, or Microsoft account? How do online payments with Paystack or PayPal work? How do apps like Facebook and Instagram share information and notifications? The answer is:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ikegah Oliver</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revisiting CSS border-image]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385158</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/revisiting-css-border-image/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T13:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve used border-image regularly. Yet, it remains one of the most underused CSS tools, and I can’t, for the life of me, figure out why. Is it possible that people steer clear of border-image because its syntax is awkward and unintuitive? Perhaps it’s because most explanations don’t solve the type of creative implementation problems that most people need to solve. Most likely, it’s both.
Revisiting CSS border-image originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Previewing Content Changes In Your Work With document.designMode]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/previewing-content-changes-work-documentdesignmode/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/previewing-content-changes-work-documentdesignmode/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You probably already know that you can use developer tools in your browser to make on-the-spot changes to a webpage — simply click the node in the Inspector and make your edits. But have you tried `document.designMode`? Victor Ayomipo explains how it can be used to preview content changes and demonstrates several use cases where it comes in handy for everything from basic content editing to improving team collaboration.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Victor Ayomipo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn ANY Language with AI]]></title>
        <id>67dc708354ef5aaf882f3c39</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-any-language-with-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T19:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning a new language can feel overwhelming, but what if you had an intelligent, always-available language tutor to help? With AI-powered tools like ChatGPT and DeepSeek, you can improve your fluency, enhance your vocabulary, and practice real-worl...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Full Stack AI Note Taking App with Next.js and Supabase]]></title>
        <id>67dc6f4f604a3dc95c9fc77d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-full-stack-ai-note-taking-app-with-nextjs-and-supabase/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T19:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taking notes is a fundamental skill for staying organized, whether you're a student, professional, or developer. But what if your notes could do more than just store information? Imagine having an intelligent note-taking app that allows you to organi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Python Magic Methods Work: A Practical Guide]]></title>
        <id>67dc33ff64b6723cee52486b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-magic-methods-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T15:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how Python makes objects work with operators like + or -? Or how it knows how to display objects when you print them? The answer lies in Python's magic methods, also known as dunder (double under) methods. Magic methods are spe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivek Sahu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick Reminder That :is() and :where() Are Basically the Same With One Key Difference]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385336</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quick-reminder-that-is-and-where-are-basically-the-same-with-one-key-difference/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-20T13:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve seen a handful of recent posts talking about the utility of the :is() relational pseudo-selector. No need to delve into the details other than to say it can help make compound selectors a lot more readable.
:is(section, article, aside, 
…
Quick Reminder That :is() and :where() Are Basically the Same With One Key Difference originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Security Audits Are Important]]></title>
        <id>67db2704d898a5f4273111cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-security-audits-are-important/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T20:20:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this digital world, companies rely on the latest technology to run their businesses, and the risk of cyber attacks is high. Every product, whether it’s software or an application, should go through some sort of security testing process. These chec...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>P S Mohammed Ali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Write Effective Prompts for AI Agents using Langbase]]></title>
        <id>67dae1dae49263fce2ef7dc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-write-effective-prompts-for-ai-agents-using-langbase/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-19T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt engineering isn’t just a skill these days – it gives you an important competitive edge in your development. In 2025, the difference between AI agents that work and those that don’t comes down to how well they’re prompted. Whether you’re a deve...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maham Codes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Need to Know About Web Acessibility]]></title>
        <id>67d9aa58a50edbbdc70e2941</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-web-accessibility-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-18T17:16:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is a great place to access information and connect with people. It has opened up countless opportunities, making life more convenient in many ways. But not everyone experiences the web in the same way. Websites are difficult to use for people...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kunal Nalawade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate Alert Provisioning with the SigNoz Terraform Provider]]></title>
        <id>67d87353b13a6fd9fb559ada</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/automate-alert-provisioning-with-the-signoz-terraform-provider/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T19:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern infrastructure requires continuous monitoring and rapid incident response. However, manually configuring and managing alerts is not only labor-intensive but also susceptible to human error. Automating alert provisioning allows you to enforce c...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gursimar Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Debug and Prevent Buffer Overflows in Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>67d84f228d156200bc7d3d8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-debug-and-prevent-buffer-overflows-in-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T16:34:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Buffer overflows are one of the most serious software bugs, especially in embedded systems, where hardware limitations and real-time execution make them hard to detect and fix. A buffer overflow happens when a program writes more data into a buffer t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Soham Banerjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styling Counters in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=384529</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/styling-counters-in-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T16:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Going from the most basic ways to style lists directly in HTML to advanced customization techniques that are even capable of making things that aren't lists look like lists.
Styling Counters in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Scraping With RSelenium (Chrome Driver) and Rvest]]></title>
        <id>67d8272af45871e3e821d5fa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-scraping-with-rselenium-chrome-driver-and-rvest/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T13:44:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web scraping lets you automatically extract data from websites, so you can store it in a structured format for later use. In this article, you'll explore how to use popular R libraries for web scraping to extract data from a website. The target websi...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elabonga Atuo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Components Vs. Framework Components: What’s The Difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/web-components-vs-framework-components/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/03/web-components-vs-framework-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-03-17T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some critics question the agnostic nature of Web Components, with some even arguing that they are not real components. Gabriel Shoyomboa explores this topic in-depth, comparing Web Components and framework components, highlighting their strengths and trade-offs, and evaluating their performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gabriel Shoyombo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>