<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-11-22T00:14:33.245Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Your Python Projects with Poetry]]></title>
        <id>6920d692526d14e1b0e126b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-your-python-projects-with-poetry/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T21:16:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python development looks simple from the outside. But managing real projects is rarely easy. You need to install packages, update them, avoid version conflicts, create virtual environments, and prepare your project for distribution. Many beginners th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Django REST Framework - Build Backend APIs with DRF]]></title>
        <id>6920d5f802099ac646b401c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-django-rest-framework/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T21:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you click on most backend development tutorials, they often teach you what to do, not how to think.That’s why many developers only realize their mistakes after they start building. So, how does one actually think like a backend developer? Before...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sketch: A guided tour of Copenhagen]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390539</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/sketch-a-guided-tour-of-copenhagen/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T18:53:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sketch probably didn't "have" to redesign its UI to line up with macOS Tahoe, but a big part of its appeal is the fact that it feels like it totally belongs to the Mac.
Sketch: A guided tour of Copenhagen originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use NLP Techniques and Tools in Your Projects [Full Handbook]]]></title>
        <id>692096d4afb994c2aecc26e9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-nlp-techniques-and-tools-in-your-projects-full-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T16:44:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, computers can comprehend and produce human-like language thanks to Natural Language Processing. And this opens up numerous opportunities for you as a developer. This guide will teach you how to create NLP projects from scratch. It includes ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Oleh Romanyuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When NOT to use AI in your hackathon project with MLH winners Cindy Cui and Alison Co [Podcast #198]]]></title>
        <id>69207ea2005b143f71163cb0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/when-not-to-use-ai-in-your-hackathon-project-with-mlh-winners-cindy-cui-and-alison-co-podcast-198/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Quincy Larson interviews Alison Co and Cindy Cui, two university students who won the NW Hacks hackathon with their tool that helps people who are losing their vision learn to read Braille. He met them when GitHub invited them to their big San ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Keyframes Tokens: Standardizing Animation Across Projects]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/keyframes-tokens-standardizing-animation-across-projects/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/keyframes-tokens-standardizing-animation-across-projects/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Animations can be one of the most joyful parts of building interfaces, but without structure, they can also become one of the biggest sources of frustration. By consolidating and standardizing keyframes, you take something that is usually messy and hard to manage and turn it into a clear, predictable system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Amit Sheen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should We Even Have :closed?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390115</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/should-we-even-have-closed/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-20T15:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is there really a difference between using :not(:open) and :closed? As always, it depends. Sunkanmi Fafowora explains why :closed is currently not a thing.
Should We Even Have :closed? originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI is Transforming Enterprise Operations]]></title>
        <id>691e0d7802a17c33f13c6a0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-ai-is-transforming-enterprise-operations/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-19T18:33:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is changing how big companies work every single day. What used to take hours of manual effort or long approval chains can now happen in seconds with AI-powered systems.  From supply chains to IT operations, AI is helping enter...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Game Developer’s Guide to Understanding Screen Resolution]]></title>
        <id>691de96a0dec4f292a0f8ff0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-game-developers-guide-to-understanding-screen-resolution/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-19T15:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every game developer obsesses over performance, textures, and frame rates, but resolution is the quiet foundation that makes or breaks visual quality.  Whether you are building a pixel-art indie game or a high-fidelity 3D world, understanding how res...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a Cute Room Portfolio with Three.js, Blender, JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>691db3b57953797388329ea6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-cute-room-portfolio-with-threejs-blender-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-19T12:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use Three.js and Blender to design a stunning and interactive 3D portfolio! We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will take you from the foundational concepts of 3D modeling in Blender to creating a fully f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use to Docker with Node.js: A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>691cf09fea147a95b92d3551</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-to-docker-with-nodejs-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-18T22:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, you’ll learn what Docker is, why it’s become an essential, must-have skill for backend and full-stack developers in 2025, and most importantly, how to use it in real-world projects from start to finish. We will go far beyond the usu...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>oghenekparobo Stephen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Compress Your Prompts and Reduce LLM Costs]]></title>
        <id>691cc4c083c778add388cc95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-compress-your-prompts-and-reduce-llm-costs/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-18T19:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every developer working with large language models eventually faces the same challenge: prompts keep getting longer, models keep getting slower, and API bills keep getting higher. Whether you’re building a retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) system ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level Up Your JavaScript – Detect Smells & Write Clean Code]]></title>
        <id>691c87f2e14e4f3c7eeb659e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/level-up-your-javascript-detect-smells-and-write-clean-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-18T14:51:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted course on freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to transform messy, hard-to-maintain JavaScript code into clean, readable, and professional-quality code that scales. This course was developed by Tapas Adhikary. He'll...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Chaos To Clarity: Simplifying Server Management With AI And Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/simplifying-server-management-ai-automation/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/simplifying-server-management-ai-automation/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-18T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Server chaos doesn’t have to be the norm. AI-ready infrastructure and automation can bring clarity, performance, and focus back to your web work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mansoor Ahmed Khan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Portfolio Website Using Figma and AI Tools – A Guide for Developers]]></title>
        <id>691b93910ca13a7c59ae7a34</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-portfolio-website-using-figma-and-ai-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-17T21:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since my article on How to Become a Full Stack Developer and Get a Job in 2025 went viral, I’ve received countless DMs, emails, and even WhatsApp messages from readers. People have been asking about everything from learning to code and mastering...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prankur Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Real-Time Web Search to Your LLM Using Tavily]]></title>
        <id>691b909391d8c0f995d8ddc4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-real-time-web-search-to-your-llm-using-tavily/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-17T21:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models are smart. But they are not always well-informed. They can write code, summarize books, and explain complex topics, but they struggle with real-time facts. Their knowledge ends at their training cutoff, which means they can’t te...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Fluid Animations with React Native Reanimated v4]]></title>
        <id>691b3eab5aa173ac953652e2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-fluid-animations-with-react-native-reanimated-v4/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-17T15:26:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reanimated 4 brings Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) animations to React Native while keeping full backward compatibility with its worklet-based API. You can now build 60+ frames-per-second (FPS) animations using familiar web syntax, or drop down to work...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balogun Wahab</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intro to Backend Web Development – Node.js, Express, MongoDB]]></title>
        <id>691b3887dbd8303d75f4137c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/intro-to-backend-web-development-nodejs-express-mongodb/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-17T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Backend development involves building the server-side "brain" of a website that manages user data, authentication, and database communication. We just posted a tutorial on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to construct a ba...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: asin(), acos(), atan() and atan2()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390236</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-most-hated-css-feature-asin-acos-atan-and-atan2/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-17T14:47:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we have a ratio that represents the sine, cosine or tangent of an angle, how can we get the original angle? This is where inverse trigonometric functions come in!
The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: asin(), acos(), atan() and atan2() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Started with PocketBase: Build a Lightweight Backend in Minutes]]></title>
        <id>691770eb5879bafaa784b694</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-get-started-with-pocketbase-build-a-lightweight-backend-in-minutes/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-14T18:11:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a developer looking for a simple, fast, and self-hosted backend, PocketBase might be exactly what you need.  It’s an open-source backend written in Go that lets you set up a complete backend with database, authentication, file storage, and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quiet UI Came and Went, Quiet as a Mouse]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390408</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/quiet-ui-came-and-went-quiet-as-a-mouse/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-14T15:32:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extremely new framework that caught lots of attention will continue as a personal project.
Quiet UI Came and Went, Quiet as a Mouse originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Trimble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Harvard CS50 prof David J. Malan on why you should learn programming slowly [Podcast #197]]]></title>
        <id>69174b1090e746d252948913</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/harvard-cs50-prof-david-j-malan-on-why-you-should-learn-programming-slowly-podcast-197/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-14T15:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. David J. Malan teaches computer science at Harvard. Over the past decade, millions of people have taken his CS50 course both in person and online. He joins us to talk about: Why he still recommends learning the C programming language in 2026 Ho...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Dependency Injection in FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>691740a91f4fa448325a55f9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-dependency-injection-in-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-14T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several languages and frameworks depend on dependency injection—no pun intended. Go, Angular, NestJS, and Python's FastAPI all use it as a core pattern. If you've been working with FastAPI, you've likely encountered dependencies in action. Perhaps yo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nneoma Uche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Gamepad API Visual Debugging With CSS Layers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/css-gamepad-api-visual-debugging-css-layers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/css-gamepad-api-visual-debugging-css-layers/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-14T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging controllers can be a real pain. Here’s a deep dive into how CSS helps clean it up and how to build a reusable visual debugger for your own projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Godstime Aburu)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Pixels to Predictions: How GPUs Started Powering Modern AI]]></title>
        <id>69164b0a612455db63b30bdc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-pixels-to-predictions-how-gpus-started-powering-modern-ai/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T21:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people think of artificial intelligence, they imagine complex models, data centers, and cloud servers.  What most don’t realize is that the real engine behind this AI revolution started in a place few expected: inside the humble gaming PC.  The ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Bluetooth Socket Settings Power Android’s Low Power Island: A Friendly Deep Dive into AOSP’s Hidden Energy Saver]]></title>
        <id>69164aadd6505b750fa4b659</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-bluetooth-socket-settings-power-androids-low-power-island-a-friendly-deep-dive-into-aosps-hidden-energy-saver/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T21:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picture this: you’re sitting in a café with your laptop open, phone on the table, smartwatch buzzing every few minutes, and Bluetooth earbuds playing music. From your perspective, life is peaceful. From your phone’s perspective, it’s juggling a ridic...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Life of Your CPU: Exploring the Low Power Island in Android Bluetooth]]></title>
        <id>69164a5b08d80a5fa5d56f1e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-secret-life-of-your-cpu-exploring-the-low-power-island-in-android-bluetooth/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T21:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If your phone were a person, it would probably be that overachieving friend who cannot sit still. The kind who insists they are relaxing while secretly running errands, replying to messages, and checking the weather at the same time. Inside your Andr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Keep LLM Outputs Predictable Using Pydantic Validation]]></title>
        <id>69164018ac4b066d7018502d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-keep-llm-outputs-predictable-using-pydantic-validation/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T20:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models are powerful, but they can also be unpredictable. They might generate long explanations when you expect a short summary, skip fields in a JSON output, or change the format completely from one request to another. When you’re buil...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is TOON? How Token-Oriented Object Notation Could Change How AI Sees Data]]></title>
        <id>6915f8076f343530b3b31c7b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-toon-how-token-oriented-object-notation-could-change-how-ai-sees-data/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T15:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON, or JavaScript Object Notation, was popularized by Douglas Crockford in early 2000. Since then, there’s been no looking back. JSON has become the standardized data exchange format between client and server technologies. JSON was built for humans...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tapas Adhikary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[System Design Patterns in Android Bluetooth [Full Handbook]]]></title>
        <id>6915f7d8453f11c904fade0c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/system-design-patterns-in-android-bluetooth-full-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T15:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve ever opened the Android Bluetooth source code, you might know this feeling. You go in with the calm confidence of a developer who just wants to understand how things work. You open BluetoothAdapter.java and think, “Ah, this looks clean.” Th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Solve 5 Common RAG Failures with Knowledge Graphs]]></title>
        <id>6915f73887b014aa0a104567</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-solve-5-common-rag-failures-with-knowledge-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T15:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have built a Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) pipeline to connect a vector store to a powerful LLM. And RAG pipelines are incredibly effective at grounding models in factual, up-to-date knowledge. But if you've worked with them long enoug...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kamal Kishore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Range Syntax Has Come to Container Style Queries and if()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390178</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-range-syntax-has-come-to-container-style-queries-and-if/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to use the range syntax with container style queries — which we can do starting with Chrome 142 — means that we can compare literal numeric values as well as numeric values tokenized by custom properties or the attr() function.
The Range Syntax Has Come to Container Style Queries and if() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Discrete Mathematics]]></title>
        <id>6915ec909bbfb50f5a356a15</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-discrete-mathematics/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T14:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discrete mathematics plays a key role in machine learning and algorithms. You can use it to find the shortest path (graph theory), encrypt files, compress data, and to do many other things. We just posted a discreet mathematics course on the freeCode...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Complex Workflows with n8n & Master AI Integration]]></title>
        <id>6915ea7e997289c5d5272773</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-complex-workflows-with-n8n-and-master-ai-integration/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T14:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[n8n is an open-source workflow automation platform that lets you connect different apps, APIs, and services to easily automate tasks without needing to implement extensive code. We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that is ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Older Tech In The Browser Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/older-tech-browser-stack/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/older-tech-browser-stack/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-13T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many existing web features and technologies in the wild that you may never touch directly in your day-to-day work. Perhaps you’re fairly new to web development and are simply unaware of them because you’re steeped in the abstraction of a specific framework that doesn’t require you to know it deeply, or even at all. Bryan Rasmussen looks specifically at XPath and demonstrates how it can be used alongside CSS to query elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Bryan Rasmussen)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Integrate Vector Search in Columnar Storage]]></title>
        <id>6914ff68e1ffda5f6ea6d8ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-integrate-vector-search-in-columnar-storage/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-12T21:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating vector search into traditional data platforms is becoming a common task in the current AI-driven landscape. When Google announced general availability for vector search in BigQuery in early 2024, it joined a growing list of established da...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chirag Agrawal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Effectively Monitoring Web Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/effectively-monitoring-web-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/effectively-monitoring-web-performance/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of tips for [improving your website performance](https://www.debugbear.com/blog/improve-website-performance?utm_campaign=sm-10). But even if you follow all of the advice, are you able to maintain an optimized site? And are you targeting the right pages? Matt Zeunert outlines an effective strategy for web performance optimization and explains the roles that different types of data play in it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Matt Zeunert)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Run an Open-Source LLM on Your Personal Computer – Run Ollama Locally]]></title>
        <id>691256ca726af9fcf5543027</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-run-an-open-source-llm-on-your-personal-computer-run-ollama-locally/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-10T21:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running a large language model (LLM) on your computer is now easier than ever. You no longer need a cloud subscription or a massive server. With just your PC, you can run models like Llama, Mistral, or Phi, privately and offline. This guide will show...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js – JavaScript Framework Course]]></title>
        <id>691228d49872f01b424e3353</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-javascript-framework-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-10T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vue.js is a progressive JavaScript framework for building user interfaces and single-page applications. Loved for its simplicity, flexibility, and performance, it allows developers to start small and scale up to complex applications with ease. Whethe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Headings: Semantics, Fluidity, and Styling — Oh My!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389885</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/headings-semantics-fluidity-and-styling-oh-my/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-10T14:44:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few links about headings that I've had stored under my top hat.
Headings: Semantics, Fluidity, and Styling — Oh My! originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VPNs vs Proxies: What are the Differences?]]></title>
        <id>690e629981a4964f4b12b422</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vpns-vs-proxies-what-are-the-differences/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T21:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the age of online privacy, two tools are often mentioned together: VPNs and proxies. Both hide your IP address and help you browse the internet more privately, but they work in different ways and serve different purposes. From simple security to w...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of Bluetooth in 2025: What’s New, What’s Possible, and How to Use It]]></title>
        <id>690e2801500cb51e735b5a9c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-state-of-bluetooth-whats-new-whats-possible-and-how-to-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T17:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction: Why Bluetooth Still Matters You probably don’t even think about Bluetooth anymore. It’s just there, quietly doing its job every single day. It’s what keeps your earbuds connected, your smartwatch synced, your car infotainment system tal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikheel Vishwas Savant</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose the Right LLM for Your Projects: A Guide to Effective Model Benchmarking]]></title>
        <id>690e27b0ca4947acbefbd755</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/choose-the-right-llm-for-your-projects-benchmarking-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T17:09:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you start building with LLMs, it quickly becomes clear that not all models behave the same. One model may excel at creative writing but struggle with technical precision. Another might be thoughtful yet verbose. A third could be fast and efficie...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surya Teja Appini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Built a Makaton AI Companion Using Gemini Nano and the Gemini API]]></title>
        <id>690e1f43cb50ea9684f6d9aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-built-a-makaton-ai-companion-using-gemini-nano-and-the-gemini-api/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T16:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I started my research on AI systems that could translate Makaton (a sign and symbol language designed to support speech and communication), I wanted to bridge a gap in accessibility for learners with speech or language difficulties. Over time, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>OMOTAYO OMOYEMI</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying into the void with recruiter admin Abbey Perini [Podcast #196]]]></title>
        <id>690e0d2661d96baa3c583c80</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/applying-into-the-void-with-recruiter-admin-abbey-perini-podcast-196/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T15:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abbey Perini taught herself programming at age 27 while working as an admin at an engineering recruitment agency. She has worked extensively with large legacy codebases and taught best practices to developers internationally. We talk about: How to h...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Animations Part 6: Magnificent SVGs With `<use>` And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/smashing-animations-part-6-svgs-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/smashing-animations-part-6-svgs-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG is one of those web technologies that’s both elegant and, at times, infuriating. In this article, pioneering author and web designer Andy Clarke explains his technique for animating SVG elements that are hidden in the Shadow DOM.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Structure Your README File – README Template Example]]></title>
        <id>690e02f392fcbf371b6e1b9d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-structure-your-readme-file/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-07T14:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a developer who aspires to be a founder, building your first startup can be filled with excitement and ideas. The worst thing that could happen to you is jumping straight into the coding part. I was in this situation and the last thing on my mind ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Casmir Onyekani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guitar Theory Course for Beginners – Learn Fretboard, Major Scale and Triads]]></title>
        <id>690ce6ccd9dcaa769b671c7e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/guitar-theory-course-for-beginners-learn-fretboard-major-scale-and-triads/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-06T18:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to play the guitar! We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you essential guitar theory including the fretboard, the major scale and the triads. It was created by baritone guitarist, Alex Gordon Hi-Fi. He...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explaining the Accessible Benefits of Using Semantic HTML Elements]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=385769</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/explaining-the-accessible-benefits-of-using-semantic-html-elements/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-06T15:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why should you use a semantic <button> instead of a generic <div>? Accessibility, right? By how exactly does it help accessibility?
Explaining the Accessible Benefits of Using Semantic HTML Elements originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Round Trip Time (RTT) with Next.js]]></title>
        <id>690c78446959d1f714d81d45</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-round-trip-time-rtt-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-06T10:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered why some websites load almost immediately and others leave you looking at a blank screen, even when your internet connection is fast? In some cases, your internet speed may not be the issue. It is usually because of Round Trip ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chukwudi Nweze</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptography for Beginners: Full Python Course (SHA-256, AES, RSA, Passwords)]]></title>
        <id>690bd280e9ceb53e15668053</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/cryptography-for-beginners-full-python-course-sha-256-aes-rsa-passwords/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T22:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about cryptography. You'll learn essential techniques like hashing (SHA-256) for verifying file integrity, symmetric encryption (AES), and asymmetric encryption (...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creative Web Development with Three.js and Blender]]></title>
        <id>690bd1964ffa7599421226c5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/creative-web-development-with-threejs-and-blender/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T22:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Creative Web Development with Three.js and Blender. freeCodeCamp just posted a beginner-friendly course that will teach you to create an immersive 3D portfolio. You'll begin by diving into Blender to learn the fundamentals of 3D modeling. With ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own Private Voice Assistant: A Step-by-Step Guide Using Open-Source Tools]]></title>
        <id>690bcbbc8abe1e0a5b05e0be</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/private-voice-assistant-using-open-source-tools/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T22:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most commercial voice assistants send your voice data to cloud servers before responding. By using open‑source tools, you can run everything directly on your phone for better privacy, faster responses, and full control over how the assistant behaves....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Surya Teja Appini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use LangChain and LangGraph: A Beginner’s Guide to AI Workflows]]></title>
        <id>690b882e468be723832787a7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-langchain-and-langgraph-a-beginners-guide-to-ai-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T17:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is moving fast. Every week, new tools appear that make it easier to build apps powered by large language models. But many beginners still get stuck on one question: how do you structure the logic of an AI application? How do y...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event-Based Architectures in JavaScript: A Handbook for Devs]]></title>
        <id>690b87a7da01ae579df92085</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/event-based-architectures-in-javascript-a-handbook-for-devs/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T17:21:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In modern software development, event-driven architectures have become one of the most powerful ways to build scalable, decoupled, and responsive systems. Instead of relying on direct calls between components, event-driven systems communicate through...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>German Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Global Execution Context and Temporal Dead Zone Work in JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>690b5691972e7bfdc1ed09c1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/global-execution-context-and-temporal-dead-zone-explained/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T13:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered how JavaScript runs your code behind the scenes, and how the Global Execution Context actually works? How does hoisting work for var, let, and const? Consider the code bellow: console.log('My age is', age) console.log('My name ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shejan Mahamud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Practical Guide To UX Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/practical-guide-ux-strategy/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/practical-guide-ux-strategy/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s dive into the building blocks of UX strategy and see how it speaks the language of product and business strategy to create user value while achieving company goals. Part of the Measure UX & Design Impact (use the code 🎟 IMPACT to save 20% off today).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How __proto__, prototype, and Inheritance Actually Work in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>690a2d839d070c31fadbc25e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-proto-prototype-and-inheritance-actually-work-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-04T16:44:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered why everything in JavaScript acts like an object? Or how inheritance actually works behind the scenes? What's the difference between __proto__ and prototype? If these questions have crossed your mind, you're not alone. These ar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shejan Mahamud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Leverage Component Variants In Penpot]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/how-leverage-component-variants-penpot/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/11/how-leverage-component-variants-penpot/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With component variants, design systems become more flexible, letting you reuse the same component while adapting its look or state with ease. In this article, Daniel Schwarz demonstrates how design tokens can be leveraged to manage components and their variations using Penpot, the open-source tool built for scalable, consistent design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Schwarz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Cybersecurity Certifications to Boost Your Career]]></title>
        <id>690933925fbdca38da0ea33b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/top-cybersecurity-certifications-to-boost-your-career/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-03T22:58:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity is one of the fastest-growing fields in the world today.  Every year, more companies face threats that put their data, reputation, and customer trust at risk. As these threats grow, so does the demand for skilled cybersecurity professio...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: tan()]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389842</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-most-hated-css-feature-tan/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-03T16:03:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last time, we discussed that, sadly, according to the State of CSS 2025 survey, trigonometric functions are deemed the “Most Hated” CSS feature.
That shocked me. I may have even been a little offended, being a math nerd and …
The “Most Hated” CSS Feature: tan() originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Automation with n8n]]></title>
        <id>6908c9fe147981c65916a40b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-automation-with-n8n/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-03T15:27:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Automation has become one of the most valuable skills for any technical team. It helps eliminate repetitive work, speeds up business operations, and lets you focus on creative or strategic tasks.  Whether it’s moving data between apps, triggering act...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Python Packages with uv]]></title>
        <id>69089c3b30ea29f0efb3f4fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-python-packages-with-uv/"/>
        <updated>2025-11-03T12:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python package managers let you install and manage dependencies—like NumPy, pandas, and so on—right from your terminal. In this article, you will learn how to use uv—an extremely fast Python package manager. Prerequisites To get the most out of this ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hew Hahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fading Light And Falling Leaves (November 2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/10/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-november-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-31T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new month is just around the corner, and that means: It’s time for some new desktop wallpapers! All of them are designed by the community for the community and can be downloaded for free. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Cybersecurity from Harvard University]]></title>
        <id>69039b943b42750686df8138</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-cybersecurity-from-harvard-university/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T17:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a Harvard University course that will provide you an introduction to cybersecurity. It's taught by one of the world's most-loved computer science teachers, Dr. David J. Malan. In this course you will learn how to secure your accounts, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Overcome a Negative Performance Review and Become a Better Developer]]></title>
        <id>69038e8be43cf9a3614ff2fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/clawing-out-of-underperformance/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T16:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was a year into my new job at Google. After repeated warnings about underperformance, my manager sat me down. I was being placed on a Performance Improvement Plan (PIP). For those unfamiliar, a PIP at Google is a two-month plan to show improvement ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Moshe Siegel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Own MCP Server with Python]]></title>
        <id>69038e6549c53ba349744d5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-own-mcp-server-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T16:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is evolving at a remarkable pace. Models today can reason, write, code, and analyze information in ways that once seemed impossible. But there’s one major limitation that still holds them back: context. Most AI models don’t ha...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Programming Skills by Building Games]]></title>
        <id>690364c01022fd77927ddcbd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-your-programming-skills-by-building-games/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T13:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When most people think about learning to code, they imagine building websites or automating small tasks. Few think of building games as a serious way to improve programming skills.  But creating even a simple game can teach lessons that no tutorial e...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile App Development with Dart and Flutter]]></title>
        <id>6902ba897614003427892ef9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mobile-app-development-with-dart-and-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-30T01:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile app development lets you build applications that run on multiple platforms. Flutter is Google's UI toolkit for building applications for mobile, web, and desktop from a single codebase. Flutter apps are written in Dart, a statically typed, obj...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Streams in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>69028db72c8d547cd3a4cb95</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-streams-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T21:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flutter, Google's open-source UI software development toolkit, has rapidly become a preferred choice for building natively compiled, cross-platform applications from a single codebase. Its declarative UI paradigm, coupled with robust performance, hel...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Parse JSON in Python – A Complete Guide With Examples]]></title>
        <id>69028d2168ede4f821f8f0e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-parse-json-in-python-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T21:54:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JSON has become the standard format for data exchange on the web. So you'll run into JSON all the time when working with REST APIs, configuration files, database exports, and more. As a developer, you should know how to parse, manipulate, and generat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCP vs APIs: What's the Real Difference?]]></title>
        <id>69028c7be37f0cfba4d00775</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/mcp-vs-apis-whats-the-real-difference/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T21:51:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs and MCPs both help systems talk to each other.  At first, they might look the same. Both allow one piece of software to ask another for data or perform an action. But the way they work and the reason they exist are completely different. An API, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Website Screenshot Generator with Python and Flask]]></title>
        <id>690245c804c1e198e965b3ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-website-screenshot-generator-with-python-and-flask/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T16:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever needed to take screenshots of websites automatically – maybe to track visual changes, include them in reports, or generate previews? Doing this manually can be time-consuming, especially if you need to capture multiple pages regularly. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Creative With Small Screens]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=390031</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-creative-with-small-screens/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T16:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On mobile, people can lose their sense of context and can’t easily tell where a section begins or ends. Good small-screen design can help orient them using a variety of techniques.
Getting Creative With Small Screens originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Serverless and Microservices with C# & Azure]]></title>
        <id>69023c73147abcc15caef5c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/serverless-and-microservices-with-c-and-azure/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T16:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can modern application architecture by building real-world serverless and microservices solutions using C# and Azure. We just posted a full course on the freeCodeCamp that will teach you to build scaleable cloud applications. Muhammad Abdullah de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare for the Kubernetes Administrator Certification and Pass]]></title>
        <id>6902148987da12fd1cbfa416</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/prepare-for-the-kubernetes-administrator-certification-and-pass/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-29T13:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We just posted a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel to help prepare you for the Certified Kubernetes Administrator Certification. This course is designed to provide a deep, practical understanding of Kubernetes administration, from founda...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Assets in Flutter using  flutter_gen]]></title>
        <id>69012bf59b2c5393aed5bccd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-assets-in-flutter-using-fluttergen/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-28T20:47:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing assets like images, icons, and fonts in a Flutter project can quickly become a tedious task, especially as your application grows. Manual referencing is prone to typos, introduces maintenance overhead, and can hinder team collaboration. Fort...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Responsive UIs in Flutter]]></title>
        <id>690108bed60a2bc774c2f435</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-responsive-uis-in-flutter/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-28T18:17:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building responsive UIs in Flutter can be challenging, especially when you want your app to look great on phones, tablets, and desktops without maintaining multiple layouts. Fortunately, Flutter provides powerful tools like MediaQuery, LayoutBuilder,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Chrome Extension That Analyzes Any Web Page Using JavaScript and Manifest V3]]></title>
        <id>6900f612596c2221585d95a4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-chrome-extension-using-javascript-and-manifest-v3/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-28T16:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever visited a website and wondered how well is this page structured? Does it have a meta description? How many links or headings does it use? Usually, you’d open DevTools or an SEO auditing tool to find answers to these questions. But what ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hitesh Chauhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your First Dynamic Performance Test in Apache JMeter]]></title>
        <id>6900f3ca65a053299e38eab3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-your-first-dynamic-performance-test-in-apache-jmeter/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-28T16:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a QA engineer, I have always found performance testing to be one of the most exciting and underrated parts of software testing. Yes, functional testing is important, but it’s of little use if users have to wait for 5 seconds for each page to load....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mah Noor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a CRUD App with TanStack Start and TanStackDB (with RxDB Integration)]]></title>
        <id>68ffdf4bd48b77fcbe0114ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-crud-app-with-tanstack-start-and-tanstackdb-with-rxdb-integration/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T21:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TanStack Start is a new full-stack framework for React. It’s been growing in popularity ever since it reached the Release Candidate stage of its development in September, 2025. The Release Candidate stage is basically a version of software which is c...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Baisden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Secure iOS Apps in Swift: Common Security Pitfalls and How to Fix Them]]></title>
        <id>68ffdf1761d216440f5bb38a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-secure-ios-apps-in-swift-common-security-pitfalls-and-how-to-fix-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T21:07:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These days, there are many ways attackers can try to compromise your applications. And thanks to the continued increase in cyberattacks, the demand for secure mobile applications – and by extension, secure coding – has never been higher. So if you’re...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Closures in Go]]></title>
        <id>68ffd791ca908949cd4f2afc</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-closures-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T20:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've written code in JavaScript, Python, or Rust, you've probably heard the word closure before. The concept has subtle differences in each language, but the core idea is the same: a closure is a function that captures variables from its surroun...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gabor Koos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pure CSS Tabs With Details, Grid, and Subgrid]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389805</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/pure-css-tabs-with-details-grid-and-subgrid/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T14:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Can we use the <details> element as the foundation for a tabbed interface? Why yes, we can!
Pure CSS Tabs With Details, Grid, and Subgrid originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvestar Bistrović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Registry in shadcn]]></title>
        <id>68ff81486f611e7895c9f9ca</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-set-up-a-registry-in-shadcn/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T14:27:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this guide, you’ll learn how to set up a registry in shadcn. If you’re not familiar with this tool, shadcn is a collection of reusable and accessible components you can use in your projects. You’ll learn about essential concepts such as setting up...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhijeet Dave</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript For Everyone: Iterators]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/10/javascript-for-everyone-iterators/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/10/javascript-for-everyone-iterators/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a lesson on Iterators. Iterables implement the iterable iteration interface, and iterators implement the iterator iteration interface. Sounds confusing? Mat breaks it all down in the article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mat Marquis)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Work with TOML Files in Python]]></title>
        <id>68fbd8942f09b776064b952c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-work-with-toml-files-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T19:50:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TOML (Tom's Obvious Minimal Language) has become the modern standard for configuration files in Python projects. It's more expressive than INI files and cleaner than JSON or YAML. Since Python 3.11, the standard library includes the tomllib module fo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bala Priya C</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Model Context Protocol Works]]></title>
        <id>68fbd8268c0c93a0a754d14e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-the-model-context-protocol-works/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T19:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of artificial intelligence is moving fast. Every week, it seems like there’s a new tool, framework, or model that promises to make AI better. But as developers build more AI applications, one big problem keeps showing up: the lack of contex...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Model Context Protocol (MCP) with Flutter and Dart]]></title>
        <id>68fbd79c4ea129b1fef69825</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-the-model-context-protocol-mcp-with-flutter-and-dart/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T19:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development is moving fast toward AI-assisted workflows and smarter tooling. Whether it’s your IDE completing code, an AI assistant analyzing your project, or automated testing pipelines, all these tools need a standardized way to communicat...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Multi-Threading in Node.js With Worker Threads [Full Handbook]]]></title>
        <id>68fba9c10656b6400beb0762</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-implement-multi-threading-in-nodejs-with-worker-threads-full-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T16:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript is a single-threaded programming language, and Node.js is the runtime environment for JavaScript. This means that JavaScript essentially runs within Node.js, and all operations are handled through a single thread. But when we perform tasks...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumit Saha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Developer Experience in Microservices Applications with .NET Aspire]]></title>
        <id>68fb8c95d81014dabb030226</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/improve-developer-experience-with-net-aspire/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T14:26:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the advent of microservices, development teams have gained the flexibility to deploy services independently, without coordinating with the entire engineering organization. Bug fixes can be released in isolation without full regression testing, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Opaluwa Emidowojo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Animations That Leverage the Parent-Child Relationship]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=389794</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-animations-that-leverage-the-parent-child-relationship/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T14:18:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we change an element’s intrinsic sizing, its children are affected, too. This is something we can use to our advantage.
CSS Animations That Leverage the Parent-Child Relationship originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First dev job at 45 – Interview with self-taught freeCodeCamp grad Eric Carlson [Podcast #194]]]></title>
        <id>68fb89f65b2841c3f1a026ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/first-dev-job-at-45-interview-with-self-taught-freecodecamp-grad-eric-carlson-podcast-194/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-24T14:15:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Carlson is a self-taught software engineer at Cisco. In his early 20s, he worked his way up to manager at the busiest Dominos Pizza in Canada. He eventually went to college and studied liberal arts, then worked as a teacher for two decades befor...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do AI Agents Work?]]></title>
        <id>68fa5f0711038bf3130f454d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-do-ai-agents-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-10-23T16:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people talk about AI agents, they often imagine something futuristic that can think, talk, and make decisions.  But the truth is, AI agents are already here. And they are working quietly in the background. They answer customer questions, schedul...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>