<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2025-06-16T00:16:06.678Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://ishikawa3.github.io/rss/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The NestJS Handbook – Learn to Use Nest with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>684c867db87f779c97f2e509</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-nestjs-handbook-learn-to-use-nest-with-code-examples/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T20:13:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NestJS is a progressive Node.js framework for building efficient, reliable, and scalable server-side applications. Combining the best ideas from OOP (Object-Oriented Programming), FP (Functional Programming), and FRP (Functional Reactive Programming)...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>German Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Medical Chatbot with Flutter and Gemini: A Beginner’s Guide]]></title>
        <id>684c61db3b494a20ba49fddb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-medical-chatbot-with-flutter-and-gemini/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T17:37:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, the demand for accessible and accurate health information is higher than ever. Leveraging the power of artificial intelligence, we can create intelligent chatbots that provide reliable health-related guidance. This beginner's ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Vue Composables Work – Explained with Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>684c58453ee20021234073af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-vue-composables-work/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vue composables are a very helpful tool when developing Vue applications. They give developers an easy way to reuse logic across our applications. In addition to allowing for “stateless” logic (things like formatting or routine calculations), composa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Barrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve Your Phone’s Privacy]]></title>
        <id>684c50b9c6ec6bf605276b54</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-your-phones-privacy/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-13T16:24:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We use our phones for everything  –  texting, banking, browsing, tracking our health, even unlocking our homes. But with all that convenience comes a lot of risk. Apps are hungry for your data. Hackers are always looking for cracks in your security. ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn MLOps by Creating a YouTube Sentiment Analyzer]]></title>
        <id>684b07b568649c5d5e8565b2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-mlops-by-creating-a-youtube-sentiment-analyzer/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T17:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re serious about machine learning and want to break into real-world ML engineering, learning MLOps is one of the best things you can do. It’s what turns experiments into reliable systems. You can train a great model, but without the right pipe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Boundaries: Building a Tangram Puzzle With (S)CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386648</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/breaking-boundaries-building-a-tangram-puzzle-with-scss/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-12T13:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We put it to the test and it turns out Sass can replace JavaScript, at least when it comes to low-level logic and puzzle behavior. With nothing but maps, mixins, functions, and a whole lot of math, we managed to bring our Tangram puzzle to life, no JavaScript required.
Breaking Boundaries: Building a Tangram Puzzle With (S)CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sladjana Stojanovic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Steal Data from Websites (And How to Stop Them)]]></title>
        <id>6849e4d1a3aec42347669919</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-steal-data-from-websites-and-how-to-stop-them/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T20:19:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across platforms, behind every app, and on your own website, hackers may patiently wait.  These days, everyone should have identity theft protections, and be informed about data threats lurking in the trenches of the world-wide-web’s war on privacy a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Tray</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating The &ldquo;Moving Highlight&rdquo; Navigation Bar With JavaScript And CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/creating-moving-highlight-navigation-bar-javascript-css/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/creating-moving-highlight-navigation-bar-javascript-css/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, Blake Lundquist walks us through two methods of creating the “moving-highlight” navigation pattern using only plain JavaScript and CSS. The first technique uses the `getBoundingClientRect` method to explicitly animate the border between navigation bar items when they are clicked. The second approach achieves the same functionality using the new View Transition API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Blake Lundquist)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Information About Your Linux System Through the Command Line]]></title>
        <id>68495738cb7b75f7a33a73c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-linux-system-info-through-cli/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-11T10:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you’ve just gained access to a new Linux system, ethically hacked into one as part of a security test, or you’re just curious to know more about your current machine, this article will guide you through the process. You’ll learn how you can g...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Apple Code Signing Handbook]]></title>
        <id>68489084490c709f6b3070ed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/apple-code-signing-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T20:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this handbook, I’ll demystify the Apple app code signing process. Apple's ecosystem is powerful, but its distribution mechanisms – with various identifiers, certificates, and profiles – can appear complex. This guide attempts to make that journey ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sravan Karuturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Deploy To Vercel With GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>684871b16bc1898625c952fd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-to-vercel-with-github-actions/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T17:56:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vercel is a cloud platform or Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) designed to help frontend developers create, preview, and deploy web applications swiftly and efficiently. In this tutorial, we’ll focus on deploying a Next.js application to Vercel using Git...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the MERN Stack in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68483a699e226a329abe4dee</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-the-mern-stack-in-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-10T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to learn full-stack web development but don’t know where to start, this new course is a solid way in. Whether you're aiming to get a job in web dev or just want to build your own projects, understanding how the pieces fit toget...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an Auto-Closing Notification With an HTML Popover]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386694</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-an-auto-closing-notification-with-an-html-popover/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T12:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The HTML popover attribute transforms elements into top-layer elements that can be opened and closed with a button or JavaScript.  Popovers can be dismissed a number of ways, but there is no option to auto-close them. Preethi has a technique you can use.
Creating an Auto-Closing Notification With an HTML Popover originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoding The SVG <code>path</code> Element: Line Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/decoding-svg-path-element-line-commands/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/decoding-svg-path-element-line-commands/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-09T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG is easy — until you meet `path`. However, it’s not as confusing as it initially looks. In this first installment of a pair of articles, Myriam Frisano aims to teach you the basics of `
` and its sometimes mystifying commands. With simple examples and visualizations, she’ll help you understand the easy syntax and underlying rules of SVG’s most powerful element so that by the end, you’re fully able to translate SVG semantic tags into a language `path` understands.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Myriam Frisano)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 3: Curves]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386876</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-css-shapes-using-shape-part-3-curves/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T13:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third article in a series about the CSS shape() function. We've covered drawing lines and arcs in previous articles and, this time, we look specifically at the curve command and how to use it for drawing complex shapes.
Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 3: Curves originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From electrical engineering student to CTO with Hitesh Choudhary [Podcast #175]]]></title>
        <id>6842e00169a5099a551058ce</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-electrical-engineering-student-to-cto-with-hitesh-choudhary-podcast-175/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T12:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews former CTO and prolific programming teacher Hitesh Choudhary.   We talk about: The limits of AI in building a robust codebase Time management Higher Education in ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Protect Your Remote Workforce from Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>6842cf8a6fcd9b03c19d04ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/protect-remote-workforce-from-cyber-attacks/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T11:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working remotely gives your team flexibility, but it also opens the door to cyber threats. Remote workers are more exposed without the protection of office firewalls and on-site IT teams.  Hackers know that people often use weak passwords, forget to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce Technical Debt in the Power Platform]]></title>
        <id>6842c4f3e7fdc9878ba5dadd</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-reduce-technical-debt-in-the-power-platform/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:37:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical debt refers to the future cost – measured in terms of time, money, effort, or opportunity – of choosing expedient solutions today instead of more deliberate and scalable ones. And it's not just a pro-code concept. It might be easier to unde...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Micro-Frontend Architecture Handbook]]></title>
        <id>6842c120a3469a9ca728862b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/complete-micro-frontends-guide/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-06T10:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, in my role as a lead full-stack developer, solutions architect, and mentor, I’ve been immersed in the world of micro frontend architecture, working across different large-scale frontend projects where multiple teams, stacks, and deplo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Maksimchenko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenFeign vs WebClient: How to Choose a REST Client for Your Spring Boot Project]]></title>
        <id>6841f2c63a801418642db429</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-choice-openfeign-or-webclient/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building microservices with Spring Boot, you’ll have to decide how the services will communicate with one another. The basic choices in terms of protocols are Messaging and REST. In this article we’ll discuss tools based on REST, which is a comm...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Casari</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Commit to Production: Hands-On GitOps Promotion with GitHub Actions, Argo CD, Helm, and Kargo]]></title>
        <id>6841f1319c94d5fa67dae6e3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/from-commit-to-production-hands-on-gitops-promotion-with-github-actions-argo-cd-helm-and-kargo/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T19:34:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to go beyond ‘hello world’ and build a real, production-style CI/CD pipeline – starting from scratch? Let’s pause for a moment: what are you trying to learn from your DevOps journey? Are you focusing on GitOps-style deployments, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitheesh Poojary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring the CSS contrast-color() Function… a Second Time]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386829</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/exploring-the-css-contrast-color-function-a-second-time/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T13:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The contrast-color() function doesn’t check color contrast, but rather it outright resolves to either black or white (whichever one contrasts the most with your chosen color). Safari Technology Preview recently implemented it and we explore its possible uses in this article.
Exploring the CSS contrast-color() Function… a Second Time originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of CSS 2025 Survey is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=387046</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-state-of-css-2025-survey-is-out/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T11:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The State of CSS 2025 Survey dropped a few days ago, and besides anticipating the results, it's exciting to see a lot of the new things shipped to CSS reflected in the questions.
The State of CSS 2025 Survey is out! originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Collaboration: The Most Underrated UX Skill No One Talks About]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/collaboration-most-underrated-ux-skill/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/collaboration-most-underrated-ux-skill/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-05T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often spotlight wireframes, research, or tools like Figma, but none of that moves the needle if we can’t collaborate well. Great UX doesn’t happen in isolation. It takes conversations with engineers, alignment with product, sales, and other stakeholders, and the ability to listen, adapt, and co-create. That’s where design becomes a team sport, and when your ability to capture the outcomes multiplies the UX impact.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Carrie Webster)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C Game Development with Raylib]]></title>
        <id>68408c368ab45ab43dad48c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/c-game-development-with-raylib/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T18:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making games is one of the best ways to learn programming. It pushes you to think logically, stay organized, and solve real problems. Plus, it’s just fun. If you're looking to improve your C programming skills and learn how to create a complete game ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Godot – Course for Beginners in Spanish]]></title>
        <id>68402e7af9ce257b34574bed</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-godot-course-for-beginners-in-spanish/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T11:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Godot is an open-source, lightweight, and powerful game engine. This course will teach you how to use it to bring your game ideas to life. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org Spanish YouTube channel that will guide you step by step thr...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Estefania Cassingena Navone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Animations Part 4: Optimising SVGs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/smashing-animations-part-4-optimising-svgs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/smashing-animations-part-4-optimising-svgs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the best way to make your SVGs faster, simpler, and more manageable? In this article, pioneering author and web designer Andy Clarke explains the process he relies on *to* prepare, optimise, and structure SVGs for animation and beyond.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[General Chemistry College Course]]></title>
        <id>683f922e111e5ab9c8a4e188</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/general-chemistry-college-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-04T00:24:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning general chemistry is one of the most important steps you can take if you're planning to study science in any serious way. Chemistry is foundational. It connects to biology, physics, environmental science, engineering, medicine, and so much m...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Creative With HTML Dialog]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386750</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-creative-with-html-dialog/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, how can you take dialogue box design beyond the generic look of frameworks and templates? How can you style them to reflect a brand’s visual identity and help to tell its stories? Here’s how I do it in CSS using ::backdrop, backdrop-filter, and animations.
Getting Creative With HTML Dialog originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source LLM Agent Handbook: How to Automate Complex Tasks with LangGraph and CrewAI]]></title>
        <id>683f04aedfb685791a4e8dd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-open-source-llm-agent-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever feel like your AI tools are a bit...well, passive? Like they just sit there, waiting for your next command? Imagine if they could take initiative, break down big problems, and even work together to get things done. That's exactly what LLM agents...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Designers Get Stuck In The Details And How To Stop]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/why-designers-get-stuck-in-details/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/why-designers-get-stuck-in-details/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designers love to craft, but polishing pixels before the problem is solved is a time-sink. This article pinpoints the five traps that lure us into premature detail — being afraid to show rough work, fixing symptoms instead of causes, solving the wrong problem, drowning in unactionable feedback, and plain fatigue — then hands you a four-step rescue plan to refocus on goals, ship faster, and keep your craft where it counts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nikita Samutin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Front-End Monitoring Handbook: Track Performance, Errors, and User Behavior]]></title>
        <id>683e5606b7c8b1ebd3a32964</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-front-end-monitoring-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-03T01:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A complete frontend monitoring system is essential for tracking application performance, errors, and user behavior. It consists of three main components: data collection and reporting, data processing and storage, and data visualization. This article...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gordan Tan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Public Wi-Fi Is Dangerous – And How to Protect Yourself]]></title>
        <id>683deb300e5fd6529479c483</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-public-wi-fi-is-dangerous-and-how-to-protect-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free Wi-Fi feels like a small win when you’re out. Coffee shops, airports, and hotels offer it like candy  –  just tap, connect, and you’re online.  But behind that convenience is a world of risk that most people never see coming. Let’s talk about wh...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Code Linked Lists with TypeScript: A Handbook for Developers]]></title>
        <id>683dea64b88211830493d3aa</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-code-linked-lists-with-typescript-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T18:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A linked list is a data structure where each item, called a node, contains data and a pointer to the next node. Unlike arrays, which store elements in contiguous memory, linked lists connect nodes that can be scattered across memory. In this hands-on...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yazdun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Beginner’s Guide to Graphs — From Google Maps to Chessboards]]></title>
        <id>683dc829f7d4772789f06d02</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/a-beginners-guide-to-graphs/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T15:50:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us use Google Maps without thinking twice. You open the app, check which route has the least traffic, and hit start. Then somewhere along the way – maybe you miss a turn (I do that often) – and Maps calmly recalculates your route, showing you...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing For Neurodiversity]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/designing-for-neurodiversity/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/06/designing-for-neurodiversity/"/>
        <updated>2025-06-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designing for neurodiversity means recognizing that people aren’t edge cases but individuals with varied ways of thinking and navigating the web. So, how can we create more inclusive experiences that work better for everyone?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prelude To Summer (June 2025 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-june-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s kick off June — and the beginning of summer — with some fresh inspiration! Artists and designers from across the globe once again tickled their creativity to welcome the new month with a new collection of desktop wallpapers. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Build a Multilayer Perceptron with Real-Life Examples and Python Code]]></title>
        <id>6839f729798ea464918cffe8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-multilayer-perceptron-with-examples-and-python-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T18:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The perceptron is a fundamental concept in deep learning, with many algorithms stemming from its original design. In this tutorial, I’ll show you how to build both single layer and multi-layer perceptrons (MLPs) across three frameworks: Custom class...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kuriko Iwai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Microfrontends Work: From iframes to Module Federation]]></title>
        <id>6839c4a906e067fe415d54b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-microfrontends-work-iframes-to-module-federation/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microfrontends are transforming how teams build and deploy frontend applications at scale. This tutorial explores the architectural landscape, from traditional approaches to modern Module Federation implementations. By the end, you'll be equipped to ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rahul gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Simple Portfolio Blog With Next.js]]></title>
        <id>6839c439ebab1f7974eac355</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-simple-portfolio-blog-with-nextjs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have written articles on different platforms including LinkedIn, The Network Bits (Substack), and freeCodeCamp. So I wanted to bring all of these articles together in a single place where someone could go and see all my work. A blog sounded like a ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chidiadi Anyanwu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 2: More on Arcs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386673</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-css-shapes-using-shape-part-2-more-on-arcs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second part of a series that dives deep into the CSS shape() command, continuing with a more detailed look at the arc command.
Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 2: More on Arcs originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Sort Dates Efficiently in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6839b592f8650e337982bcba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-sort-dates-efficiently-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:41:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently, I was working on a PowerApps Component Framework (PCF) project that required sorting an array of objects by date. The dates were in ISO 8601 format but without a time zone – for example, "2025-05-01T15:00:00.00". Without much thought, I wro...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Survive in Tech When Everything's Changing w/ 21-year Veteran Dev Joe Attardi [Podcast #174]]]></title>
        <id>6839abf3d23bb1460e9ea0ea</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-survive-in-tech-when-everythings-changing-w-21-year-veteran-dev-joe-attardi-podcast-174/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-30T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews Joe Attardi. He's a software engineer and prolific author of programming books. We talk about: How software development has changed over the past 21 years Tips for s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LeetCode Meditations: A Visualized Tour of DSA Concepts (A Handbook)]]></title>
        <id>6838baed0c839b0170a2e731</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/leetcode-dsa-concepts-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T19:52:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may seem like an oxymoron when the words "LeetCode" and "meditation" are used together – after all, one thing that almost everyone can agree is that LeetCode is challenging. It's called grinding LeetCode for a reason. It doesn't have anything to d...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eda Eren</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Python for Data Science – Full Course for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>6838a96337f76032ee644b85</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-python-for-data-science-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T18:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data science has become one of the most sought-after skills in today's technology-driven world. Whether you're looking to advance your career, make data-driven decisions, or simply understand the patterns hidden in everyday information, Python offers...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build an AI-Powered Cooking Assistant with Flutter and Gemini]]></title>
        <id>68388c4c973615b7f6864e63</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-an-ai-powered-cooking-assistant-with-flutter-and-gemini/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-29T16:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After soaking in everything shared at GoogleIO, I can’t lie – I feel supercharged! From What’s New in Flutter to Building Agentic Apps with Flutter and Firebase AI Logic, and the deep dive into How Flutter Makes the Most of Your Platforms, it felt li...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Atuoha Anthony</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Target Travelers – and How to Defend Yourself]]></title>
        <id>68372f981dca8ddfbed5d732</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-attackers-target-travelers-and-how-to-defend-yourself/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T15:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traveling is one of life’s greatest joys  –  but it also puts a big target on your back for cybercriminals. Tourists are often rushed, distracted, or unfamiliar with local providers. That’s exactly what hackers count on. From fake Wi-Fi networks to s...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Agentic AI Handbook: A Beginner's Guide to Autonomous Intelligent Agents]]></title>
        <id>68371c1c13269a460c440e6c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-agentic-ai-handbook/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T14:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have heard about “Agentic AI” systems and wondered what they’re all about. Well, in basic terms, the idea behind Agentic AI is that it can see its surroundings, set and pursue goals, plan and reason through many processes, and learn from expe...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Balajee Asish Brahmandam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master REST API Development with .NET 9]]></title>
        <id>6837137d733fa231f684d399</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-rest-api-development-with-net-9/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:45:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building robust web applications and services requires a solid understanding of REST APIs, the backbone of modern web communication. Whether you're looking to create mobile app backends, integrate different systems, or build scalable web services, RE...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Your Own ViT Model from Scratch]]></title>
        <id>68371245a0ad7212aa3fe103</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-your-own-vit-model-from-scratch/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T13:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vision Transformers have fundamentally changed how we approach computer vision problems, delivering state-of-the-art results that often surpass traditional convolutional neural networks. As the industry shifts toward transformer-based architectures f...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliably Detecting Third-Party Cookie Blocking In 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/reliably-detecting-third-party-cookie-blocking-2025/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/reliably-detecting-third-party-cookie-blocking-2025/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The web is mired in a struggle to eliminate third-party cookies, with the World Wide Web Consortium Technical Architecture Group leading the charge. But there are obstacles preventing this from happening, and, as a result, many essential web features continue to rely on cookies to function properly. That’s why detecting third-party cookie blocking isn’t just good technical hygiene but a frontline defense for user experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Mikhail Prosmitskiy)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best AWS Services to Deploy Front-End Applications in 2025]]></title>
        <id>68363d68d27e47d637cc580b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-aws-services-for-frontend-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T22:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As front-end development evolves, finding the right deployment service is more important than ever. Amazon Web Services (AWS), a cloud-based service, offers a number of helpful tools and platforms for hosting modern front-end applications. Although i...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijeoma Igboagu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Your Raspberry Pi Headlessly with VS Code and SSH (No Monitor Needed)]]></title>
        <id>6835cf3101fd0876c3c66de0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-your-raspberry-pi-headlessly-with-vs-code-and-ssh/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T14:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi is a portable computer with an onboard processor that fits comfortably in the palm of your hand. Compared with general purpose computers, it’s an affordable option developed by the Raspberry Pi Foundation. The Raspberry Pi Model B wa...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josiah Adesola</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What We Know (So Far) About CSS Reading Order]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386654</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-we-know-so-far-about-css-reading-order/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The reading-flow and reading-order proposed CSS properties are designed to specify the source order of HTML elements in the DOM tree, or in simpler terms, how accessibility tools deduce the order of elements. You’d use them to make the focus order of focusable elements match the visual order, as outlined in the Web Content Accessibility Guidelines (WCAG 2.2).
What We Know (So Far) About CSS Reading Order originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Vs. Findings Vs. Insights In UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/data-vs-findings-vs-insights-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/data-vs-findings-vs-insights-ux/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-27T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the difference between data, findings, and UX insights? And how do you argue for statistical significance in your UX research? Let’s unpack it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Testing Framework for E-Commerce Checkout and Payments]]></title>
        <id>68308f32f4205e3b843cfb37</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-build-a-testing-framework-for-e-commerce-checkout-and-payments/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:07:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started working on E-commerce applications, I assumed testing checkout flows and payments would be straightforward. My expectation was simple: users select items, provide an address, pay, and receive confirmation. But I quickly learned t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Venkata Sai Sandeep</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Architecture of Mathematics – And How Developers Can Use it in Code]]></title>
        <id>68308ee8ccde6bc325c82393</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-architecture-of-mathematics-and-how-developers-can-use-it-in-code/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T15:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["To understand is to perceive patterns." - Isaiah Berlin Math is not just numbers. It is the science of finding complex patterns that shape our world. This means that to truly understand it, we need to see beyond numbers, formulas, and theorems and ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tiago Capelo Monteiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use React 19 in Power Apps PCF Components]]></title>
        <id>6830767c62d9a28c0de11007</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-use-react-19-in-pcf-components/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Power Apps Component Framework – PCF for short – lets you create complex custom components using traditional web development tools like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When creating a new PCF project, you can choose from two types of controls: standar...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Wozniewicz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 1: Lines and Arcs]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386640</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/better-css-shapes-using-shape-part-1-lines-and-arcs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T13:02:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the first part of a series that dives deep into the shape function, starting with shapes that use lines and arcs.
Better CSS Shapes Using shape() — Part 1: Lines and Arcs originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Zen And The Art Of Motorcycle Maintenance Can Teach Us About Web Design]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/what-zen-art-motorcycle-maintenance-teach-web-design/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/what-zen-art-motorcycle-maintenance-teach-web-design/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Road-tripping along the line between engineering and spirituality, Robert M. Pirsig’s musings on the arts, sciences, and Quality ring as true now as they ever have.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Laid off but not afraid with X-senior Microsoft Dev MacKevin Fey [Podcast #173]]]></title>
        <id>68304756ecdb03ab557f3974</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/laid-off-but-not-afraid-with-x-senior-microsoft-dev-mackevin-fey-podcast-173/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-23T10:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this week's episode of the podcast, freeCodeCamp founder Quincy Larson interviews MacKevin Fey. He just got laid off last week from his senior engineering role at Microsoft. We talk about: How Mack's approaching the job search after being laid of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Vue.js in This Beginner's Course]]></title>
        <id>682f84537a13a40bfa336307</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-vuejs-in-this-beginners-course/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T20:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve been meaning to add Vue.js to your front-end toolbelt, today’s your day. We just published a full, 6-hour Vue 3 course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Instructor Bhrugen Patel walks you through everything you need to build modern, ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Deploy Your FastAPI + PostgreSQL App on Render: A Beginner's Guide]]></title>
        <id>682f4900bcc94cb9bccbf905</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/deploy-fastapi-postgresql-app-on-render/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide is a comprehensive roadmap for deploying a FastAPI backend connected to a PostgreSQL database using Render, a cloud platform that supports hosting Python web apps and managed PostgreSQL databases.   You can find the complete source code he...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preston Osoro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Animated Introduction to Elixir]]></title>
        <id>682f44e3dcb21c615cf1a12d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-animated-introduction-to-elixir/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T15:38:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Elixir is a dynamic, functional programming language designed for building scalable and maintainable applications. It leverages the battle-tested Erlang VM, known for running low-latency, distributed, and fault-tolerant systems. Elixir is based on an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Mahoney</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can style alt text like any other text]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/you-can-style-alt-text-like-any-other-text/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-22T14:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clever, clever that Andy Bell. He shares a technique for displaying image alt text when the image fails to load. Well, more precisely, it's a technique to apply styles to the alt when the image doesn't load, offering a nice UI fallback for what would otherwise be a busted-looking error.
You can style alt text like any other text originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Database Management Systems]]></title>
        <id>682e3c04117e792e5f46edc3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/master-database-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T20:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding how to manage data effectively is a critical skill for anyone pursuing a career in tech. And we just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you all about Database Management Systems (DBMS). This in-de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Refactor Complex Codebases – A Practical Guide for Devs]]></title>
        <id>682df5a0f2057ab279952dbe</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-refactor-complex-codebases/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often see refactoring as a secondary concern that they can delay indefinitely because it doesn’t immediately contribute to revenue or feature development. And managers frequently view refactoring as "not a business need" until it boils ove...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ankur Tyagi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Vibe Coding Won't Destroy Software Engineering]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/why-vibe-coding-wont-destroy-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will “Vibe Coders” Take Our Dev Jobs?]]></title>
        <id>682df55da72360814bcae9ef</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/will-vibe-coders-take-our-dev-jobs/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI is disrupting all industries at a pace not seen at any time in history. Technologies and industries that were once dominated by one or two companies or were very much “human-focused” are coming under threat. Google is losing ground to AI search, t...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How JavaScript Lint Rules Work (and Why Abstract Syntax Trees Matter)]]></title>
        <id>682def7ddd9c9fdc3dae95cf</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-javascript-lint-rules-work-and-why-abstract-syntax-trees-matter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:21:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before I started to contribute to eslint-plugin-react, I didn’t think too deeply about the linters I used every day while writing code. Like many developers, I installed them at the start of a project, appreciated the red underlines or auto-fixes, an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tilda Udufo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVG to CSS Shape Converter]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386716</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/svg-to-css-shape-converter/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T15:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shape master Temani Afif has what might be the largest collection of CSS shapes on the planet with all the tools to generate them on the fly. There’s a mix of clever techniques he’s typically used to make those shapes, …
SVG to CSS Shape Converter originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Animations Part 3: SMIL’s Not Dead Baby, SMIL’s Not Dead]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/smashing-animations-part-3-smil-not-dead/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/smashing-animations-part-3-smil-not-dead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are plenty of ways that CSS animations can bring designs to life, adding simple SMIL (Synchronized Multimedia Integration Language) animations in SVG can help them do much more. Andy Clarke explains where SMIL animations in SVG take over where CSS leaves off.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Andy Clarke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn LangGraph and Build Conversational AI with Python]]></title>
        <id>682ca2c574938e5428551845</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-langgraph-and-build-conversational-ai-with-python/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-20T15:41:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you're building conversational AI and tired of messy logic or hard-to-scale workflows, LangGraph makes it easier. It uses graphs to manage dialogue flow, so your bots stay organized even as they get more complex. Great for anything from support ag...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals Crack Your Passwords (And How to Stay One Step Ahead)]]></title>
        <id>682b3930e99a22ce9f9199c8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-cybercriminals-crack-your-passwords-and-how-to-stay-one-step-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T13:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Passwords are the keys to your digital life  –  email, bank accounts, social media, and even your workplace systems. Unfortunately, they’re also one of the weakest links in cybersecurity.  Every year, billions of credentials are stolen and sold on th...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Manish Shivanandhan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Reader’s Question on Nested Lists]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=386580</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-readers-question-on-nested-lists/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T12:32:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Answering a reader's question about how to create a complex numbering system with CSS list counters.
A Reader’s Question on Nested Lists originally published on CSS-Tricks, which is part of the DigitalOcean family. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juan Diego Rodríguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design System In 90 Days]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/design-system-in-90-days/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2025/05/design-system-in-90-days/"/>
        <updated>2025-05-19T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helpful PDF worksheets and tools to get the design system effort up and running — and adopted! Kindly powered by How To Measure UX and Design Impact, a friendly course on how to show the impact of your incredible UX work on business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>